<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>The 3DS is a portable console that has the ability to produce three-dimensional images without the need for special glasses. It is the successor to the Nintendo DS, and is backwards compatible with the latter's software. Its main competitor is Sony's PlayStation Vita.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>La 3DS est une console portable qui a la capacité de produire des images tridimensionnelles sans besoin de lunettes spécifiques. Elle succède à la Nintendo DS, et est rétrocompatible avec les logiciels de cette dernière. Sa principale concurrente est la PlayStation Vita de Sony.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Der 3DS ist eine tragbare Konsole, die die Fähigkeit besitzt, dreidimensionale Bilder zu erzeugen, ohne dass eine spezielle Brille erforderlich ist. Er ist der Nachfolger des Nintendo DS und abwärtskompatibel mit dessen Software. Sein Hauptkonkurrent ist die PlayStation Vita von Sony.</text>
</text>


<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>La 3DS es una consola portátil capaz de producir imágenes tridimensionales sin necesidad de gafas especiales. Es la sucesora de la Nintendo DS y es retrocompatible con el software de esta última. Su principal competidora es la PlayStation Vita de Sony.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Il 3DS è una console portatile in grado di produrre immagini tridimensionali senza bisogno di occhiali speciali. È il successore del Nintendo DS ed è retrocompatibile con il software di quest'ultimo. Il suo principale concorrente è la PlayStation Vita di Sony.</text>
</text>


<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>3DSは、特殊なメガネを使わずに立体的な映像が楽しめる携帯ゲーム機です。ニンテンドーDSの後継機であり、DSのソフトとの後方互換性がある。主な競合機種はソニーの「プレイステーション ヴィータ」。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>De 3DS is een draagbare console die driedimensionale beelden kan weergeven zonder dat een speciale bril nodig is. Het is de opvolger van de Nintendo DS en is compatibel met de software van de Nintendo DS. Zijn belangrijkste concurrent is Sony's PlayStation Vita.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>3DS to przenośna konsola, która posiada możliwość tworzenia trójwymiarowych obrazów bez konieczności używania specjalnych okularów. Jest następcą Nintendo DS i jest wstecznie kompatybilna z oprogramowaniem tego ostatniego. Jej głównym konkurentem jest PlayStation Vita firmy Sony.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>O 3DS é uma consola portátil que tem a capacidade de produzir imagens tridimensionais sem a necessidade de óculos especiais. É o sucessor do Nintendo DS, e é retrocompatível com o software deste último. O seu principal concorrente é a PlayStation Vita da Sony.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>3DS - это портативная консоль, способная создавать трехмерные изображения без использования специальных очков. Она является преемницей Nintendo DS и имеет обратную совместимость с программным обеспечением последней. Ее главным конкурентом является PlayStation Vita от Sony.</text>
</text>


<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Professeur Layton et le Masque des Miracles (2012)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>Layton and Luke investigate Monte d'Or after a masked figure appears and performs impossible miracles. Their partnership blends observation, puzzle solving and playful exchanges between mentor and apprentice. This figurine highlights their first 3DS adventure and the elegant mystery tone of the series.
Fun fact: The game replaced the earlier 2D sprites with 3D character models while keeping the illustrated spirit of the saga.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Layton et Luke enquêtent à Dorémont après l’apparition d’un mystérieux homme masqué capable de provoquer des miracles. Leur duo repose sur l’observation, les énigmes et les échanges malicieux entre maître et apprenti. Cette figurine met en avant leur complicité, dans le premier épisode 3DS de la série.
Fun fact : Le jeu remplace les sprites 2D des anciens épisodes par des modèles 3D, tout en conservant l’esprit illustré de la saga.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Layton y Luke investigan en Monte d'Or tras la aparición de un misterioso hombre enmascarado capaz de provocar milagros. Su dúo combina observación, enigmas e intercambios cómplices entre maestro y aprendiz. Esta figura destaca su primera aventura en 3DS y el tono elegante de la serie.
Dato curioso: El juego sustituyó los sprites 2D anteriores por modelos 3D, manteniendo el espíritu ilustrado de la saga.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Layton e Luke indagano a Monte d'Or dopo l'apparizione di un misterioso uomo mascherato capace di compiere miracoli. Il loro duo unisce osservazione, enigmi e scambi arguti tra maestro e apprendista. Questa statuetta evidenzia la loro prima avventura su 3DS e il tono elegante della serie.
Curiosità: Il gioco sostituì gli sprite 2D dei capitoli precedenti con modelli 3D, conservando lo spirito illustrato della saga.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Layton und Luke ermitteln in Monte d'Or, nachdem ein geheimnisvoller maskierter Mann scheinbare Wunder vollbringt. Ihr Duo verbindet Beobachtung, Rätsel und gewitzte Gespräche zwischen Meister und Lehrling. Diese Figur betont ihr erstes 3DS-Abenteuer und den eleganten Mystery-Ton der Reihe.
Interessante Tatsache: Das Spiel ersetzte die früheren 2D-Sprites durch 3D-Modelle, bewahrte aber den illustrierten Stil der Serie.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Layton e Luke investigam em Monte d'Or após o aparecimento de um misterioso homem mascarado capaz de provocar milagres. A dupla combina observação, enigmas e diálogos cúmplices entre mestre e aprendiz. Esta figura destaca a primeira aventura da série no 3DS e o seu tom elegante de mistério.
Curiosidade: O jogo substituiu os sprites 2D anteriores por modelos 3D, mantendo o espírito ilustrado da saga.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
