<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>Acclaim Entertainment was a North American video game development and publishing company founded in 1987 and closed in 2004.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Acclaim Entertainment était une société nord-américaine de développement et d'édition de jeux vidéo fondée en 1987 et disparue en 2004.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Acclaim Entertainment war ein nordamerikanisches Unternehmen für die Entwicklung und Veröffentlichung von Videospielen, das 1987 gegründet wurde und 2004 verschwand.</text>
</text>


<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Acclaim Entertainment fue un desarrollador y editor de videojuegos norteamericano fundado en 1987 y desaparecido en 2004.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Acclaim Entertainment è stato uno sviluppatore ed editore di videogiochi nordamericano fondato nel 1987 e scomparso nel 2004.</text>
</text>


<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>アクレイム・エンターテイメントは、1987年に設立され、2004年に消滅した北米のビデオゲーム開発会社およびパブリッシャーです。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>Acclaim Entertainment was een Noord-Amerikaanse ontwikkelaar en uitgever van videospelletjes, opgericht in 1987 en verdwenen in 2004.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>Acclaim Entertainment był północnoamerykańskim producentem i wydawcą gier wideo, założonym w 1987 roku i nieistniejącym od 2004 roku.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Acclaim Entertainment foi uma empresa norte-americana de desenvolvimento e publicação de jogos de vídeo fundada em 1987 e extinta em 2004.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>Acclaim Entertainment - североамериканский разработчик и издатель видеоигр, основанный в 1987 году и прекративший существование в 2004 году.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
