<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>The Coleco Adam is a personal computer from the Connecticut Leather Company (Coleco). It is also a plug-in for the Colecovision console. It was a commercial failure for the company.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Le Coleco Adam est un ordinateur personnel de la société Connecticut Leather Company (Coleco). Il s'agit également d'un module d'extension pour la console Colecovision. C'est un échec commercial pour la société.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Der Coleco Adam ist ein Personalcomputer der Firma Connecticut Leather Company (Coleco). Er ist auch ein Erweiterungsmodul für die Konsole Colecovision. Es war ein kommerzieller Misserfolg für das Unternehmen.</text>
</text>


<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>El Coleco Adam es un ordenador personal de la Connecticut Leather Company (Coleco). También es un complemento para la consola Colecovision. Fue un fracaso comercial para la empresa.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Il Coleco Adam è un personal computer della Connecticut Leather Company (Coleco). È anche un plug-in per la console Colecovision. Fu un fallimento commerciale per l'azienda.</text>
</text>


<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>Coleco Adamは、Connecticut Leather Company（Coleco社）のパーソナルコンピュータである。また、ゲーム機「Colecovision」のプラグインでもある。同社にとっては商業的に失敗作であった。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>De Coleco Adam is een personal computer van de Connecticut Leather Company (Coleco). Het is ook een plug-in voor de Colecovision console. Het was een commerciële mislukking voor het bedrijf.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>Coleco Adam to komputer osobisty firmy Connecticut Leather Company (Coleco). Jest to również wtyczka do konsoli Colecovision. Była to komercyjna porażka dla firmy.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>O Coleco Adam é um computador pessoal da Connecticut Leather Company (Coleco). É também um plug-in para a consola Colecovision. Foi um fracasso comercial para a empresa.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>Coleco Adam - это персональный компьютер от компании Connecticut Leather Company (Coleco). Он также является плагином для консоли Colecovision. Для компании это был коммерческий провал.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
