 <!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>The CDTV, for Commodore Dynamic Total Vision, is a personal computer and game console in the form of a black turntable. It was aimed at a family audience that was new to computers, interested in games but also in multimedia capabilities and interactivity.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Le CDTV, pour Commodore Dynamic Total Vision, est un ordinateur personnel et une console de jeu prenant la forme d'une platine de salon de couleur noire. Elle visait un public familial néophyte en informatique, intéressé par les jeux mais aussi par les capacités multimédia et l'interactivité.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Der CDTV, der für Commodore Dynamic Total Vision steht, ist ein Personal Computer und eine Spielkonsole in Form eines schwarzen Plattenspielers für das Wohnzimmer. Er zielte auf ein Familienpublikum ab, das Computerneulinge war und sich für Spiele, aber auch für Multimediafähigkeiten und Interaktivität interessierte.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>El CDTV, por Commodore Dynamic Total Vision, es un ordenador personal y consola de juegos con forma de tocadiscos negro. Estaba dirigido a un público familiar que se iniciaba en la informática, interesado en los juegos pero también en las capacidades multimedia y la interactividad.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Il CDTV, acronimo di Commodore Dynamic Total Vision, è un personal computer e una console di gioco a forma di giradischi nero. Si rivolgeva a un pubblico familiare alle prime armi con i computer, interessato ai giochi ma anche alle funzionalità multimediali e all'interattività.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>CDTVは、コモドール・ダイナミック・トータル・ビジョンの略で、黒いターンテーブルの形をしたパーソナルコンピュータとゲーム機である。コンピュータに初めて触れるファミリー層をターゲットに、ゲームだけでなくマルチメディア機能やインタラクティビティにも関心を持たせた。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>De CDTV, voor Commodore Dynamic Total Vision, is een personal computer en spelconsole in de vorm van een zwarte draaitafel. Het was gericht op een familiepubliek dat nieuw was met computers, geïnteresseerd in spelletjes maar ook in multimediamogelijkheden en interactiviteit.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>CDTV, czyli Commodore Dynamic Total Vision, to komputer osobisty i konsola do gier w formie czarnego gramofonu. Była skierowana do rodzinnej publiczności, która była nowa dla komputerów, zainteresowana grami, ale także możliwościami multimedialnymi i interaktywnością.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>O CDTV, para Commodore Dynamic Total Vision, é um computador pessoal e uma consola de jogos sob a forma de mesa giratória preta. Era dirigido a um público familiar que era novo nos computadores, interessado em jogos mas também em capacidades multimédia e interactividade.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>CDTV, для Commodore Dynamic Total Vision, - это персональный компьютер и игровая консоль в виде черного проигрывателя. Он был нацелен на семейную аудиторию, которая была новичком в компьютерах, заинтересована в играх, а также в мультимедийных возможностях и интерактивности.</text>
</text>


<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Sherlock Holmes: Consulting Detective (1991)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>On CDTV, Sherlock Holmes is represented through several episodes of the Consulting Detective series, offering different interactive investigations. These titles use the CD-ROM format to deliver a rich narrative approach, mixing video, testimonies and free exploration, typical of the first multimedia experiments of the early 90s.
Fun fact: The investigations are based on cases inspired by the writings of Arthur Conan Doyle, with a structure that allows several paths to resolution.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Sur CDTV, Sherlock Holmes est représenté à travers plusieurs épisodes de la série Consulting Detective, proposant différentes enquêtes interactives. Ces titres exploitent le support CD-ROM pour offrir une approche narrative riche, mêlant vidéos, témoignages et exploration libre, typique des premières expériences multimédia du début des années 90.
Fun fact : Les enquêtes sont basées sur des cas inspirés des écrits d’Arthur Conan Doyle, avec une structure permettant plusieurs chemins de résolution.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>En CDTV, Sherlock Holmes está representado por varios episodios de la serie Consulting Detective, con diferentes investigaciones interactivas. Estos títulos aprovechan el CD-ROM para ofrecer un enfoque narrativo rico, con vídeos, testimonios y exploración libre, típico de las primeras experiencias multimedia de los años 90.
Dato curioso: Las investigaciones se basan en casos inspirados en los escritos de Arthur Conan Doyle, con una estructura que permite varios caminos de resolución.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Su CDTV, Sherlock Holmes è rappresentato da diversi episodi della serie Consulting Detective, con varie indagini interattive. Questi titoli sfruttano il CD-ROM per offrire un approccio narrativo ricco, tra video, testimonianze ed esplorazione libera, tipico delle prime esperienze multimediali dei primi anni 90.
Curiosità: Le indagini si basano su casi ispirati agli scritti di Arthur Conan Doyle, con una struttura che permette più percorsi di risoluzione.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Auf CDTV ist Sherlock Holmes durch mehrere Episoden der Consulting-Detective-Reihe vertreten, mit verschiedenen interaktiven Ermittlungen. Diese Titel nutzen das CD-ROM-Format für einen erzählerisch dichten Ansatz mit Videos, Aussagen und freier Erkundung, typisch für frühe Multimedia-Erfahrungen der frühen 90er.
Interessante Tatsache: Die Ermittlungen basieren auf Fällen, die von Arthur Conan Doyles Schriften inspiriert sind, mit einer Struktur, die mehrere Lösungswege erlaubt.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>No CDTV, Sherlock Holmes é representado por vários episódios da série Consulting Detective, com diferentes investigações interativas. Estes títulos exploram o CD-ROM para oferecer uma abordagem narrativa rica, com vídeos, testemunhos e exploração livre, típica das primeiras experiências multimédia do início dos anos 90.
Curiosidade: As investigações baseiam-se em casos inspirados nos escritos de Arthur Conan Doyle, com uma estrutura que permite vários caminhos de resolução.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
