<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>The A4000 was the successor to the A2000 and A3000 computers. The machine was available in several models equipped respectively with a Motorola 68EC030 and a Motorola 68040, as well as the A4000T, which was a tower version with a different internal architecture. The last units produced by Escom after their takeover of Commodore included a 68060 processor running at 50Mhz. </text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>L'A4000 était le successeur des ordinateurs A2000 et A3000. La machine était disponible en plusieurs modèles équipés respectivement d'un Motorola 68EC030 et d'un Motorola 68040 ainsi que l'A4000T qui était une version en tour à l'architecture interne différente et dont les dernières unités produites par Escom après leur rachat de Commodore incluaient un processeur 68060 cadencé à 50Mhz. </text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>El A4000 fue el sucesor de los ordenadores A2000 y A3000. La máquina estuvo disponible en varios modelos equipados respectivamente con un Motorola 68EC030 y un Motorola 68040, además del A4000T, una versión torre con una arquitectura interna diferente. Las últimas unidades producidas por Escom tras adquirir Commodore incluían un procesador 68060 a 50Mhz.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>L'A4000 fu il successore dei computer A2000 e A3000. La macchina era disponibile in vari modelli equipaggiati rispettivamente con un Motorola 68EC030 e un Motorola 68040, oltre all'A4000T, una versione tower con architettura interna diversa. Le ultime unità prodotte da Escom dopo l'acquisizione di Commodore includevano un processore 68060 a 50Mhz.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Der A4000 war der Nachfolger der Computer A2000 und A3000. Die Maschine war in mehreren Modellen erhältlich, die jeweils mit einem Motorola 68EC030 und einem Motorola 68040 ausgestattet waren, sowie als A4000T, eine Tower-Version mit anderer interner Architektur. Die letzten von Escom nach der Übernahme von Commodore produzierten Geräte enthielten einen 68060-Prozessor mit 50Mhz.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>O A4000 foi o sucessor dos computadores A2000 e A3000. A máquina esteve disponível em vários modelos equipados respetivamente com um Motorola 68EC030 e um Motorola 68040, além do A4000T, uma versão em torre com arquitetura interna diferente. As últimas unidades produzidas pela Escom após a compra da Commodore incluíam um processador 68060 a 50Mhz.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Agony (1992)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>Agony is a fantasy horizontal shoot'em up where the player controls an owl crossing six natural worlds filled with monsters, traps and bosses. Driven by a dark atmosphere, parallax scenery and memorable music, the game values mood as much as action, with magic shots and powers to collect.
Fun fact: Agony's owl echoes the Psygnosis emblem, turning the publisher's logo into a playable hero within a medieval fantasy world.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Agony est un shoot’em up horizontal fantastique où le joueur contrôle une chouette traversant six mondes naturels peuplés de monstres, de pièges et de boss. Porté par une ambiance sombre, des décors en parallaxe et une musique marquante, le jeu privilégie l’atmosphère autant que l’action, avec des tirs magiques et des pouvoirs à récupérer.
Fun fact : La chouette d’Agony reprend l’emblème de Psygnosis, transformant le logo de l’éditeur en héros jouable dans un univers médiéval-fantastique.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Agony es un shoot’em up horizontal fantástico donde el jugador controla un búho que cruza seis mundos naturales llenos de monstruos, trampas y jefes. Con una atmósfera oscura, escenarios en paralaje y música memorable, el juego valora tanto el ambiente como la acción, con disparos mágicos y poderes por recoger.
Dato curioso: El búho de Agony retoma el emblema de Psygnosis, convirtiendo el logotipo del editor en un héroe jugable dentro de un mundo medieval fantástico.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Agony è uno shoot’em up orizzontale fantasy in cui il giocatore controlla un gufo attraverso sei mondi naturali pieni di mostri, trappole e boss. Con atmosfera cupa, scenari in parallasse e musica memorabile, il gioco valorizza l’atmosfera quanto l’azione, con colpi magici e poteri da raccogliere.
Curiosità: Il gufo di Agony richiama l’emblema di Psygnosis, trasformando il logo dell’editore in un eroe giocabile dentro un mondo fantasy medievale.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Agony ist ein fantastisches horizontales Shoot’em up, in dem der Spieler eine Eule durch sechs Naturwelten voller Monster, Fallen und Bosse steuert. Mit dunkler Atmosphäre, Parallax-Kulissen und prägnanter Musik setzt das Spiel ebenso auf Stimmung wie auf Action, mit magischen Schüssen und sammelbaren Kräften.
Interessante Tatsache: Die Eule aus Agony greift das Psygnosis-Emblem auf und macht das Logo des Publishers zum spielbaren Helden einer mittelalterlichen Fantasywelt.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Agony é um shoot’em up horizontal fantástico onde o jogador controla uma coruja através de seis mundos naturais cheios de monstros, armadilhas e bosses. Com atmosfera sombria, cenários em paralaxe e música marcante, o jogo valoriza tanto o ambiente como a ação, com tiros mágicos e poderes para recolher.
Curiosidade: A coruja de Agony retoma o emblema da Psygnosis, transformando o logótipo da editora num herói jogável dentro de um mundo medieval fantástico.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
