 <!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>The Amiga 500 is the first entry-level model in Commodore's Amiga family of personal computers. It was released in 1987, two years after the Amiga 1000, at the same time as the high-end Amiga 2000. It competed directly with the Atari 520ST. The Amiga 500+ released in 1991 is a slightly improved version.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>L'Amiga 500 est le premier modèle d'entrée de gamme de la famille d'ordinateurs personnels Amiga de Commodore. Il sort en 1987, deux ans après l'Amiga 1000, en même temps que le modèle haut de gamme Amiga 2000. Il est en concurrence directe avec l'Atari 520ST. L'Amiga 500+ sortie en 1991 en est une version légèrement améliorée.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Der Amiga 500 ist das erste Einstiegsmodell der Amiga-Personalcomputerfamilie von Commodore. Er kam 1987, zwei Jahre nach dem Amiga 1000, zusammen mit dem Spitzenmodell Amiga 2000 auf den Markt. Er stand in direkter Konkurrenz zum Atari 520ST. Der 1991 veröffentlichte Amiga 500+ ist eine leicht verbesserte Version des Amiga.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>El Amiga 500 es el primer modelo básico de la familia Amiga de ordenadores personales de Commodore. Salió a la venta en 1987, dos años después del Amiga 1000, al mismo tiempo que el Amiga 2000 de gama alta. Compitió directamente con el Atari 520ST. El Amiga 500+ lanzado en 1991 es una versión ligeramente mejorada.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>L'Amiga 500 è il primo modello entry-level della famiglia di personal computer Amiga di Commodore. È stato rilasciato nel 1987, due anni dopo l'Amiga 1000, contemporaneamente all'Amiga 2000 di fascia alta. Era in concorrenza diretta con l'Atari 520ST. L'Amiga 500+ rilasciato nel 1991 è una versione leggermente migliorata.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>Amiga 500は、コモドール社のパーソナルコンピュータ「Amiga」シリーズの最初のエントリーモデルです。Amiga 1000から2年後の1987年に、ハイエンドのAmiga 2000と同時に発売された。アタリ520STと直接競合していた。1991年に発売されたAmiga500+は、若干の改良が加えられたバージョンである。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>De Amiga 500 was het eerste instapmodel in Commodore's Amiga familie van personal computers. Het werd uitgebracht in 1987, twee jaar na de Amiga 1000, tegelijk met de high-end Amiga 2000. Het concurreerde rechtstreeks met de Atari 520ST. De Amiga 500+ uitgebracht in 1991 is een licht verbeterde versie.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>Amiga 500 to pierwszy podstawowy model w rodzinie komputerów osobistych Amiga firmy Commodore. Została wydana w 1987 roku, dwa lata po Amidze 1000, w tym samym czasie co high-endowa Amiga 2000. Konkurowała bezpośrednio z Atari 520ST. Amiga 500+ wydana w 1991 roku to nieco ulepszona wersja.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>O Amiga 500 é o primeiro modelo de nível básico na família de computadores pessoais Amiga da Commodore. Foi lançado em 1987, dois anos após o Amiga 1000, ao mesmo tempo que o Amiga 2000 de gama alta. Competiu directamente com o Atari 520ST. O Amiga 500+, lançado em 1991, é uma versão ligeiramente melhorada.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>Amiga 500 - это первая модель начального уровня в семействе персональных компьютеров Amiga компании Commodore. Она была выпущена в 1987 году, через два года после Amiga 1000, одновременно с высококлассной Amiga 2000. Она напрямую конкурировала с Atari 520ST. Amiga 500+, выпущенная в 1991 году, является немного улучшенной версией.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Superfrog (1993)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>Superfrog tells the story of a prince turned into a frog who sets out on an adventure to regain his human form. Initially released on Amiga, the game stands out for its fast pace, colorful presentation and typically British humor, which became representative of Team17’s craft (future creator of the iconic Worms series).
Fun fact: The game features an unusual product placement with Lucozade bottles, even outside the United Kingdom where many thought they were a fictional drink.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Superfrog raconte l’histoire d’un prince transformé en grenouille qui part à l’aventure pour retrouver sa forme humaine. Initialement sorti sur Amiga, le jeu se distingue par son rythme rapide, sa réalisation colorée et son humour typiquement britannique, devenus représentatifs du savoir-faire de Team17 (futur créateur de l’emblématique série Worms).
Fun fact : Le jeu intègre un placement de produit inhabituel avec les bouteilles de Lucozade, même hors Royaume-Uni où beaucoup pensaient à une boisson fictive.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Superfrog cuenta la historia de un príncipe transformado en rana que parte de aventura para recuperar su forma humana. Lanzado inicialmente en Amiga, el juego destaca por su ritmo rápido, su apartado colorido y su humor típicamente británico, convertidos en señas del saber hacer de Team17 (futuro creador de la emblemática serie Worms).
Dato curioso: El juego integra un emplazamiento de producto poco habitual con las botellas de Lucozade, incluso fuera del Reino Unido, donde muchos pensaban que era una bebida ficticia.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Superfrog racconta la storia di un principe trasformato in rana che parte all’avventura per ritrovare la sua forma umana. Uscito inizialmente su Amiga, il gioco si distingue per il ritmo rapido, la grafica colorata e l’umorismo tipicamente britannico, diventati rappresentativi del talento di Team17 (futuro creatore dell’emblematica serie Worms).
Curiosità: Il gioco integra un product placement insolito con le bottiglie di Lucozade, anche fuori dal Regno Unito, dove molti pensavano fosse una bevanda immaginaria.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Superfrog erzählt die Geschichte eines Prinzen, der in einen Frosch verwandelt wurde und sich aufmacht, seine menschliche Gestalt zurückzuerlangen. Ursprünglich für Amiga erschienen, fällt das Spiel durch sein hohes Tempo, die farbenfrohe Gestaltung und den typisch britischen Humor auf, die repräsentativ für das Können von Team17 wurden (späterer Schöpfer der legendären Worms-Reihe).
Interessante Tatsache: Das Spiel enthält eine ungewöhnliche Produktplatzierung mit Lucozade-Flaschen, sogar außerhalb des Vereinigten Königreichs, wo viele sie für ein fiktives Getränk hielten.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Superfrog conta a história de um príncipe transformado em sapo que parte em aventura para recuperar a sua forma humana. Lançado inicialmente no Amiga, o jogo destaca-se pelo ritmo rápido, pelo visual colorido e pelo humor tipicamente britânico, que se tornaram representativos do saber fazer da Team17 (futura criadora da emblemática série Worms).
Curiosidade: O jogo inclui uma colocação de produto invulgar com garrafas de Lucozade, mesmo fora do Reino Unido, onde muitos pensavam tratar-se de uma bebida fictícia.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
