 <!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>The CD32 is a 32-bit console whose architecture is based on the Amiga 1200 computer. It was the first 32-bit console to be released in the West (the FM Towns Marty preceded it in Japan). It did not manage to break into the market despite the support of Amiga fans.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>La CD32 est une console 32-bit dont l'architecture est basée sur l'ordinateur Amiga 1200. Il s'agit de la première 32-bit à voir le jour en Occident (la FM Towns Marty l'a précédée au Japon). Elle ne sera pas parvenue à percer sur le marché malgré le soutien des fans de la gamme Amiga.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Der CD32 ist eine 32-Bit-Konsole, deren Architektur auf dem Computer Amiga 1200 basiert. Sie war die erste 32-Bit-Konsole, die im Westen auf den Markt kam (in Japan war die FM Towns Marty vor ihr erschienen). Trotz der Unterstützung durch die Fans der Amiga-Reihe gelang ihr der Durchbruch auf dem Markt nicht.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>La CD32 es una consola de 32 bits cuya arquitectura se basa en el ordenador Amiga 1200. Fue la primera consola de 32 bits que salió a la venta en Occidente (la FM Towns Marty la precedió en Japón). No consiguió introducirse en el mercado a pesar del apoyo de los aficionados a Amiga.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Il CD32 è una console a 32 bit la cui architettura è basata sul computer Amiga 1200. È stata la prima console a 32 bit a essere rilasciata in Occidente (la FM Towns Marty l'ha preceduta in Giappone). Non è riuscita a sfondare sul mercato nonostante il supporto dei fan di Amiga.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>CD32は、Amiga 1200コンピュータをベースとしたアーキテクチャを持つ32ビットゲーム機です。欧米で発売された最初の32ビットゲーム機です（日本ではFMタウンズマーティが先行して発売されました）。Amigaファンの支持を得たが、市場には定着しなかった。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>De CD32 is een 32-bit console waarvan de architectuur is gebaseerd op de Amiga 1200 computer. Het was de eerste 32-bit console die in het Westen werd uitgebracht (de FM Towns Marty ging hem voor in Japan). Ondanks de steun van Amiga-fans slaagde hij er niet in door te breken op de markt.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>CD32 to 32-bitowa konsola, której architektura została oparta na komputerze Amiga 1200. Była to pierwsza 32-bitowa konsola wydana na Zachodzie (w Japonii poprzedzała ją FM Towns Marty). Nie udało jej się przebić na rynku mimo wsparcia fanów Amigi.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>O CD32 é uma consola de 32-bit cuja arquitectura é baseada no computador Amiga 1200. É a primeira consola de 32-bit a ser lançada no Ocidente (a FM Towns Marty precedeu-a no Japão). Não conseguiu penetrar no mercado apesar do apoio dos fãs do Amiga.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>CD32 - это 32-битная консоль, архитектура которой основана на компьютере Amiga 1200. Это была первая 32-битная консоль, выпущенная на Западе (в Японии ей предшествовала FM Towns Marty). Несмотря на поддержку фанатов Amiga, ей не удалось пробиться на рынок.</text>
</text>


<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Alien Breed: Special Edition ’92 (1994)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>The special edition of the game arrived on Amiga CD32 mainly through bundles and compilations accompanying the console, rather than as an independent release. This pack-in distribution helped make it one of the games most associated with the machine during its commercial life.
Fun fact: The game was developed with strong inspiration from the film Alien, to the point that its atmosphere and creatures were sometimes seen by players as an unofficial adaptation.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>L’édition spéciale du jeu arrive sur Amiga CD32 principalement via des bundles et compilations accompagnant la console, plutôt que comme sortie indépendante. Cette diffusion en pack contribue à en faire l’un des jeux les plus associés à la machine lors de sa commercialisation.
Fun fact : Le jeu a été développé en s’inspirant fortement du film Alien, au point que son ambiance et ses créatures ont parfois été perçues comme une adaptation non officielle par les joueurs.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>La edición especial del juego llegó a Amiga CD32 principalmente a través de bundles y recopilatorios que acompañaban a la consola, más que como lanzamiento independiente. Esta distribución en pack ayudó a convertirlo en uno de los juegos más asociados a la máquina durante su comercialización.
Dato curioso: El juego se desarrolló con una fuerte inspiración en la película Alien, hasta el punto de que su atmósfera y criaturas fueron vistas a veces por los jugadores como una adaptación no oficial.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>L’edizione speciale del gioco arrivò su Amiga CD32 principalmente tramite bundle e compilation che accompagnavano la console, più che come uscita indipendente. Questa distribuzione in pack contribuì a renderlo uno dei giochi più associati alla macchina durante la sua commercializzazione.
Curiosità: Il gioco fu sviluppato con una forte ispirazione al film Alien, al punto che atmosfera e creature furono talvolta percepite dai giocatori come un adattamento non ufficiale.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Die Sonderedition des Spiels erschien auf Amiga CD32 vor allem über Bundles und Compilations, die der Konsole beilagen, statt als eigenständige Veröffentlichung. Diese Verbreitung im Paket trug dazu bei, es während der Vermarktung zu einem der am stärksten mit der Maschine verbundenen Spiele zu machen.
Interessante Tatsache: Das Spiel wurde stark vom Film Alien inspiriert, sodass Atmosphäre und Kreaturen von Spielern teils als inoffizielle Adaption wahrgenommen wurden.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>A edição especial do jogo chegou ao Amiga CD32 principalmente através de bundles e compilações que acompanhavam a consola, mais do que como lançamento independente. Esta distribuição em pack ajudou a torná-lo um dos jogos mais associados à máquina durante a sua comercialização.
Curiosidade: O jogo foi desenvolvido com forte inspiração no filme Alien, ao ponto de a sua atmosfera e criaturas terem sido por vezes vistas pelos jogadores como uma adaptação não oficial.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
