 <!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>The APF-MP1000 is a cartridge-based video game console. The two controllers are not detachable and include a joystick and a 12-button pad each. It comes with a built-in game, Rocket Patrol, and can only be used on a colour television.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>L'APF-MP1000 est une console de jeux vidéo à cartouches. Les deux contrôleurs ne sont pas détachables, ils comprennent un joystick et un pavé de 12 boutons chacun. Livrée avec un jeu intégré, Rocket Patrol, elle peut être utilisée que sur une télévision couleur.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Der APF-MP1000 ist eine Videospielkonsole mit Kassetten. Die beiden Controller sind nicht abnehmbar und bestehen aus einem Joystick und einem Tastenfeld mit jeweils 12 Tasten. Sie wird mit dem integrierten Spiel Rocket Patrol geliefert und kann nur auf einem Farbfernseher verwendet werden.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>La APF-MP1000 es una videoconsola basada en cartuchos. Los dos mandos no son desmontables e incluyen un joystick y un pad de 12 botones cada uno. Viene con un juego incorporado, Rocket Patrol, y sólo puede utilizarse en un televisor en color.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>L'APF-MP1000 è una console per videogiochi basata su cartucce. I due controller non sono staccabili e comprendono un joystick e un pad a 12 tasti ciascuno. Viene fornita con un gioco incorporato, Rocket Patrol, e può essere utilizzata solo su un televisore a colori.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>APF-MP1000は、カートリッジを使用したゲーム機です。2つのコントローラは着脱式ではなく、ジョイスティックと12ボタンパッドがそれぞれ1つずつ入っています。ゲーム「ロケットパトロール」が内蔵されており、カラーテレビでのみ使用できる。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>De APF-MP1000 is een videospelconsole op basis van een cartridge. De twee controllers zijn niet afneembaar en bevatten elk een joystick en een pad met 12 knoppen. Hij wordt geleverd met een ingebouwd spel, Rocket Patrol, en kan alleen worden gebruikt op een kleurentelevisie.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>APF-MP1000 to konsola do gier wideo oparta na kartridżach. Dwa kontrolery nie są odłączane i zawierają joystick oraz pad z 12 przyciskami każdy. Posiada wbudowaną grę Rocket Patrol i może być używana tylko na kolorowym telewizorze.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>O APF-MP1000 é uma consola de videojogos baseada em cartuchos. Os dois controladores não são destacáveis e incluem um joystick e um bloco de 12 botões cada um. Vem com um jogo incorporado, Rocket Patrol, e só pode ser utilizado numa televisão a cores.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>APF-MP1000 - это игровая консоль на базе картриджа. Два контроллера не являются съемными и включают в себя джойстик и 12-кнопочную панель каждый. Она поставляется со встроенной игрой Rocket Patrol и может использоваться только с цветным телевизором.</text>
</text>


<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Grayskull - Heman&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>Adam rides Battle Cat with a calm, heroic presence, ready to become He-Man and defend the power of Grayskull. The scene focuses on the bond between the prince and his armored steed, using a simple but iconic composition that immediately recalls Eternia, its fantasy atmosphere and the visual identity of Masters of the Universe.
Fun fact: Battle Cat was released by Mattel in 1982 as part of the first Masters of the Universe toy line, using a reworked Big Jim tiger mold.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Adam chevauche ici son tigre de combat dans une posture assurée, déjà prêt à incarner la puissance de Musclor. L’ensemble évoque directement l’univers d’Eternia et ses figures emblématiques, avec une mise en scène simple qui met en avant le lien entre le prince et sa monture, symbole de courage et de transformation.
Fun fact : Le tigre de combat a été commercialisé par Mattel en 1982 dans la première gamme Masters of the Universe, avec un moule issu de la ligne Big Jim.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Adam cabalga aquí sobre Battle Cat con una postura segura, listo para encarnar el poder de He-Man y proteger Grayskull. La escena evoca directamente el universo de Eternia y sus figuras emblemáticas, con una composición sencilla que destaca el vínculo entre el príncipe y su montura, símbolo de valor y transformación.
Dato curioso: Battle Cat fue lanzado por Mattel en 1982 dentro de la primera línea Masters of the Universe, usando un molde adaptado de Big Jim.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Adam cavalca Battle Cat con una posa sicura, già pronto a incarnare la forza di He-Man e difendere Grayskull. La scena richiama direttamente l’universo di Eternia e le sue figure simboliche, con una composizione semplice che mette in risalto il legame tra il principe e la sua cavalcatura, emblema di coraggio e trasformazione.
Curiosità: Battle Cat fu commercializzato da Mattel nel 1982 nella prima linea Masters of the Universe, usando uno stampo derivato da Big Jim.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Adam reitet hier auf Battle Cat in einer sicheren Haltung, bereit, die Kraft von He-Man zu verkörpern und Grayskull zu verteidigen. Die Szene erinnert direkt an Eternia und seine bekannten Figuren, mit einer klaren Inszenierung, die die Verbindung zwischen dem Prinzen und seinem Reittier als Symbol für Mut und Verwandlung betont.
Interessante Tatsache: Battle Cat wurde 1982 von Mattel in der ersten Masters-of-the-Universe-Reihe veröffentlicht und nutzte eine überarbeitete Big-Jim-Tigerform.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Adam cavalga Battle Cat numa postura confiante, já pronto para encarnar o poder de He-Man e defender Grayskull. A cena evoca diretamente o universo de Eternia e as suas figuras emblemáticas, com uma composição simples que destaca a ligação entre o príncipe e a sua montada, símbolo de coragem e transformação.
Curiosidade: Battle Cat foi lançado pela Mattel em 1982 na primeira linha Masters of the Universe, usando um molde adaptado da coleção Big Jim.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
