 <!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>The Apple II has a special place in the history of computing. It was the first successful personal computer to be produced on a large scale. Personal computers, then confined to the garages of enthusiasts, became available to millions of homes and small businesses, mainly in the United States.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>L'Apple II occupe une place particulière dans l'histoire de l'informatique. Il est le premier ordinateur personnel à rencontrer le succès et produit à grande échelle. Les ordinateurs personnels, alors cantonnés dans les garages de passionnés, sont devenus accessibles à des millions de foyers et aux petites entreprises, principalement aux Etats-Unis.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Der Apple II nimmt einen besonderen Platz in der Geschichte der Computer ein. Er war der erste erfolgreiche Personal Computer, der in großem Umfang produziert wurde. Computer, die bis dahin nur in den Garagen von Enthusiasten zu finden waren, wurden für Millionen von Haushalten und kleinen Unternehmen, vor allem in den USA, erschwinglich.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>El Apple II ocupa un lugar especial en la historia de la informática. Fue el primer ordenador personal fabricado con éxito a gran escala. Los ordenadores personales, entonces confinados a los garajes de los entusiastas, pasaron a estar al alcance de millones de hogares y pequeñas empresas, principalmente en Estados Unidos.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>L'Apple II occupa un posto speciale nella storia dell'informatica. È stato il primo personal computer di successo a essere prodotto su larga scala. I personal computer, allora confinati nei garage degli appassionati, divennero disponibili per milioni di case e piccole imprese, soprattutto negli Stati Uniti.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>Apple IIは、コンピュータの歴史の中で特別な位置を占めている。Apple IIは、大規模な生産に成功した最初のパーソナルコンピュータである。当時は愛好家のガレージにしかなかったパソコンが、アメリカを中心に何百万という家庭や中小企業で利用されるようになったのだ。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>De Apple II heeft een bijzondere plaats in de geschiedenis van de computerwereld. Het was de eerste succesvolle personal computer die op grote schaal werd geproduceerd. Personal computers, toen nog beperkt tot de garages van liefhebbers, werden beschikbaar voor miljoenen huishoudens en kleine bedrijven, voornamelijk in de Verenigde Staten.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>Apple II zajmuje szczególne miejsce w historii informatyki. Był to pierwszy udany komputer osobisty produkowany na dużą skalę. Komputery osobiste, wówczas ograniczone do garaży entuzjastów, stały się dostępne dla milionów domów i małych firm, głównie w Stanach Zjednoczonych.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>O Apple II tem um lugar especial na história da informática. Foi o primeiro computador pessoal de sucesso a ser produzido em grande escala. Os computadores pessoais, então confinados às garagens dos entusiastes, tornaram-se disponíveis para milhões de lares e pequenas empresas, principalmente nos Estados Unidos.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>Apple II занимает особое место в истории вычислительной техники. Это был первый успешный персональный компьютер, выпускавшийся в больших масштабах. Персональные компьютеры, в то время ограничивавшиеся гаражами энтузиастов, стали доступны в миллионах домов и малых предприятий, в основном в США.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Prince of Persia (1989)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>The Prince is an agile hero moving through a palace filled with deadly traps, where every jump and duel demands precision and timing. On Apple II, the realistic animation, created through rotoscoping, stands out for its time and strengthens the tension of this demanding oriental adventure.
Fun fact: Jordan Mechner filmed his own brother to create the Prince's realistic animations through rotoscoping.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Le Prince incarne un héros agile évoluant dans un palais truffé de pièges mortels, où chaque saut et chaque duel demandent précision et timing. Sur Apple II, l’animation réaliste, obtenue grâce à la rotoscopie, se distingue pour l’époque et renforce l’immersion dans cet univers oriental tendu et exigeant.
Fun fact : Jordan Mechner a utilisé son propre frère comme modèle filmé pour créer les animations réalistes du Prince via la rotoscopie.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>El Príncipe encarna a un héroe ágil que avanza por un palacio lleno de trampas mortales, donde cada salto y cada duelo exigen precisión y buen ritmo. En Apple II, la animación realista, creada mediante rotoscopia, destaca para su época y refuerza la inmersión en este entorno oriental tenso y exigente.
Dato curioso: Jordan Mechner filmó a su propio hermano para crear las animaciones realistas del Príncipe mediante rotoscopia.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Il Principe incarna un eroe agile che si muove in un palazzo pieno di trappole mortali, dove ogni salto e ogni duello richiedono precisione e tempismo. Su Apple II, l’animazione realistica, ottenuta con la rotoscopia, si distingue per l’epoca e rafforza l’immersione in questo scenario orientale teso ed esigente.
Curiosità: Jordan Mechner filmò suo fratello per creare le animazioni realistiche del Principe tramite rotoscopia.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Der Prinz verkörpert einen wendigen Helden, der sich durch einen Palast voller tödlicher Fallen bewegt, in dem jeder Sprung und jedes Duell Präzision und Timing verlangen. Auf dem Apple II hebt sich die realistische Animation durch Rotoskopie für ihre Zeit hervor und verstärkt die Spannung dieses anspruchsvollen orientalischen Abenteuers.
Interessante Tatsache: Jordan Mechner filmte seinen eigenen Bruder, um die realistischen Animationen des Prinzen per Rotoskopie zu erstellen.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>O Príncipe encarna um herói ágil que avança por um palácio cheio de armadilhas mortais, onde cada salto e cada duelo exigem precisão e ritmo. No Apple II, a animação realista, criada por rotoscopia, destaca-se para a época e reforça a imersão neste ambiente oriental tenso e exigente.
Curiosidade: Jordan Mechner filmou o próprio irmão para criar as animações realistas do Príncipe por rotoscopia.</text>
</text>
</view>
</theme>
