<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>Aquarius is a personal computer produced by Mattel Electronics. It was equipped with a Zilog Z80 processor, 4 kB RAM (expandable to 52 k) and a BASIC interpreter in ROM. It could be fitted with a special screen and cassette player, and a port extension for two joysticks.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Aquarius est un ordinateur personnel produit par Mattel Electronics. Il était équipé d'un processeur Zilog Z80, de 4 ko de RAM (extensible jusqu'à 52 k) et disposait d'un interpréteur BASIC en ROM. Il pouvait recevoir un écran et un lecteur de cassettes spécifiques, une extension de ports permettant de brancher deux manettes.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Aquarius es un ordenador personal producido por Mattel Electronics. Estaba equipado con un procesador Zilog Z80, 4 kB de RAM (ampliable a 52 k) y un intérprete BASIC en ROM. Podía utilizar una pantalla y un lector de casetes específicos, además de una extensión de puertos para dos joysticks.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Aquarius è un personal computer prodotto da Mattel Electronics. Era dotato di un processore Zilog Z80, 4 kB di RAM (espandibili a 52 k) e un interprete BASIC in ROM. Poteva essere collegato a uno schermo e a un lettore di cassette dedicati, oltre a un'estensione di porte per due joystick.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Der Aquarius ist ein von Mattel Electronics produzierter Personal Computer. Er war mit einem Zilog-Z80-Prozessor, 4 kB RAM (erweiterbar auf 52 k) und einem BASIC-Interpreter im ROM ausgestattet. Er konnte mit einem speziellen Bildschirm und Kassettenrekorder sowie einer Porterweiterung für zwei Joysticks genutzt werden.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>O Aquarius é um computador pessoal produzido pela Mattel Electronics. Era equipado com um processador Zilog Z80, 4 kB de RAM (expansível até 52 k) e um interpretador BASIC em ROM. Podia receber um ecrã e um leitor de cassetes específicos, além de uma extensão de portas para dois joysticks.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Night Stalker (1983)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>Night Stalker places the player in a dark maze filled with hostile robots, spiders and bats, with constant tension from ammunition management and limited movement. The figurine shows an isolated survivor, armed but vulnerable, moving through a closed space where every shot matters.
Fun fact: Night Stalker was originally an Intellivision game, later ported to Aquarius, with technical differences due to the machine's much more limited capabilities.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Night Stalker place le joueur dans un labyrinthe sombre rempli de robots hostiles, d’araignées et de chauves-souris, avec une tension constante liée à la gestion des munitions et aux déplacements limités. La figurine représente le survivant isolé, armé mais vulnérable, évoluant dans un espace fermé où chaque tir compte.
Fun fact : Night Stalker est à l’origine un jeu Intellivision, porté ensuite sur Aquarius, avec des différences techniques dues aux capacités bien plus limitées de la machine.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Night Stalker sitúa al jugador en un laberinto oscuro lleno de robots hostiles, arañas y murciélagos, con una tensión constante por la gestión de munición y los movimientos limitados. La figura muestra a un superviviente aislado, armado pero vulnerable, avanzando en un espacio cerrado donde cada disparo cuenta.
Dato curioso: Night Stalker nació como juego de Intellivision y después llegó a Aquarius, con diferencias técnicas por las capacidades mucho más limitadas de la máquina.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Night Stalker porta il giocatore in un labirinto buio pieno di robot ostili, ragni e pipistrelli, con una tensione costante legata alla gestione delle munizioni e ai movimenti limitati. La statuina mostra un sopravvissuto isolato, armato ma vulnerabile, che avanza in uno spazio chiuso dove ogni colpo conta.
Curiosità: Night Stalker nacque su Intellivision e fu poi convertito per Aquarius, con differenze tecniche dovute alle capacità molto più limitate della macchina.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Night Stalker versetzt den Spieler in ein dunkles Labyrinth voller feindlicher Roboter, Spinnen und Fledermäuse, mit ständiger Spannung durch Munitionsverwaltung und begrenzte Bewegung. Die Figur zeigt einen isolierten Überlebenden, bewaffnet, aber verletzlich, in einem geschlossenen Raum, in dem jeder Schuss zählt.
Interessante Tatsache: Night Stalker erschien zuerst auf Intellivision und wurde später auf Aquarius umgesetzt, mit technischen Unterschieden durch die deutlich begrenzteren Fähigkeiten der Maschine.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Night Stalker coloca o jogador num labirinto escuro cheio de robôs hostis, aranhas e morcegos, com tensão constante ligada à gestão de munições e aos movimentos limitados. A figura representa o sobrevivente isolado, armado mas vulnerável, avançando num espaço fechado onde cada disparo conta.
Curiosidade: Night Stalker surgiu primeiro na Intellivision e foi depois convertido para Aquarius, com diferenças técnicas pelas capacidades muito mais limitadas da máquina.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
