 <!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>The arduboy is an 8-bit portable game console based on the open source2 Arduino platform. It was initially a Kickstarter3 project by Kevin Bates that came to life in early 2015 and has secured over $400,000 with over 7,000 contributors. It embeds a 1.3-inch monochrome OLED display with a resolution of 128 x 64.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>L'arduboy est une console de jeu portable 8 bits basée sur la plateforme open source2 Arduino. C'est initialement un projet Kickstarter3 de Kevin Bates qui a vu le jour début 2015 et qui a obtenu plus de 400 000$ avec plus de 7 000 contributeurs. Il embarque un écran OLED monochrome de 1.3 pouces et de résolution de 128 x 64.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Der Arduboy ist eine tragbare 8-Bit-Spielkonsole, die auf der Open-Source-Plattform2 Arduino basiert. Er war ursprünglich ein Kickstarter3 -Projekt von Kevin Bates, das Anfang 2015 ins Leben gerufen wurde und mit über 7.000 Unterstützern mehr als 400.000 US-Dollar einbrachte. Es hat einen 1,3 Zoll großen monochromen OLED-Bildschirm mit einer Auflösung von 128 x 64.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>El arduboy es una videoconsola portátil de 8 bits basada en la plataforma de código abierto2 Arduino. Originalmente fue un proyecto de Kickstarter3 de Kevin Bates que cobró vida a principios de 2015 y ha recaudado más de 400.000 dólares con más de 7.000 contribuyentes. Incorpora una pantalla OLED monocroma de 1,3 pulgadas con una resolución de 128 x 64.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>L'arduboy è una console di gioco portatile a 8 bit basata sulla piattaforma open source2 Arduino. Originariamente era un progetto Kickstarter3 di Kevin Bates che ha preso vita all'inizio del 2015 e ha raccolto oltre 400.000 dollari con più di 7.000 collaboratori. Incorpora un display OLED monocromatico da 1,3 pollici con una risoluzione di 128 x 64.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>arduboyは、オープンソース2であるArduinoプラットフォームをベースとした8ビット携帯ゲーム機です。もともとはKevin BatesによるKickstarter3プロジェクトで、2015年初頭に実現し、7000人以上の貢献者を得て40万ドル以上の資金を調達しています。解像度128×64の1.3インチモノクロ有機ELディスプレイを埋め込んでいます。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>De arduboy is een 8-bit draagbare spelconsole gebaseerd op het open source2 Arduino platform. Het was aanvankelijk een Kickstarter-project3 van Kevin Bates dat begin 2015 tot leven kwam en meer dan 400.000 dollar opbracht met meer dan 7.000 bijdragers. Het bevat een 1,3-inch monochroom OLED-scherm met een resolutie van 128 x 64.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>Arduboy to 8-bitowa przenośna konsola do gier oparta na platformie open source2 Arduino. Pierwotnie był to projekt Kickstarter3 autorstwa Kevina Batesa, który ożył na początku 2015 roku i zebrał ponad 400 000 dolarów dzięki ponad 7000 wpłat. Osadzono w niej 1,3-calowy monochromatyczny wyświetlacz OLED o rozdzielczości 128 x 64.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>O arduboy é uma consola de jogos portátil de 8 bits baseada na plataforma Arduino open source2. Foi originalmente um projecto Kickstarter3 de Kevin Bates que ganhou vida no início de 2015 e angariou mais de $400.000 com mais de 7.000 contribuintes. Incorpora um ecrã OLED monocromático de 1,3 polegadas com uma resolução de 128 x 64.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>arduboy - это 8-битная портативная игровая консоль на базе платформы Arduino с открытым исходным кодом2. Первоначально это был проект Кевина Бейтса на Kickstarter3, который стартовал в начале 2015 года и собрал более 400 000 долларов при участии более 7 000 вкладчиков. В него встроен 1,3-дюймовый монохромный OLED-дисплей с разрешением 128 x 64.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
