<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>The successor to the 5200, the Atari 7800 was temporarily delayed due to the sale of the company after the collapse of the video game market. It was released as a competitor to the Nintendo Entertainment System and the Sega Master System during the third generation video game console era. However, the console never really competed with its rivals.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Succédant à la 5200, l'Atari 7800 est temporairement retardées en raison de la vente de la société après l'écroulement du marché du jeu vidéo. Elle sort comme concurrente à la Nintendo Entertainment System et à la Sega Master System pendant l'ère des consoles de jeux vidéo de troisième génération. Toutefois, la console ne rivalisera jamais réellement avec ses concurrentes.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Als Nachfolger des 5200 wurde der Atari 7800 vorübergehend verschoben, da das Unternehmen nach dem Zusammenbruch des Videospielmarktes verkauft wurde. Sie wurde als Konkurrenz für das Nintendo Entertainment System und das Sega Master System während der Ära der Videospielkonsolen der dritten Generation herausgebracht. Die Konsole wird jedoch nie wirklich mit ihren Konkurrenten konkurrieren.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>La sucesora de la 5200, la Atari 7800, se retrasó temporalmente debido a la venta de la empresa tras el colapso del mercado de los videojuegos. Salió al mercado como competidora de la Nintendo Entertainment System y la Sega Master System durante la era de la tercera generación de videoconsolas. Sin embargo, la consola nunca llegó a competir realmente con sus rivales.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Successore del 5200, l'Atari 7800 fu temporaneamente ritardato a causa della vendita dell'azienda dopo il crollo del mercato dei videogiochi. Fu rilasciata come concorrente del Nintendo Entertainment System e del Sega Master System durante l'era delle console per videogiochi di terza generazione. Tuttavia, la console non riuscì mai a competere veramente con i suoi rivali.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>5200の後継機であるアタリ7800は、ゲーム市場の崩壊に伴う会社売却のため、一時期発売が延期されていた。第3世代ゲーム機時代、Nintendo Entertainment SystemやSega Master Systemの対抗馬として発売された。しかし、このゲーム機はライバルと競争することはなかった。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>De opvolger van de 5200, de Atari 7800, werd tijdelijk uitgesteld vanwege de verkoop van het bedrijf na de ineenstorting van de videogamemarkt. Hij werd uitgebracht als concurrent van het Nintendo Entertainment System en het Sega Master System tijdens het tijdperk van de derde generatie videogameconsoles. De console concurreerde echter nooit echt met zijn rivalen.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>Następca 5200, Atari 7800 został czasowo opóźniony z powodu sprzedaży firmy po załamaniu się rynku gier wideo. Został wydany jako konkurent dla Nintendo Entertainment System i Sega Master System podczas ery konsoli gier wideo trzeciej generacji. Jednak konsola nigdy nie będzie naprawdę konkurować z rywalami.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>O sucessor do 5200, o Atari 7800 foi temporariamente adiado devido à venda da empresa após o colapso do mercado dos jogos de vídeo. Foi lançado como concorrente do Nintendo Entertainment System e do Sega Master System durante a era da consola de jogos de vídeo de terceira geração. No entanto, a consola nunca competiu realmente com os seus rivais.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>Преемник модели 5200, Atari 7800, был временно отложен из-за продажи компании после краха рынка видеоигр. Она была выпущена в качестве конкурента Nintendo Entertainment System и Sega Master System в эпоху видеоигровых консолей третьего поколения. Однако консоль так и не смогла составить реальную конкуренцию своим соперникам.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Asteroids (1986)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>The Asteroids ship keeps the simple, sharp silhouette of Atari’s space shooter, with inertia-based handling, precise fire and a screen filled with rocks to split apart. On Atari 7800, this version preserves the arcade spirit while adding two-player modes in cooperation or opposition, strengthening its appeal in the living room.
Fun fact: The Atari 7800 version was originally called 3-D Asteroids because its rocks were drawn with more depth.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Le vaisseau d’Asteroids reprend la silhouette simple et nerveuse du shooter spatial d’Atari, avec son pilotage à inertie, ses tirs précis et son écran rempli de rochers à fragmenter. Sur Atari 7800, cette version conserve l’esprit arcade tout en ajoutant des modes deux joueurs en coopération ou en opposition, ce qui renforce son intérêt en salon.
Fun fact : La version Atari 7800 portait à l’origine le nom 3-D Asteroids, car ses rochers étaient dessinés avec plus de relief.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>La nave de Asteroids conserva la silueta simple y nerviosa del shooter espacial de Atari, con manejo por inercia, disparos precisos y una pantalla llena de rocas que fragmentar. En Atari 7800, esta versión mantiene el espíritu arcade y añade modos para dos jugadores en cooperación o enfrentamiento, reforzando su interés en casa.
Dato curioso: La versión de Atari 7800 se llamó originalmente 3-D Asteroids, porque sus rocas estaban dibujadas con más relieve.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>La navicella di Asteroids riprende la sagoma semplice e scattante dello shooter spaziale Atari, con guida a inerzia, colpi precisi e uno schermo pieno di rocce da frammentare. Su Atari 7800, questa versione conserva lo spirito arcade e aggiunge modalità a due giocatori in cooperazione o in sfida, rendendola più interessante in salotto.
Curiosità: La versione Atari 7800 si chiamava in origine 3-D Asteroids, perché le rocce erano disegnate con maggiore rilievo.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Das Raumschiff aus Asteroids bewahrt die schlichte, direkte Silhouette von Ataris Weltraum-Shooter, mit Trägheitssteuerung, präzisen Schüssen und einem Bildschirm voller Felsen, die zerlegt werden müssen. Auf dem Atari 7800 erhält diese Version den Arcade-Geist und ergänzt Zwei-Spieler-Modi im Zusammenspiel oder Gegeneinander.
Interessante Tatsache: Die Atari-7800-Version hieß ursprünglich 3-D Asteroids, weil die Felsen mit mehr räumlicher Tiefe gezeichnet waren.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>A nave de Asteroids mantém a silhueta simples e nervosa do shooter espacial da Atari, com controlo por inércia, disparos precisos e um ecrã cheio de rochas para fragmentar. No Atari 7800, esta versão preserva o espírito arcade e acrescenta modos para dois jogadores em cooperação ou confronto, reforçando o seu interesse em casa.
Curiosidade: A versão Atari 7800 chamava-se originalmente 3-D Asteroids, porque as rochas eram desenhadas com mais relevo.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
