<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>The Jaguar is a cartridge-based home video game console with a limited game library, which has not been very successful despite its innovative technology.  The so-called 64-bit system was advertised as superior to existing 16-bit systems but sales were poor from the start.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>La Jaguar est une console de jeux vidéo de salon à cartouches disposant d'une ludothèque limitée, et qui n'a pas connu un grand succès malgré sa technologie innovante.  Ce prétendu système 64 bits voit sa campagne publicitaire axée sur sa supériorité sur les systèmes 16 bits existants mais les ventes seront mauvaises dès le départ.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Der Jaguar ist eine kassettenbasierte Videospielkonsole für den Heimgebrauch mit einer begrenzten Spielbibliothek, die trotz ihrer innovativen Technologie nicht sehr erfolgreich war.  Das angebliche 64-Bit-System sieht seine Werbekampagne auf seine Überlegenheit gegenüber den vorhandenen 16-Bit-Systemen ausgerichtet, doch die Verkaufszahlen sind von Anfang an schlecht.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>La Jaguar es una videoconsola doméstica basada en cartuchos con una biblioteca de juegos limitada, que no ha tenido mucho éxito a pesar de su innovadora tecnología.  El llamado sistema de 64 bits se anunció como superior a los sistemas de 16 bits existentes, pero las ventas fueron escasas desde el principio.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Il Jaguar è una console per videogiochi domestici basata su cartucce e con una libreria di giochi limitata, che non ha avuto molto successo nonostante la sua tecnologia innovativa.  Il cosiddetto sistema a 64 bit è stato pubblicizzato come superiore ai sistemi a 16 bit esistenti, ma le vendite sono state scarse fin dall'inizio.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>Jaguarは、カートリッジ式の家庭用ゲーム機で、ゲームライブラリーは限られており、革新的な技術を搭載しているにもかかわらず、あまり成功していない。 いわゆる64ビットシステムは、既存の16ビットシステムより優れていると宣伝されたが、当初から売れ行きは芳しくなかった。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>De Jaguar is een videogameconsole voor thuisgebruik met een beperkte spelbibliotheek, die ondanks zijn innovatieve technologie niet erg succesvol was.  Het zogenaamde 64-bit systeem werd aangeprezen als superieur aan de bestaande 16-bit systemen, maar de verkoop was vanaf het begin slecht.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>Jaguar to oparta na kartridżach domowa konsola do gier wideo z ograniczoną biblioteką gier, która mimo innowacyjnej technologii nie odniosła wielkiego sukcesu.  Tak zwany system 64-bitowy był reklamowany jako lepszy od istniejących systemów 16-bitowych, ale sprzedaż od początku była słaba.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>A Jaguar é uma consola de videojogos doméstica baseada em cartuchos com uma biblioteca de jogos limitada, que não teve muito sucesso apesar da sua tecnologia inovadora.  O chamado sistema de 64 bits foi anunciado como superior aos sistemas de 16 bits existentes, mas as vendas foram fracas desde o início.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>Jaguar - это домашняя игровая консоль на базе картриджа с ограниченной библиотекой игр, которая не имела большого успеха, несмотря на инновационную технологию.  Так называемая 64-битная система рекламировалась как превосходящая существующие 16-битные системы, но продажи с самого начала были низкими.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Rayman (1995)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>Rayman is an iconic platform game character, recognizable by his floating limbs and his design without arms or legs. On Atari Jaguar, the game stands out for its particularly faithful and smooth presentation, often considered one of the best console versions of the title, with rich animations and highly detailed backgrounds.
Fun fact: Rayman was the first major game created by Michel Ancel, a French developer born in Monaco who became an important figure in video games.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Rayman est un personnage emblématique du jeu de plateforme, reconnaissable à ses membres flottants et son design sans bras ni jambes. Sur Atari Jaguar, le jeu se distingue par une réalisation particulièrement fidèle et fluide, souvent considérée comme l’une des meilleures versions du titre sur console, avec des animations riches et des décors très détaillés.
Fun fact : Rayman est le premier jeu majeur créé par Michel Ancel, développeur français né à Monaco, devenu une figure importante du jeu vidéo.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Rayman es un personaje emblemático de los juegos de plataformas, reconocible por sus extremidades flotantes y su diseño sin brazos ni piernas. En Atari Jaguar, el juego destaca por una presentación especialmente fiel y fluida, a menudo considerada una de las mejores versiones del título en consola, con animaciones ricas y fondos muy detallados.
Dato curioso: Rayman fue el primer gran juego creado por Michel Ancel, desarrollador francés nacido en Mónaco que se convirtió en una figura importante del videojuego.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Rayman è un personaggio emblematico dei giochi di piattaforme, riconoscibile per i suoi arti fluttuanti e il design senza braccia né gambe. Su Atari Jaguar, il gioco si distingue per una realizzazione particolarmente fedele e fluida, spesso considerata una delle migliori versioni console del titolo, con animazioni ricche e fondali molto dettagliati.
Curiosità: Rayman fu il primo grande gioco creato da Michel Ancel, sviluppatore francese nato a Monaco e divenuto una figura importante dei videogiochi.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Rayman ist eine ikonische Figur des Jump-’n’-Run-Genres, erkennbar an seinen schwebenden Gliedmaßen und seinem Design ohne Arme und Beine. Auf dem Atari Jaguar zeichnet sich das Spiel durch eine besonders originalgetreue und flüssige Umsetzung aus, die oft als eine der besten Konsolenversionen des Titels gilt, mit detailreichen Animationen und Hintergründen.
Interessante Tatsache: Rayman war das erste große Spiel von Michel Ancel, einem in Monaco geborenen französischen Entwickler, der zu einer wichtigen Figur der Videospielwelt wurde.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Rayman é uma personagem emblemática dos jogos de plataformas, reconhecível pelos seus membros flutuantes e pelo design sem braços nem pernas. No Atari Jaguar, o jogo destaca-se por uma apresentação particularmente fiel e fluida, muitas vezes considerada uma das melhores versões do título em consola, com animações ricas e cenários muito detalhados.
Curiosidade: Rayman foi o primeiro grande jogo criado por Michel Ancel, programador francês nascido no Mónaco que se tornou uma figura importante dos videojogos.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
