<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>The Jaguar CD is a peripheral for the Atari Jaguar, allowing the reading of CD-ROMs. There will be very few games developed. Despite this, the Jaguar has attracted a number of amateur developers since its production ended in 1996.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Le Jaguar CD est un périphérique pour la Jaguar d'Atari, permettant la lecture de CD-ROM.. Il y aura très peu de jeux de développés. Malgré tout la Jaguar attire, depuis sa fin de production en 1996, un certain nombre de développeurs amateurs.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Die Jaguar CD ist ein Peripheriegerät für den Atari Jaguar, mit dem CD-ROMs abgespielt werden können. Es werden nur sehr wenige Spiele entwickelt. Trotzdem zieht der Jaguar seit seinem Produktionsende im Jahr 1996 eine Reihe von Hobbyentwicklern an.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>El Jaguar CD es un periférico para el Atari Jaguar que permite la lectura de CD-ROMs. Se desarrollan muy pocos juegos. A pesar de ello, el Jaguar ha atraído a numerosos desarrolladores aficionados desde que finalizó su producción en 1996.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Il Jaguar CD è una periferica per l'Atari Jaguar che consente la lettura di CD-ROM. I giochi sviluppati saranno pochissimi. Nonostante ciò, il Jaguar ha attirato numerosi sviluppatori amatoriali da quando la sua produzione è terminata nel 1996.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>Jaguar CDは、Atari Jaguar用の周辺機器で、CD-ROMの読み込みが可能です。開発されたゲームはほとんどないだろう。にもかかわらず、Jaguarは1996年に生産が終了して以来、多くのアマチュア開発者を惹きつけています。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>De Jaguar CD is een randapparaat voor de Atari Jaguar, waarmee CD-ROM's kunnen worden gelezen. Er worden weinig spellen ontwikkeld. Desondanks heeft de Jaguar een aantal amateur-ontwikkelaars aangetrokken sinds de productie ervan in 1996 eindigde.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>Jaguar CD to urządzenie peryferyjne dla Atari Jaguar, umożliwiające odczyt płyt CD-ROM. Powstanie bardzo mało gier. Pomimo tego, Jaguar przyciągnął wielu amatorskich programistów od czasu zakończenia jego produkcji w 1996 roku.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>O CD Jaguar é um periférico para o Atari Jaguar, permitindo a leitura de CD-ROMs. Haverá muito poucos jogos desenvolvidos. Apesar disso, o Jaguar atraiu vários criadores amadores desde que a sua produção terminou em 1996.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>Jaguar CD - это периферийное устройство для Atari Jaguar, позволяющее читать CD-ROM. Игр будет разработано очень мало. Несмотря на это, Jaguar привлек множество разработчиков-любителей после того, как его производство закончилось в 1996 году.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
