<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>The Acorn Atom is a home computer made by Acorn Computers Ltd from 1980 to 1982, when it was replaced by the BBC Micro. The Micro began life as an upgrade to the Atom, originally known as the Proton.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>L'Acorn Atom est un ordinateur de salon fabriqué par Acorn Computers Ltd de 1980 à 1982, date à laquelle il a été remplacé par le BBC Micro. Le Micro a commencé sa vie comme une mise à niveau de l'Atom, initialement connu sous le nom de Proton.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Der Acorn Atom ist ein Heimcomputer, der von 1980 bis 1982 von Acorn Computers Ltd. hergestellt wurde. Danach wurde er durch den BBC Micro ersetzt. Der Micro war ursprünglich eine Weiterentwicklung des Atom, der ursprünglich als Proton bekannt war.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>El Acorn Atom es un ordenador doméstico fabricado por Acorn Computers Ltd de 1980 a 1982, cuando fue sustituido por el BBC Micro. El Micro comenzó su vida como una actualización del Atom, originalmente conocido como Proton.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>L'Acorn Atom è un home computer prodotto da Acorn Computers Ltd dal 1980 al 1982, quando fu sostituito dal BBC Micro. Il Micro nasce come aggiornamento dell'Atom, originariamente noto come Proton.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>Acorn Atomは、Acorn Computers Ltdが1980年から1982年まで製造したホームコンピュータで、BBC Microに取って代わられた。MicroはAtomのアップグレード版として誕生し、当初はProtonとして知られていました。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>De Acorn Atom is een thuiscomputer die door Acorn Computers Ltd werd gemaakt van 1980 tot 1982, toen hij werd vervangen door de BBC Micro. De Micro begon zijn leven als een upgrade van de Atom, oorspronkelijk bekend als de Proton.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>Acorn Atom to komputer domowy produkowany przez Acorn Computers Ltd w latach 1980-1982, kiedy to został zastąpiony przez BBC Micro. Micro rozpoczął życie jako upgrade do Atoma, pierwotnie znanego jako Proton.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>O Acorn Atom é um computador doméstico fabricado pela Acorn Computers Ltd de 1980 a 1982, quando foi substituído pela BBC Micro. O Micro começou a sua vida como uma actualização para o Atom, originalmente conhecido como Proton.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>Acorn Atom - это домашний компьютер, выпускавшийся компанией Acorn Computers Ltd с 1980 по 1982 год, когда его сменил BBC Micro. Micro начал свою жизнь как модернизация Atom, первоначально известного как Proton.</text>
</text>


<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>  Snapper (1982)  </text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>A lively Pac-Man clone adapted for the Acorn Atom, Snapper keeps the maze instantly readable despite limited hardware, with simple but clear sprites and smooth animation for its time. The controls are immediate, movement feels precise, and the enemies maintain constant pressure, delivering a surprisingly addictive experience on this minimalist machine.
Fun fact: Snapper was withdrawn from sale after a complaint from Namco, which objected to its obvious similarity to Pac-Man.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Clone nerveux de Pac-Man adapté sur l’Acorn Atom, Snapper propose une lecture immédiate du labyrinthe malgré des moyens limités, avec des sprites simples mais lisibles et une animation fluide pour l’époque. La prise en main est instantanée, les déplacements sont précis et les ennemis maintiennent une pression constante, offrant une expérience étonnamment addictive sur cette machine minimaliste.
Fun fact : Snapper a été retiré de la vente après une plainte de Namco, qui a reconnu la similarité évidente avec Pac-Man.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="en">
<text>A lively Pac-Man clone adapted for the Acorn Atom, Snapper keeps the maze instantly readable despite limited hardware, with simple but clear sprites and smooth animation for its time. The controls are immediate, movement feels precise, and the enemies maintain constant pressure, delivering a surprisingly addictive experience on this minimalist machine.
Fun fact: Snapper was withdrawn from sale after a complaint from Namco, which objected to its obvious similarity to Pac-Man.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Clon ágil de Pac-Man adaptado al Acorn Atom, Snapper mantiene el laberinto claro al instante pese a sus límites técnicos, con sprites simples pero legibles y una animación fluida para la época. El control es inmediato, el movimiento preciso y los enemigos sostienen una presión constante, logrando una experiencia sorprendentemente adictiva en esta máquina minimalista.
Fun fact: Snapper fue retirado de la venta tras una reclamación de Namco por su evidente parecido con Pac-Man.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Clone scattante di Pac-Man adattato per Acorn Atom, Snapper mantiene il labirinto subito leggibile nonostante i limiti hardware, con sprite semplici ma chiari e un’animazione fluida per l’epoca. I comandi sono immediati, i movimenti precisi e i nemici tengono alta la pressione, offrendo un’esperienza sorprendentemente coinvolgente su questa macchina minimalista.
Fun fact: Snapper fu ritirato dalla vendita dopo un reclamo di Namco per la sua evidente somiglianza con Pac-Man.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Als flotter Pac-Man-Klon für den Acorn Atom hält Snapper das Labyrinth trotz knapper Hardware sofort lesbar, mit einfachen, aber klaren Sprites und für die Zeit flüssiger Animation. Die Steuerung reagiert direkt, die Bewegungen wirken präzise und die Gegner erzeugen dauerhaft Druck, was auf dieser minimalistischen Maschine erstaunlich fesselnd bleibt.
Fun fact: Snapper wurde nach einer Beschwerde von Namco wegen der deutlichen Ähnlichkeit zu Pac-Man aus dem Verkauf genommen.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Clone ágil de Pac-Man adaptado ao Acorn Atom, Snapper mantém o labirinto imediatamente legível apesar das limitações técnicas, com sprites simples mas claros e animação fluida para a época. O controlo é direto, os movimentos são precisos e os inimigos mantêm pressão constante, criando uma experiência surpreendentemente viciante nesta máquina minimalista.
Fun fact: Snapper foi retirado de venda após uma reclamação da Namco pela sua semelhança evidente com Pac-Man.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
