<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>The Atomiswave is a cartridge-based video game system for JAMMA compatible arcade terminals. It is a low-cost, easy-to-use and easily scalable game system, with the possibility to easily connect a gun, a steering wheel or a trackball.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>L'Atomiswave est un système de jeux vidéo à cartouche pour borne d'arcade compatible JAMMA. Il se veut être un système de jeu à bas coût, très facile d'utilisation et aisément modulable, avec la possibilité de brancher facilement un pistolet, un volant ou un trackball.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Atomiswave ist ein JAMMA-kompatibles Videospielsystem mit Kassetten für Arcade-Automaten. Es soll ein kostengünstiges, sehr benutzerfreundliches und leicht erweiterbares Spielsystem sein, mit der Möglichkeit, eine Pistole, ein Lenkrad oder einen Trackball problemlos anzuschließen.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>El Atomiswave es un sistema de juego basado en cartuchos para terminales arcade compatibles con JAMMA. Pretende ser un sistema de juego de bajo coste, muy fácil de usar y fácilmente actualizable, con la posibilidad de conectar fácilmente una pistola, un volante o un trackball.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Atomiswave è un sistema di gioco basato su cartucce per terminali arcade compatibili con JAMMA. Si tratta di un sistema di gioco a basso costo, molto facile da usare e facilmente aggiornabile, con la possibilità di collegare facilmente una pistola, un volante o una trackball.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>Atomiswaveは、JAMMA互換のアーケード端末用のカートリッジ式ゲームシステムです。銃やステアリングホイール、トラックボールなどを簡単に接続することができ、低コストで非常に使いやすく、簡単にアップグレードできるゲーミングシステムを目指したものです。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>De Atomiswave is een cartridge-gebaseerd spelsysteem voor JAMMA-compatibele arcade-terminals. Het is bedoeld als een goedkoop, zeer eenvoudig te gebruiken en gemakkelijk te upgraden spelsysteem, met de mogelijkheid om gemakkelijk een pistool, stuurwiel of trackball aan te sluiten.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>Atomiswave jest systemem gier opartym na kartridżach dla terminali arcade kompatybilnych z JAMMA. Ma to być tani, bardzo prosty w obsłudze i łatwy do rozbudowy system gier, z możliwością łatwego podłączenia pistoletu, kierownicy lub trackballa.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>O Atomiswave é um sistema de jogo baseado em cartuchos para terminais de arcada compatíveis com JAMMA. Destina-se a ser um sistema de jogo de baixo custo, muito fácil de usar e facilmente actualizável, com a capacidade de ligar facilmente uma arma, volante ou trackball.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>Atomiswave - это игровая система на базе картриджа для аркадных терминалов, совместимых с JAMMA. Это недорогая, очень простая в использовании и легко модернизируемая игровая система, к которой можно легко подключить пистолет, руль или трекбол.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
