<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>The Atomiswave is a cartridge-based video game system for JAMMA compatible arcade terminals. It is a low-cost, easy-to-use and easily scalable game system, with the possibility to easily connect a gun, a steering wheel or a trackball.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>L'Atomiswave est un système de jeux vidéo à cartouche pour borne d'arcade compatible JAMMA. Il se veut être un système de jeu à bas coût, très facile d'utilisation et aisément modulable, avec la possibilité de brancher facilement un pistolet, un volant ou un trackball.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Atomiswave ist ein JAMMA-kompatibles Videospielsystem mit Kassetten für Arcade-Automaten. Es soll ein kostengünstiges, sehr benutzerfreundliches und leicht erweiterbares Spielsystem sein, mit der Möglichkeit, eine Pistole, ein Lenkrad oder einen Trackball problemlos anzuschließen.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>El Atomiswave es un sistema de juego basado en cartuchos para terminales arcade compatibles con JAMMA. Pretende ser un sistema de juego de bajo coste, muy fácil de usar y fácilmente actualizable, con la posibilidad de conectar fácilmente una pistola, un volante o un trackball.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Atomiswave è un sistema di gioco basato su cartucce per terminali arcade compatibili con JAMMA. Si tratta di un sistema di gioco a basso costo, molto facile da usare e facilmente aggiornabile, con la possibilità di collegare facilmente una pistola, un volante o una trackball.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>Atomiswaveは、JAMMA互換のアーケード端末用のカートリッジ式ゲームシステムです。銃やステアリングホイール、トラックボールなどを簡単に接続することができ、低コストで非常に使いやすく、簡単にアップグレードできるゲーミングシステムを目指したものです。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>De Atomiswave is een cartridge-gebaseerd spelsysteem voor JAMMA-compatibele arcade-terminals. Het is bedoeld als een goedkoop, zeer eenvoudig te gebruiken en gemakkelijk te upgraden spelsysteem, met de mogelijkheid om gemakkelijk een pistool, stuurwiel of trackball aan te sluiten.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>Atomiswave jest systemem gier opartym na kartridżach dla terminali arcade kompatybilnych z JAMMA. Ma to być tani, bardzo prosty w obsłudze i łatwy do rozbudowy system gier, z możliwością łatwego podłączenia pistoletu, kierownicy lub trackballa.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>O Atomiswave é um sistema de jogo baseado em cartuchos para terminais de arcada compatíveis com JAMMA. Destina-se a ser um sistema de jogo de baixo custo, muito fácil de usar e facilmente actualizável, com a capacidade de ligar facilmente uma arma, volante ou trackball.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>Atomiswave - это игровая система на базе картриджа для аркадных терминалов, совместимых с JAMMA. Это недорогая, очень простая в использовании и легко модернизируемая игровая система, к которой можно легко подключить пистолет, руль или трекбол.</text>
</text>


<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Hokuto no Ken (2005)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>Kenshiro is the heir to Hokuto Shinken, a deadly martial art able to strike an opponent’s vital points. On Atomiswave, Hokuto no Ken becomes a fast 2D fighting game by Arc System Works, with spectacular duels, explosive attacks and a presentation faithful to the brutal intensity of the manga.
Fun fact: The game is famous for huge combos and its seven-star system, which can lead to instant death when all of a fighter’s stars disappear.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Kenshiro est l’héritier du Hokuto Shinken, un art martial mortel capable de frapper les points vitaux de ses adversaires. Sur Atomiswave, Hokuto no Ken devient un jeu de combat 2D nerveux signé Arc System Works, avec des duels spectaculaires, des attaques explosives et une mise en scène fidèle à l’intensité brutale du manga.
Fun fact : Le jeu est célèbre pour ses combos démesurés et son système des sept étoiles, qui peut mener à une mort instantanée si toutes les étoiles d’un combattant disparaissent.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Kenshiro es el heredero del Hokuto Shinken, un arte marcial mortal capaz de golpear los puntos vitales de sus rivales. En Atomiswave, Hokuto no Ken se convierte en un juego de lucha 2D rápido de Arc System Works, con duelos espectaculares, ataques explosivos y una puesta en escena fiel a la intensidad brutal del manga.
Dato curioso: El juego es famoso por sus combos enormes y su sistema de siete estrellas, que puede causar muerte instantánea si desaparecen todas las estrellas.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Kenshiro è l’erede dell’Hokuto Shinken, un’arte marziale letale capace di colpire i punti vitali degli avversari. Su Atomiswave, Hokuto no Ken diventa un picchiaduro 2D rapido firmato Arc System Works, con duelli spettacolari, attacchi esplosivi e una messa in scena fedele all’intensità brutale del manga.
Curiosità: Il gioco è famoso per le sue combo enormi e per il sistema delle sette stelle, che può portare alla morte istantanea quando spariscono tutte.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Kenshiro ist der Erbe des Hokuto Shinken, einer tödlichen Kampfkunst, die die Vitalpunkte des Gegners trifft. Auf Atomiswave wird Hokuto no Ken zu einem schnellen 2D-Kampfspiel von Arc System Works, mit spektakulären Duellen, explosiven Angriffen und einer Inszenierung nahe an der brutalen Intensität des Mangas.
Interessante Tatsache: Das Spiel ist für riesige Combos und sein Sieben-Sterne-System bekannt, das zum sofortigen Tod führen kann, wenn alle Sterne verschwinden.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Kenshiro é o herdeiro do Hokuto Shinken, uma arte marcial mortal capaz de atingir os pontos vitais dos adversários. Na Atomiswave, Hokuto no Ken torna-se um jogo de luta 2D rápido da Arc System Works, com duelos espetaculares, ataques explosivos e encenação fiel à intensidade brutal do manga.
Curiosidade: O jogo é famoso pelos combos enormes e pelo sistema das sete estrelas, que pode causar morte instantânea quando todas desaparecem.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
