<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>Puzzle games are a broad genre of video games that focus on solving puzzles. The types of puzzles can test problem-solving skills such as logic, pattern recognition, sequence solving or word completion.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Les jeux vidéo de réflexion constituent un vaste genre de jeux vidéo qui mettent l'accent sur la résolution d'énigmes. Les types d'énigmes peuvent mettre à l'épreuve les capacités de résolution de problèmes, notamment la logique, la reconnaissance des formes, la résolution de séquences ou encore la complétion de mots.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Rätsel-Videospiele sind ein breites Genre von Videospielen, bei denen das Lösen von Rätseln im Vordergrund steht. Die Arten von Rätseln können die Problemlösungsfähigkeiten auf die Probe stellen, darunter Logik, Mustererkennung, das Lösen von Sequenzen oder das Vervollständigen von Wörtern.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Los juegos de puzles son un amplio género de videojuegos que se centran en la resolución de rompecabezas. Los tipos de puzles pueden poner a prueba habilidades de resolución de problemas como la lógica, el reconocimiento de patrones, la resolución de secuencias o la compleción de palabras.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>I giochi di enigmistica sono un ampio genere di videogiochi che si concentrano sulla risoluzione di enigmi. I tipi di puzzle possono mettere alla prova abilità di risoluzione di problemi come la logica, il riconoscimento di schemi, la risoluzione di sequenze o il completamento di parole.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>パズルゲームは、パズルを解くことに焦点を当てた幅広いジャンルのビデオゲームです。パズルの種類は、ロジック、パターン認識、シーケンス解決、単語補完などの問題解決能力をテストすることができます。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>Puzzelspellen zijn een breed genre videospellen waarin het oplossen van puzzels centraal staat. De soorten puzzels kunnen probleemoplossende vaardigheden testen, zoals logica, patroonherkenning, het oplossen van reeksen of het aanvullen van woorden.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>Gry logiczne to szeroki gatunek gier wideo, które skupiają się na rozwiązywaniu zagadek. Rodzaje zagadek mogą testować umiejętności rozwiązywania problemów, takie jak logika, rozpoznawanie wzorów, rozwiązywanie sekwencji lub uzupełnianie słów.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Os jogos de puzzle são um amplo género de jogos de vídeo que se concentram na resolução de puzzles. Os tipos de puzzles podem testar capacidades de resolução de problemas tais como lógica, reconhecimento de padrões, resolução de sequências ou preenchimento de palavras.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>Логические игры - это широкий жанр видеоигр, в которых основное внимание уделяется решению головоломок. Типы головоломок могут проверять навыки решения проблем, такие как логика, распознавание образов, решение последовательности или завершение слов.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Captain Toad: Treasure Tracker (Wii U, 2014)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>Captain Toad explores small diorama-like stages filled with hidden paths, mechanisms and treasures to collect without being able to jump. Each level relies on observation, camera rotation and careful reading of the scenery, with a gentle, precise puzzle approach very different from classic platform games.
Fun fact: The game grew out of the “Adventures of Captain Toad” stages from Super Mario 3D World before becoming a full title.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Captain Toad explore de petits dioramas remplis de passages cachés, de mécanismes et de trésors à récupérer sans pouvoir sauter. Chaque niveau repose sur l’observation, la rotation de la caméra et la lecture attentive du décor, avec une approche puzzle douce, précise et très différente des jeux de plateforme classiques.
Fun fact : Le jeu est né des niveaux “Adventures of Captain Toad” présents dans Super Mario 3D World, avant de devenir un titre complet.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Captain Toad explora pequeños dioramas llenos de pasajes ocultos, mecanismos y tesoros que recoger sin poder saltar. Cada nivel se basa en la observación, la rotación de la cámara y la lectura cuidadosa del escenario, con un enfoque de puzle tranquilo y preciso muy distinto de los juegos de plataformas clásicos.
Dato curioso: El juego nació a partir de los niveles “Adventures of Captain Toad” de Super Mario 3D World antes de convertirse en un título completo.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Captain Toad esplora piccoli diorami pieni di passaggi nascosti, meccanismi e tesori da raccogliere senza poter saltare. Ogni livello si basa sull’osservazione, sulla rotazione della telecamera e sulla lettura attenta dello scenario, con un approccio puzzle calmo e preciso molto diverso dai platform classici.
Curiosità: Il gioco è nato dai livelli “Adventures of Captain Toad” presenti in Super Mario 3D World prima di diventare un titolo completo.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Captain Toad erkundet kleine Diorama-Level voller versteckter Wege, Mechanismen und Schätze, die er einsammeln muss, ohne springen zu können. Jede Stage setzt auf Beobachtung, Kameradrehung und genaues Lesen der Umgebung, mit einem ruhigen und präzisen Puzzle-Ansatz.
Interessante Tatsache: Das Spiel entstand aus den “Adventures of Captain Toad”-Leveln aus Super Mario 3D World, bevor daraus ein eigenes Spiel wurde.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Captain Toad explora pequenos dioramas cheios de passagens escondidas, mecanismos e tesouros para recolher sem poder saltar. Cada nível depende da observação, da rotação da câmara e da leitura cuidadosa do cenário, com uma abordagem de puzzle calma e precisa, bem diferente dos jogos de plataforma clássicos.
Curiosidade: O jogo nasceu das fases “Adventures of Captain Toad” de Super Mario 3D World antes de se tornar um título completo.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>

