<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>Automatic game list. Here you will find all the games compatible with four or more players on any system. How about a little Bomberman?</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Vous trouverez ici tous les jeux compatibles pour quatre joueurs ou plus tout système confondus. Et si on se lançait un petit Bomberman des familles ?</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Automatische Liste von Spielen. Hier finden Sie alle kompatiblen Spiele für vier oder mehr Spieler auf allen Systemen. Wie wäre es mit einem kleinen Bomberman?</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Lista automática de juegos. Aquí encontrarás todos los juegos compatibles para cuatro o más jugadores en cualquier sistema. ¿Qué tal un poco de Bomberman?</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Elenco automatico dei giochi. Qui troverete tutti i giochi compatibili con quattro o più giocatori su qualsiasi sistema. Che ne dite di un po' di Bomberman?</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>自動ゲームリストです。ここでは、どのシステムでも4人以上のプレイヤーに対応したゲームをすべて見つけることができます。ボンバーマンなんていかがですか？</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>Automatische spelletjeslijst. Hier vind je alle spellen die geschikt zijn voor vier of meer spelers op elk systeem. Wat dacht je van een beetje Bomberman?</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>Automatyczna lista gier. Tutaj znajdziesz wszystkie gry, które są kompatybilne dla czterech lub więcej graczy na dowolnym systemie. Co powiecie na małego Bombermana?</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Lista de jogos automática. Aqui encontrará todos os jogos que são compatíveis para quatro ou mais jogadores em qualquer sistema. Que tal um pequeno bombardeiro?</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>Автоматический список игр. Здесь вы найдете все игры, совместимые для четырех и более игроков на любой системе. Как насчет маленького Бомбермена?</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>

