<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>A role-playing video game (RPG) is a video game genre where the player controls the actions of a character (or several party of members) immersed in some well-defined world, usually involving some form of character development by way of recording statistics.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Un jeu vidéo de rôle (RPG) est un genre de jeu vidéo dans lequel le joueur contrôle les actions d'un personnage (ou de plusieurs membres d'un groupe) immergé dans un monde bien défini, impliquant généralement une forme de développement du personnage par le biais de l'enregistrement de statistiques.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Ein Rollenspiel-Videospiel (RPG) ist ein Videospielgenre, bei dem der Spieler die Handlungen einer Figur (oder mehrerer Gruppenmitglieder) steuert, die in eine genau definierte Welt eintaucht, wobei in der Regel eine Form der Charakterentwicklung durch die Aufzeichnung von Statistiken vorgesehen ist.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Un videojuego de rol (RPG) es un género de videojuego en el que el jugador controla las acciones de un personaje (o varios miembros de un grupo) inmerso en un mundo bien definido, que suele implicar algún tipo de desarrollo del personaje mediante el registro de estadísticas.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Un videogioco di ruolo (RPG) è un genere di videogiochi in cui il giocatore controlla le azioni di un personaggio (o di un gruppo di membri) immerso in un mondo ben definito, che di solito prevede una forma di sviluppo del personaggio attraverso la registrazione di statistiche.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>ロールプレイング・ビデオゲーム（RPG）は、ビデオゲームのジャンルの一つで、プレイヤーは、ある定義された世界に没入するキャラクター（または複数のパーティメンバー）の行動をコントロールし、通常、統計を記録することによって何らかの形でキャラクターの成長を伴います。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>Een role-playing video game (RPG) is een videogame genre waarbij de speler de acties van een personage (of meerdere partijen) bestuurt, ondergedompeld in een welbepaalde wereld, meestal met een vorm van karakterontwikkeling door middel van het vastleggen van statistieken.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>Role-playing video game (RPG) to gatunek gier wideo, w których gracz kontroluje działania postaci (lub kilku partii członków) zanurzonych w jakimś dobrze zdefiniowanym świecie, zwykle obejmującym jakąś formę rozwoju postaci poprzez zapisywanie statystyk.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Um jogo de role-playing (RPG) é um género de videojogo onde o jogador controla as acções de uma personagem (ou de vários membros) imersa em algum mundo bem definido, geralmente envolvendo alguma forma de desenvolvimento de personagens através de estatísticas de gravação.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>Ролевая видеоигра (RPG) - это жанр видеоигры, в котором игрок управляет действиями персонажа (или нескольких членов партии), погруженного в некий четко определенный мир, обычно включающий некоторую форму развития персонажа путем записи статистики.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
