<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>Vertical-view arcade games are games where the action takes place from top to bottom, offering an ideal perspective for shoot'em ups, racing games and some run and gun games. This format gives a better view of the terrain and promotes fast, fluid gameplay. Very popular in the 80s and 90s, these games are known for their progressive difficulty and high replayability.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Les jeux d'arcade en vue verticale sont des jeux où l'action se déroule de haut en bas, offrant une perspective idéale pour les shoot'em up, les jeux de course et certains run and gun. Ce format permet une meilleure visibilité du terrain et favorise un gameplay rapide et fluide. Très populaires dans les années 80 et 90, ces jeux sont connus pour leur difficulté progressive et leur rejouabilité élevée.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Los juegos arcade de vista vertical son títulos donde la acción se desarrolla en una pantalla más alta que ancha, ideal para shoot'em ups, carreras y otros géneros de ritmo rápido. Este formato ofrece una lectura clara del terreno y favorece partidas directas, fluidas y muy rejugables.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>I giochi arcade a visuale verticale sono titoli in cui l'azione si sviluppa su uno schermo più alto che largo, ideale per shoot'em up, corse e altri generi dal ritmo rapido. Questo formato offre una lettura chiara del terreno e favorisce partite dirette, fluide e molto rigiocabili.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Arcade-Spiele mit vertikaler Ansicht sind Titel, bei denen die Action auf einem höheren als breiten Bildschirm abläuft, ideal für Shoot'em-ups, Rennspiele und andere schnelle Genres. Dieses Format sorgt für klare Übersicht und direkte, flüssige, sehr wiederspielbare Partien.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Os jogos arcade de vista vertical são títulos em que a ação decorre num ecrã mais alto do que largo, ideal para shoot'em ups, corridas e outros géneros de ritmo rápido. Este formato oferece uma leitura clara do terreno e favorece partidas diretas, fluidas e muito rejogáveis.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;1942 (1984)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>Vertical arcade games bring together titles designed for a taller display, where the action often moves from the bottom to the top of the screen. They include shoot'em ups as well as other genres suited to this format, with direct readability, fast pacing and immediate play built for arcade sessions.
Fun fact: Many arcade cabinets used a screen rotated 90 degrees, known as tate mode, to provide a native vertical display for these games.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Les jeux verticaux regroupent des titres conçus pour un affichage en hauteur, où l'action se déroule souvent du bas vers le haut de l'écran. On y trouve aussi bien des shoot'em up que d'autres genres adaptés à ce format, avec une lisibilité directe, un rythme rapide et un jeu immédiat pensé pour l'arcade.
Fun fact : De nombreuses bornes d'arcade utilisaient un écran pivoté à 90 degrés, appelé mode tate, pour offrir un affichage vertical natif adapté à ces jeux.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Los juegos verticales reúnen títulos diseñados para una pantalla en altura, donde la acción suele avanzar desde la parte inferior hacia la superior. Incluyen shoot'em ups y otros géneros adaptados a este formato, con lectura directa, ritmo rápido y partidas inmediatas pensadas para arcade.
Dato curioso: Muchas recreativas usaban una pantalla girada 90 grados, llamada modo tate, para ofrecer una visualización vertical nativa adaptada a estos juegos.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>I giochi verticali riuniscono titoli pensati per uno schermo in altezza, dove l'azione spesso procede dal basso verso l'alto. Comprendono shoot'em up e altri generi adatti a questo formato, con lettura immediata, ritmo rapido e partite dirette pensate per l'arcade.
Curiosità: Molti cabinati arcade usavano uno schermo ruotato di 90 gradi, chiamato modalità tate, per offrire una visualizzazione verticale nativa.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Vertikale Arcade-Spiele umfassen Titel, die für eine hohe Bildfläche gedacht sind, bei denen die Action oft von unten nach oben verläuft. Dazu zählen Shoot'em-ups und andere passende Genres, mit klarer Lesbarkeit, schnellem Tempo und direktem Spielgefühl für die Arcade.
Interessante Tatsache: Viele Automaten nutzten einen um 90 Grad gedrehten Bildschirm, den tate-Modus, um diesen Spielen eine native vertikale Darstellung zu geben.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Os jogos verticais reúnem títulos criados para um ecrã em altura, onde a ação avança muitas vezes de baixo para cima. Incluem shoot'em ups e outros géneros adaptados a este formato, com leitura direta, ritmo rápido e partidas imediatas pensadas para arcade.
Curiosidade: Muitas máquinas arcade usavam um ecrã rodado 90 graus, chamado modo tate, para oferecer uma visualização vertical nativa adaptada a estes jogos.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
