<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>Automatic game list. Got an itchy trigger finger? Then you've come to the right place to satisfy your cravings!</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Liste de jeux automatique. Vous avez la gâchette qui démange ? Alors vous êtes au bon endroit pour satisfaire vos envies !</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Automatische Liste von Spielen. Juckt es Sie in den Fingern, den Abzug zu betätigen? Dann sind Sie hier genau richtig, um Ihre Lust zu befriedigen!</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Lista automática de juegos. ¿Le pica el dedo en el gatillo? Entonces ha venido al lugar adecuado para satisfacer sus ansias.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Elenco automatico dei giochi. Vi prude il dito del grilletto? Allora siete nel posto giusto per soddisfare le vostre voglie!</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>自動ゲームリスト。トリガーフィンガーが痒い？それなら、あなたの欲求を満たすために正しい場所に来たんだ!</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>Automatische spelletjeslijst. Heb je een jeukende vinger? Dan ben je op de juiste plaats om je verlangens te bevredigen!</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>Automatyczna lista gier. Masz swędzący palec u nogi? W takim razie trafiłeś we właściwe miejsce, aby zaspokoić swoje pragnienia!</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Lista de jogos automática. Tem comichão no dedo do gatilho? Então veio ao lugar certo para satisfazer os seus desejos!</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>Автоматический список игр. У вас чешется палец? Тогда вы пришли в правильное место, чтобы удовлетворить свои желания!</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>

