<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>Automatic Game Collection. 
You felt like a little fight ? 
You are at the right place :)</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Collection automatique.
Vous aviez envie d'un petit coup de castagne ? Vous êtes au bon endroit :)</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Automatic Game Collection.
Sie hatten Lust auf einen kleinen Kampf? 
Dann sind Sie hier richtig :)</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Automatic Game Collection.
¿Tienes ganas de pelea? 
Has venido al lugar adecuado :)</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Automatic Game Collection.
Avete voglia di litigare un po'? 
Siete nel posto giusto :)</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>オートゲーマーリスト。ちょっと戦いたい気分？あなたは正しい場所に来ている :)</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>Automatic Game Collection.
Heb je zin in een robbertje vechten? 
Dan ben je op de juiste plaats :)</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>Automatic Game Collection.
Miałeś ochotę na małą walkę? 
Trafiłeś w odpowiednie miejsce :)</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Lista automática de jogos. 
Apeteceu-lhe um pouco de luta? 
Veio ao lugar certo :)</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>Автоматический геймлист. 
Вам захотелось немного подраться? 
Вы пришли по адресу :)</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Street Fighter II (Arcade, 1991)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>A brutal boxer inspired by American heavyweights, Balrog relies on raw power and constant pressure to crush his opponents in the arena. With fast rush punches, devastating straights and an aggressive style, every mistake can cost a round in seconds during especially tense fights.
Fun fact: In the original Japanese version, Balrog was called Mike Bison, a name Capcom changed internationally to avoid a possible lawsuit with Mike Tyson.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Boxeur brutal inspiré des poids lourds américains, Balrog mise sur la puissance et la pression constante pour écraser ses adversaires dans l’arène. Avec ses charges rapides, ses directs dévastateurs et son style agressif, chaque erreur peut coûter un round en quelques secondes dans des combats particulièrement nerveux.
Fun fact : Dans la version japonaise originale, Balrog s’appelait Mike Bison, un nom modifié à l’international par Capcom pour éviter un possible procès avec Mike Tyson.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Boxeador brutal inspirado en los pesos pesados estadounidenses, Balrog apuesta por la fuerza y la presión constante para aplastar a sus rivales en la arena. Con cargas rápidas, directos demoledores y un estilo agresivo, cualquier error puede costar un asalto en segundos.
Dato curioso: En la versión japonesa original, Balrog se llamaba Mike Bison, nombre que Capcom cambió internacionalmente para evitar un posible juicio con Mike Tyson.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Pugile brutale ispirato ai pesi massimi americani, Balrog punta su potenza e pressione costante per travolgere gli avversari nell’arena. Con cariche rapide, diretti devastanti e uno stile aggressivo, ogni errore può costare un round in pochi secondi.
Curiosità: Nella versione giapponese originale, Balrog si chiamava Mike Bison, nome cambiato da Capcom a livello internazionale per evitare una possibile causa con Mike Tyson.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Als brutaler Boxer nach dem Vorbild amerikanischer Schwergewichte setzt Balrog auf Kraft und dauerhaften Druck, um seine Gegner im Ring zu überrollen. Mit schnellen Anstürmen, harten Geraden und aggressivem Stil kann jeder Fehler in Sekunden eine Runde kosten.
Interessante Tatsache: In der japanischen Originalversion hieß Balrog Mike Bison, ein Name, den Capcom international änderte, um einen möglichen Rechtsstreit mit Mike Tyson zu vermeiden.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Boxeur brutal inspirado nos pesos-pesados americanos, Balrog aposta na força e na pressão constante para esmagar os adversários na arena. Com investidas rápidas, diretos devastadores e um estilo agressivo, qualquer erro pode custar um round em poucos segundos.
Curiosidade: Na versão japonesa original, Balrog chamava-se Mike Bison, nome que a Capcom alterou internacionalmente para evitar um possível processo com Mike Tyson.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>

