<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>Automatic game list. The beat 'em up or beat 'em all is a kind of video game featuring hand-to-hand combat between the protagonist and an unbelievable and endless number of opponents coming to fight.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Liste de jeux automatique. Le beat 'em up ou beat 'em all est un genre de jeu vidéo mettant en scène des combats au corps à corps entre le protagoniste et un nombre invraisemblable et interminable d'adversaires venus pour en découdre.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Automatische Liste von Spielen. Ein Beat 'em up oder Beat 'em all ist ein Videospielgenre, in dem der Protagonist im Nahkampf mit einer unglaublichen und endlosen Anzahl von Gegnern kämpft.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Lista automática de juegos. El beat 'em up o beat 'em all es un género de videojuegos que presenta combates cuerpo a cuerpo entre el protagonista y un número increíble e interminable de adversarios que han venido a luchar.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Elenco dei giochi automatici. Il beat 'em up o beat 'em all è un genere di videogiochi che prevede combattimenti corpo a corpo tra il protagonista e un numero incredibile e infinito di avversari venuti a combattere.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>自動ゲームリスト。beat 'em upまたはbeat 'em allは、主人公と、戦いに来た信じられないほど無限の数の相手との手による戦闘を特徴とするビデオゲームのジャンルです。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>Automatische spelletjeslijst. De beat 'em up of beat 'em all is een genre videospel met hand-aan-hand gevechten tussen de hoofdpersoon en een ongelooflijk en eindeloos aantal tegenstanders die zijn gekomen om te vechten.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>Automatyczna lista gier. Beat 'em up lub beat 'em all to gatunek gry wideo zawierający walkę wręcz pomiędzy protagonistą a niewiarygodną i nieskończoną liczbą przeciwników, którzy przyszli walczyć.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Lista de jogos automática. O jogo "beat 'up" ou "beat 'all" é um género de jogo de vídeo com combate corpo a corpo entre o protagonista e um número inacreditável e interminável de adversários que vieram para lutar.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>Список автоматических игр. Beat 'em up или beat 'em all - это жанр видеоигр, в котором представлены рукопашные бои между главным героем и невероятным и бесконечным количеством противников, пришедших сразиться.</text>
</text>


<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Captain Commando (Arcade, 1991)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>Captain Commando is a futuristic hero created by Capcom who fights gangs of mutants and criminals alongside an unlikely team made up of a ninja, a baby piloting a mech and an alien warrior. The game mixes explosive action, street fights and absurd weapons in a fast-paced arcade style packed with enemies and visual effects.
Fun fact: Captain Commando was originally created as Capcom’s official mascot before becoming the hero of his own arcade game.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Héros futuriste imaginé par Capcom, Captain Commando combat des gangs de mutants et de criminels aux côtés d’une équipe complètement improbable composée d’un ninja, d’un bébé pilote de mécha et d’un extraterrestre. Le jeu enchaîne combats de rue, armes loufoques et action explosive dans un style arcade nerveux et particulièrement généreux en ennemis et effets visuels.
Fun fact : Captain Commando avait été créé au départ comme mascotte officielle de Capcom avant de devenir le héros de son propre jeu arcade.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Héroe futurista imaginado por Capcom, Captain Commando combate bandas de mutantes y criminales junto a un equipo totalmente improbable formado por un ninja, un bebé piloto de mecha y un extraterrestre. El juego mezcla peleas callejeras, armas absurdas y acción explosiva en un estilo arcade rápido y lleno de efectos visuales.
Dato curioso: Captain Commando fue creado originalmente como la mascota oficial de Capcom antes de convertirse en el héroe de su propio arcade.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Eroe futuristico creato da Capcom, Captain Commando affronta bande di mutanti e criminali insieme a una squadra improbabile composta da un ninja, un neonato pilota di mecha e un alieno. Il gioco unisce combattimenti di strada, armi folli e azione esplosiva in uno stile arcade frenetico ricco di effetti visivi.
Curiosità: Captain Commando era stato creato inizialmente come mascotte ufficiale di Capcom prima di diventare protagonista del suo gioco arcade.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Der futuristische Held Captain Commando kämpft zusammen mit einem Ninja, einem Baby im Kampf-Mecha und einem Außerirdischen gegen Mutanten und Verbrecherbanden. Das Spiel verbindet Straßenkämpfe, verrückte Waffen und explosive Action in einem schnellen Arcade-Stil voller Gegner und visueller Effekte.
Interessante Tatsache: Captain Commando wurde ursprünglich als offizielles Maskottchen von Capcom erschaffen, bevor er seinen eigenen Arcade-Titel erhielt.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Herói futurista criado pela Capcom, Captain Commando enfrenta gangues de mutantes e criminosos ao lado de uma equipa improvável composta por um ninja, um bebé piloto de mecha e um extraterrestre. O jogo mistura combates de rua, armas absurdas e ação explosiva num estilo arcade rápido e cheio de efeitos visuais.
Curiosidade: Captain Commando foi criado inicialmente como mascote oficial da Capcom antes de se tornar o herói do seu próprio jogo arcade.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>

