<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>The games range from realistic racing simulations to more fantasy arcade-style racing games. They can be based on any type of competition, from real-world racing championships to complete fantasy settings and championships.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Les jeux se répartissent sur un spectre allant des simulations de course réalistes aux jeux de course plus fantastiques de type arcade. Ils peuvent être basés sur n'importe quel type de compétition, qu'il s'agisse de championnats de course du monde réel ou de décors et championnats complètements fantastiques.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Die Spiele reichen von realistischen Rennsimulationen bis hin zu eher fantastischen Rennspielen im Arcade-Stil. Sie können auf jeder Art von Wettbewerb basieren, von Rennmeisterschaften in der realen Welt bis hin zu komplett fantastischen Hintergründen und Meisterschaften.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Los juegos van desde simulaciones de carreras realistas hasta juegos de carreras más fantásticos de estilo arcade. Pueden basarse en cualquier tipo de competición, desde campeonatos de carreras del mundo real hasta escenarios y campeonatos totalmente fantásticos.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>I giochi spaziano da simulazioni di corse realistiche a giochi di corse in stile arcade più fantasy. Possono essere basati su qualsiasi tipo di competizione, da campionati di corse reali ad ambientazioni e campionati di fantasia.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>ゲームは、リアルなレースシミュレーションから、よりファンタジーなアーケードスタイルのレースゲームまで、さまざまです。また、現実のレース選手権から完全なファンタジー設定や選手権まで、あらゆるタイプの競技をベースとすることができます。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>De spellen variëren van realistische racesimulaties tot meer fantasievolle arcade-achtige racespellen. Ze kunnen gebaseerd zijn op elk type competitie, van echte racekampioenschappen tot volledige fantasiesettings en -kampioenschappen.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>Gry te obejmują zarówno realistyczne symulacje wyścigów, jak i bardziej fantastyczne gry wyścigowe w stylu arcade. Mogą być oparte na dowolnym rodzaju zawodów, od mistrzostw wyścigowych w świecie rzeczywistym do pełnych fantazji ustawień i mistrzostw.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Os jogos variam de simulações de corrida realistas a mais jogos de corrida ao estilo arcade de fantasia. Podem ser baseados em qualquer tipo de competição, desde campeonatos de corridas do mundo real a cenários e campeonatos completos de fantasia.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>Игры варьируются от реалистичных гоночных симуляторов до более фантазийных гоночных игр в аркадном стиле. Они могут быть основаны на любом типе соревнований, от реальных гоночных чемпионатов до полностью фантастических условий и чемпионатов.</text>
</text>


<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;The Need for Speed (3DO, 1994)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>The Need for Speed focuses on speed, prestige cars and illegal races on open roads, with a more realistic approach than most arcade racing games of its time. Between traffic, police chases and sharp driving sensations, it laid the foundations for a major racing series.
Fun fact: The first cars in the series were recorded from real engines to reproduce a more authentic sound in game.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>The Need for Speed met l’accent sur la vitesse, les voitures de prestige et les courses illégales sur routes ouvertes, dans une approche plus réaliste que la plupart des jeux de course arcade de l’époque. Entre trafic, poursuites policières et sensations de conduite nerveuses, le jeu pose les bases d’une licence majeure du genre.
Fun fact : Les premières voitures de la série avaient été enregistrées avec de vrais moteurs afin de reproduire un son plus réaliste en jeu.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>The Need for Speed apuesta por la velocidad, los coches de prestigio y las carreras ilegales en carreteras abiertas, con un enfoque más realista que la mayoría de juegos arcade de la época. Entre tráfico, persecuciones policiales y conducción intensa, sentó las bases de una gran saga de carreras.
Dato curioso: Los primeros coches de la serie se grabaron con motores reales para reproducir un sonido más auténtico en el juego.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>The Need for Speed punta su velocità, auto di prestigio e corse illegali su strade aperte, con un approccio più realistico rispetto a molti giochi di guida arcade dell’epoca. Tra traffico, inseguimenti della polizia e guida nervosa, gettò le basi di una grande serie automobilistica.
Curiosità: Le prime auto della serie furono registrate da motori reali per ottenere un suono più autentico in gioco.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>The Need for Speed setzt auf Tempo, edle Sportwagen und illegale Rennen auf offenen Straßen, mit einem realistischeren Ansatz als viele Arcade-Rennspiele seiner Zeit. Mit Verkehr, Polizeiverfolgungen und direktem Fahrgefühl legte es die Basis für eine große Rennspielreihe.
Interessante Tatsache: Die ersten Autos der Reihe wurden mit echten Motoren aufgenommen, um im Spiel einen authentischeren Klang zu erzeugen.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>The Need for Speed aposta na velocidade, em carros de prestígio e corridas ilegais em estradas abertas, com uma abordagem mais realista do que muitos jogos arcade da época. Entre trânsito, perseguições policiais e condução intensa, lançou as bases de uma grande série de corridas.
Curiosidade: Os primeiros carros da série foram gravados a partir de motores reais para reproduzir um som mais autêntico no jogo.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
