<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>Auto gamelist. Generally in this list you will find classic board games adapted to the screen and especially chess games.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Auto gamelist. Généralement dans cette liste vous trouverez des jeux de société classiques adaptés à l'écran et notamment des jeux d'échecs.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Auto gamelist. In der Regel finden Sie in dieser Liste klassische Brettspiele, die für den Bildschirm angepasst wurden, insbesondere Schachspiele.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Auto gamelist. Por lo general, en esta lista encontrarás juegos de mesa clásicos adaptados a la pantalla y, en particular, juegos de ajedrez.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Elenco di giochi automatici. In generale, in questo elenco troverete i classici giochi da tavolo adattati allo schermo e in particolare i giochi di scacchi.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>自動ゲームリスト。このリストでは一般的に、スクリーンに適応した古典的なボードゲーム、特にチェスゲームを見つけることができます。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>Automatische spelletjeslijst. Over het algemeen vindt u in deze lijst klassieke bordspellen aangepast aan het scherm en in het bijzonder schaakspellen.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>Auto gamelist. Ogólnie na tej liście znajdziecie klasyczne gry planszowe przystosowane do ekranu, a w szczególności gry szachowe.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Lista automática de jogos. Geralmente nesta lista encontrará jogos de tabuleiro clássicos adaptados ao ecrã e, em particular, jogos de xadrez.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>Автоматический список игр. Как правило, в этом списке вы найдете классические настольные игры, адаптированные для экрана, и, в частности, шахматные игры.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>

