<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>Auto gamelist. An action game is a video game genre that emphasizes physical challenges, including hand-eye coordination and reaction-time. The genre includes a large variety of sub-genres, such as fighting games, beat 'em ups, shooter games, and platform games.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Liste de jeux automatique. Un jeu d'action est un genre de jeu vidéo qui met l'accent sur les défis physiques, notamment la coordination main-œil et le temps de réaction. Le genre comprend une grande variété de sous-genres, tels que les jeux de combat, les beat 'em ups, les jeux de tir et les jeux de plateforme.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Auto-Gameliste. Ein Actionspiel ist ein Videospielgenre, das körperliche Herausforderungen wie Hand-Augen-Koordination und Reaktionszeit in den Vordergrund stellt. Das Genre umfasst eine Vielzahl von Untergenres, wie Kampfspiele, Beat 'em ups, Shooter und Plattformspiele.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Auto gamelist. Un juego de acción es un género de videojuegos que hace hincapié en los desafíos físicos, como la coordinación mano-ojo y el tiempo de reacción. El género incluye una gran variedad de subgéneros, como juegos de lucha, beat 'em ups, juegos de disparos y juegos de plataformas.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Elenco dei giochi d'azione. Un gioco d'azione è un genere di videogiochi che enfatizza le sfide fisiche, tra cui la coordinazione occhio-mano e il tempo di reazione. Il genere comprende una grande varietà di sottogeneri, come i giochi di combattimento, i beat 'em up, gli sparatutto e i giochi di piattaforma.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>オートゲーメリスト。アクションゲームとは、手と目の連携や反応時間など、身体的な挑戦を重視するビデオゲームのジャンルです。このジャンルには、格闘ゲーム、ビート・エム・アップ、シューティングゲーム、プラットフォームゲームなど、多種多様なサブジャンルがあります。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>Auto gamelist. Een actiespel is een videogamegenre dat de nadruk legt op fysieke uitdagingen, zoals hand-oogcoördinatie en reactietijd. Het genre omvat een groot aantal subgenres, zoals vechtspellen, beat 'em ups, schietspellen en platformspellen.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>Auto gamelist. Gra akcji to gatunek gier wideo, który podkreśla fizyczne wyzwania, w tym koordynację ręka-oko i czas reakcji. Gatunek ten obejmuje wiele różnych podgatunków, takich jak gry walki, beat 'em ups, strzelanki i gry platformowe.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Lista automática de jogos. Um jogo de acção é um género de videojogo que enfatiza os desafios físicos, incluindo a coordenação mão-olho e o tempo de reacção. O género inclui uma grande variedade de subgéneros, tais como jogos de luta, jogos de tiros, e jogos de plataforma.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>Автоматический игровой список. Экшн-игра - это жанр видеоигр, в котором особое внимание уделяется физическим нагрузкам, включая координацию движений рук и время реакции. Жанр включает в себя большое количество поджанров, таких как файтинги, beat 'em ups, шутеры и платформенные игры.</text>
</text>


<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Earthworm Jim (Mega Drive, 1994)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>An ordinary earthworm turned accidental hero after finding a powerful space suit, Jim crosses levels packed with action, absurd humor and completely unhinged creatures. Mixing platforming, combat and exaggerated animation, the game created a unique cartoon style that became emblematic of the 1990s.
Fun fact: The game’s animations were drawn frame by frame by hand, giving it a rare sense of fluidity for a 16-bit console.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Ver de terre ordinaire devenu héros malgré lui après avoir trouvé une armure spatiale ultra-puissante, Jim traverse des niveaux remplis d’action, d’humour absurde et de créatures complètement déjantées. Entre plateforme, combats et animations exagérées, le jeu impose un style cartoon unique devenu emblématique des années 90.
Fun fact : Les animations du jeu ont été dessinées image par image à la main, ce qui donnait une fluidité rare pour une console 16 bits.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Un gusano corriente convertido en héroe por accidente tras encontrar un potente traje espacial, Jim atraviesa niveles llenos de acción, humor absurdo y criaturas completamente disparatadas. Entre plataformas, combates y animaciones exageradas, el juego impuso un estilo de dibujo animado único y emblemático de los años 90.
Dato curioso: Las animaciones del juego fueron dibujadas a mano fotograma a fotograma, lo que le daba una fluidez poco común en una consola de 16 bits.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Un normale lombrico diventato eroe per caso dopo aver trovato una potente tuta spaziale, Jim attraversa livelli pieni d’azione, umorismo assurdo e creature completamente fuori di testa. Tra piattaforme, combattimenti e animazioni esagerate, il gioco impose uno stile cartoon unico diventato simbolo degli anni 90.
Curiosità: Le animazioni del gioco furono disegnate a mano fotogramma per fotogramma, dando una fluidità rara per una console a 16 bit.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Ein gewöhnlicher Regenwurm wird nach dem Fund eines mächtigen Raumanzugs unfreiwillig zum Helden und durchquert Level voller Action, absurdem Humor und völlig verrückter Kreaturen. Mit Plattformpassagen, Kämpfen und überzeichneten Animationen prägte das Spiel einen einzigartigen Cartoon-Stil der 90er Jahre.
Interessante Tatsache: Die Animationen des Spiels wurden Bild für Bild von Hand gezeichnet, was ihm für eine 16-Bit-Konsole eine seltene Geschmeidigkeit verlieh.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Uma minhoca comum transformada em herói por acaso depois de encontrar uma poderosa armadura espacial, Jim atravessa níveis cheios de ação, humor absurdo e criaturas completamente malucas. Entre plataformas, combates e animações exageradas, o jogo impôs um estilo cartoon único e marcante dos anos 90.
Curiosidade: As animações do jogo foram desenhadas à mão quadro a quadro, dando uma fluidez rara numa consola de 16 bits.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>

