<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
"<text>This type of video game generally adopts a contest format for several players in turn. 
Tests, questions, puzzles... Who will win?</text>"
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
"<text>Ce type de jeu vidéo adopte généralement un format de concours pour plusieurs joueurs à tour de rôle. 
Tests, questions, énigmes... Qui va gagner ?</text>"
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
"<text>Diese Art von Videospielen nimmt in der Regel ein Wettbewerbsformat an, bei dem mehrere Spieler abwechselnd gegeneinander antreten. 
Tests, Fragen, Rätsel ... Wer wird gewinnen?</text>"
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
"<text>Este tipo de videojuegos adopta generalmente un formato de competición para varios jugadores por turnos. 
Pruebas, preguntas, rompecabezas... ¿Quién ganará?</text>"
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
"<text>Questo tipo di videogiochi adotta generalmente un formato di competizione per più giocatori a turno. 
Test, domande, enigmi... Chi vincerà?</text>"
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
"<text>この種のビデオゲームは、一般に複数のプレイヤーが順番に対戦する形式が採用されています。
テスト、問題、パズル...。誰が勝つのでしょうか？</text>"
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
"<text>Dit type videospel heeft over het algemeen een competitievorm voor meerdere spelers om de beurt. 
Tests, vragen, puzzels... Wie zal er winnen?</text>"
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
"<text>Ten typ gry wideo zazwyczaj przyjmuje format konkurencji dla kilku graczy z kolei. 
Testy, pytania, zagadki... Kto wygra?</text>"
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
"<text>Este tipo de jogo de vídeo adopta geralmente um formato de competição para vários jogadores por sua vez. 
Testes, perguntas, puzzles... Quem vai ganhar?</text>"
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
"<text>Этот тип видеоигр обычно принимает формат соревнования для нескольких игроков по очереди. 
Тесты, вопросы, головоломки... Кто победит?</text>"
</text>

<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Buzz! The Mega Quiz (PlayStation 2, 2005)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>Buzz hosts wild quiz sessions inspired by television game shows, where players compete using the colorful oversized buzzers that became iconic for the series. With general knowledge, traps, absurd rounds and a strong TV-show atmosphere, the game easily turns a night with friends into a loud and chaotic competition.
Fun fact: The series’ USB buzzers became so popular that many PC games and emulators later recognized them automatically.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Buzz anime des quiz délirants inspirés des émissions télévisées, où les joueurs s’affrontent à l’aide de gros buzzers colorés devenus emblématiques de la série. Entre culture générale, pièges, manches absurdes et ambiance de plateau TV, le jeu transforme facilement une soirée entre amis en compétition bruyante et complètement chaotique.
Fun fact : Les buzzers USB de la série sont devenus si populaires qu’ils ont ensuite été reconnus automatiquement par de nombreux jeux et émulateurs sur PC.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Buzz presenta concursos disparatados inspirados en los programas de televisión, donde los jugadores compiten con grandes pulsadores de colores que se volvieron emblemáticos de la serie. Entre cultura general, trampas, rondas absurdas y ambiente de plató, el juego convierte una noche entre amigos en una competición ruidosa y caótica.
Dato curioso: Los pulsadores USB de la serie se hicieron tan populares que muchos juegos y emuladores de PC los reconocieron automáticamente más tarde.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Buzz conduce quiz folli ispirati ai programmi televisivi, in cui i giocatori si sfidano usando grandi pulsanti colorati diventati simbolo della serie. Tra cultura generale, trabocchetti, manche assurde e atmosfera da studio TV, il gioco trasforma una serata tra amici in una competizione rumorosa e caotica.
Curiosità: I buzzer USB della serie divennero così popolari che molti giochi ed emulatori su PC li riconobbero automaticamente in seguito.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Buzz moderiert verrückte Quizrunden im Stil von Fernsehshows, bei denen die Spieler mit großen farbigen Buzzern gegeneinander antreten, die zum Markenzeichen der Serie wurden. Mit Allgemeinwissen, Fallen, absurden Runden und TV-Studio-Atmosphäre wird jeder Abend mit Freunden schnell zu einem lauten Wettbewerb.
Interessante Tatsache: Die USB-Buzzer der Serie wurden so beliebt, dass viele PC-Spiele und Emulatoren sie später automatisch erkannten.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Buzz apresenta concursos malucos inspirados nos programas de televisão, nos quais os jogadores competem com grandes buzzers coloridos que se tornaram emblemáticos da série. Entre cultura geral, armadilhas, rondas absurdas e ambiente de estúdio, o jogo transforma uma noite entre amigos numa competição barulhenta e caótica.
Curiosidade: Os buzzers USB da série tornaram-se tão populares que muitos jogos e emuladores de PC passaram a reconhecê-los automaticamente.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
