<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>Automatic game list. A simple game that does not require much skill or dedication from the player. Not really for the hardcore gamer, more for family fun.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Liste de jeux automatique. Un jeu simple qui ne demande pas beaucoup d'habileté ou de dévouement de la part du joueur. Il n'est pas vraiment destiné aux joueurs invétérés, mais plutôt aux familles.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Automatische Spielliste. Ein einfaches Spiel, das dem Spieler nicht viel Geschick oder Hingabe abverlangt. Nicht wirklich für den Hardcore-Gamer, mehr für die Familie Spaß.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Lista automática de juegos. Un juego sencillo que no requiere mucha habilidad ni dedicación por parte del jugador. No es realmente para el jugador hardcore, más para la diversión familiar.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Elenco automatico dei giochi. Un gioco semplice che non richiede molta abilità o dedizione da parte del giocatore. Non è adatto ai giocatori più accaniti, ma è più adatto al divertimento della famiglia.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>自動ゲームリスト。プレイヤーのスキルや献身をあまり必要としない、シンプルなゲームです。ハードコアゲーマー向けではなく、家族で楽しむのに適しています。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>Automatische spellijst. Een eenvoudig spel dat niet veel vaardigheid of toewijding van de speler vraagt. Niet echt voor de hardcore gamer, meer voor familieplezier.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>Automatyczna lista gier. Prosta gra, która nie wymaga od gracza dużych umiejętności ani poświęcenia. Raczej nie dla hardcorowego gracza, bardziej do rodzinnej zabawy.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Lista de jogos automática. Um jogo simples que não requer muita habilidade ou dedicação por parte do jogador. Não realmente para o jogador hardcore, mais para diversão familiar.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>Автоматический список игр. Простая игра, которая не требует от игрока большого мастерства или самоотверженности. Не совсем для хардкорных геймеров, скорее для семейного развлечения.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;South Park (Nintendo 64, 1998)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>Cartman, Stan, Kyle and Kenny represent the irreverent humor of South Park in a video game adaptation faithful to the spirit of the animated series. With deliberately caricatured characters, absurd situations and a chaotic atmosphere, the game brings back the show’s world with the provocative tone that marked the late 1990s.
Fun fact: South Park began as a handmade cutout animated short film that went viral long before YouTube or social networks existed.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Cartman, Stan, Kyle et Kenny représentent l’humour irrévérencieux de South Park dans une adaptation vidéoludique fidèle à l’esprit de la série animée. Entre personnages volontairement caricaturaux, situations absurdes et ambiance déjantée, le jeu reprend l’univers du dessin animé avec un ton volontairement provocateur typique de la fin des années 90.
Fun fact : South Park est né à partir d’un court métrage animé bricolé avec du papier découpé, devenu viral bien avant l’arrivée de YouTube ou des réseaux sociaux.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Cartman, Stan, Kyle y Kenny representan el humor irreverente de South Park en una adaptación de videojuego fiel al espíritu de la serie animada. Con personajes deliberadamente caricaturescos, situaciones absurdas y un ambiente disparatado, el juego recupera el mundo de la serie con el tono provocador propio de finales de los años 90.
Dato curioso: South Park nació como un cortometraje animado hecho con recortes de papel que se volvió viral mucho antes de YouTube o las redes sociales.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Cartman, Stan, Kyle e Kenny rappresentano l’umorismo irriverente di South Park in un adattamento videoludico fedele allo spirito della serie animata. Tra personaggi volutamente caricaturali, situazioni assurde e atmosfera folle, il gioco riprende il mondo del cartone con il tono provocatorio tipico della fine degli anni 90.
Curiosità: South Park nacque da un cortometraggio animato realizzato con carta ritagliata, diventato virale molto prima di YouTube o dei social network.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Cartman, Stan, Kyle und Kenny verkörpern den respektlosen Humor von South Park in einer Videospielumsetzung, die dem Geist der Zeichentrickserie treu bleibt. Mit bewusst überzeichneten Figuren, absurden Situationen und chaotischer Stimmung greift das Spiel die Welt der Serie mit dem provokanten Ton der späten 90er Jahre auf.
Interessante Tatsache: South Park entstand aus einem von Hand gebastelten Kurzfilm mit ausgeschnittenem Papier, der lange vor YouTube oder sozialen Netzwerken viral wurde.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Cartman, Stan, Kyle e Kenny representam o humor irreverente de South Park numa adaptação em videojogo fiel ao espírito da série animada. Com personagens caricaturais, situações absurdas e uma atmosfera caótica, o jogo recria o universo do desenho animado com o tom provocador típico do final dos anos 90.
Curiosidade: South Park nasceu de uma curta-metragem animada feita com recortes de papel, que se tornou viral muito antes do YouTube ou das redes sociais.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>

