<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>A subgenre of action games, they are characterized by a level design featuring uneven terrain and suspended platforms of varying heights, which requires the use of the player character's abilities, such as jumping and climbing, to navigate the environment and achieve its objective.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Sous-genre de jeu d'action, ils se caractérisent par une conception de niveau comportant un terrain irrégulier et des plates-formes suspendues de hauteur variable, qui nécessite l'utilisation des capacités du personnage du joueur, comme le saut et l'escalade, pour naviguer dans l'environnement et atteindre son objectif.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Untergattung der Actionspiele, sie zeichnen sich durch ein Leveldesign mit unregelmäßigem Gelände und hängenden Plattformen unterschiedlicher Höhe aus, das den Einsatz von Fähigkeiten der Spielerfigur wie Springen und Klettern erfordert, um durch die Umgebung zu navigieren und das Ziel zu erreichen.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Subgénero de los juegos de acción, se caracterizan por un diseño de niveles con terreno irregular y plataformas suspendidas de distintas alturas, que requiere el uso de las habilidades del personaje del jugador, como saltar y trepar, para recorrer el entorno y alcanzar su objetivo.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Sottogenere dei giochi d'azione, sono caratterizzati da un design dei livelli caratterizzato da terreni irregolari e piattaforme sospese di altezza variabile, che richiede l'uso delle abilità del giocatore, come il salto e l'arrampicata, per navigare nell'ambiente e raggiungere l'obiettivo.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>アクションゲームの亜流で、凹凸のある地形や高さの異なる吊り下げ式のプラットフォームが特徴的なレベルデザインで、プレイヤーキャラクターがジャンプやクライミングなどの能力を駆使して環境を移動し、目的を達成することが要求されるゲームです。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>Dit subgenre van actiegames wordt gekenmerkt door een levelontwerp met oneffen terrein en hangende platforms van verschillende hoogte, waarbij de vaardigheden van de speler, zoals springen en klimmen, moeten worden gebruikt om door de omgeving te navigeren en het doel te bereiken.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>Podgatunek gier akcji, charakteryzują się projektem poziomu zawierającym nierówny teren i zawieszone platformy o różnej wysokości, co wymaga użycia umiejętności postaci gracza, takich jak skoki i wspinaczka, aby poruszać się po środowisku i osiągnąć swój cel.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Um sub-género de jogos de acção, caracterizam-se por um desenho de nível com terreno irregular e plataformas suspensas de diferentes alturas, o que requer a utilização das capacidades do personagem jogador, tais como saltar e escalar, para navegar no ambiente e alcançar o seu objectivo.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>Поджанр экшн-игр, для них характерен дизайн уровней с неровным рельефом и подвесными платформами разной высоты, что требует использования способностей персонажа игрока, таких как прыжки и лазание, для перемещения по окружению и достижения цели.</text>
</text>


<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Alex Kidd in Miracle World (Master System, 1986)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>Alex Kidd crosses the kingdom of Radaxian with his fists, vehicles, hidden items and rock-paper-scissors duels against the minions of Janken the Great. Its colorful style, many secrets and sometimes harsh difficulty make it one of the most memorable games on the Master System.
Fun fact: Before Sonic arrived, Alex Kidd was long considered Sega’s official mascot.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Alex Kidd traverse le royaume de Radaxian à coups de poing, enchaînant plateformes, véhicules, objets cachés et duels de pierre-feuille-ciseaux contre les sbires de Janken le Grand. Son style très coloré, ses secrets nombreux et sa difficulté parfois rude en font l’un des jeux les plus marquants de la Master System.
Fun fact : Avant l’arrivée de Sonic, Alex Kidd a longtemps été considéré comme la mascotte officielle de Sega.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Alex Kidd recorre el reino de Radaxian a puñetazos, entre plataformas, vehículos, objetos ocultos y duelos de piedra, papel o tijera contra los secuaces de Janken el Grande. Su estilo colorido, sus muchos secretos y su dificultad a veces dura lo convierten en uno de los juegos más recordados de Master System.
Dato curioso: Antes de la llegada de Sonic, Alex Kidd fue considerado durante mucho tiempo la mascota oficial de Sega.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Alex Kidd attraversa il regno di Radaxian a colpi di pugni, tra piattaforme, veicoli, oggetti nascosti e duelli di sasso-carta-forbici contro gli scagnozzi di Janken il Grande. Il suo stile colorato, i tanti segreti e la difficoltà a tratti severa lo rendono uno dei giochi più ricordati del Master System.
Curiosità: Prima dell’arrivo di Sonic, Alex Kidd è stato a lungo considerato la mascotte ufficiale di Sega.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Alex Kidd durchquert das Königreich Radaxian mit Fäusten, Fahrzeugen, versteckten Gegenständen und Stein-Schere-Papier-Duellen gegen die Schergen von Janken dem Großen. Sein farbenfroher Stil, viele Geheimnisse und teils harte Schwierigkeit machen es zu einem der bekanntesten Master-System-Spiele.
Interessante Tatsache: Vor Sonics Auftritt galt Alex Kidd lange Zeit als offizielles Maskottchen von Sega.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Alex Kidd atravessa o reino de Radaxian aos socos, entre plataformas, veículos, objetos escondidos e duelos de pedra-papel-tesoura contra os soldados de Janken, o Grande. O estilo colorido, os muitos segredos e a dificuldade por vezes dura tornam-no num dos jogos mais marcantes da Master System.
Curiosidade: Antes da chegada de Sonic, Alex Kidd foi durante muito tempo considerado a mascote oficial da Sega.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>

