<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>A genre that aims to simulate reality as closely as possible, avoiding the simplistic controls or mechanics characteristic of games and applying the laws of physics in a realistic manner. There are countless types of games depending on their subject matter, such as flight, driving or control simulations (business, construction, etc.). </text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Genre qui vise à simuler la réalité le plus fidèlement possible, en évitant les contrôles ou mécaniques simplistes caractéristiques des jeux et en appliquant les lois de la physique de manière réaliste. Il existe d'innombrables types de jeux en fonction de leur sujet, tels que les simulations de vol, de conduite ou de contrôle (affaires, construction, etc.). </text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Genre, das darauf abzielt, die Realität so genau wie möglich zu simulieren, indem es die für Spiele typischen simplen Steuerungen oder Mechaniken vermeidet und die Gesetze der Physik realistisch anwendet. Je nach Thema gibt es unzählige Arten von Spielen, z. B. Flug-, Fahr- oder Kontrollsimulationen (Wirtschaft, Bauwesen usw.). </text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Género que pretende simular la realidad lo más fielmente posible, evitando los controles o mecánicas simplistas característicos de los juegos y aplicando las leyes de la física de forma realista. Existen innumerables tipos de juegos en función de su temática, como las simulaciones de vuelo, de conducción o de control (empresas, construcción, etc.). </text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Un genere che mira a simulare il più possibile la realtà, evitando i controlli o le meccaniche semplicistiche tipiche dei giochi e applicando le leggi della fisica in modo realistico. Esistono innumerevoli tipi di giochi a seconda dell'argomento trattato, come ad esempio le simulazioni di volo, di guida o di controllo (affari, costruzioni, ecc.). </text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>ゲーム特有の単純化された操作や仕組みを避け、物理法則をリアルに適用して、できるだけ現実をシミュレートすることを目的としたジャンルをいう。飛行、運転、制御シミュレーション（ビジネス、建設など）など、対象によって数え切れないほどの種類がある。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>Een genre dat ernaar streeft de werkelijkheid zo dicht mogelijk te benaderen, waarbij de voor games kenmerkende simplistische besturing of mechanica wordt vermeden en de wetten van de fysica op realistische wijze worden toegepast. Er zijn talloze soorten games, afhankelijk van hun onderwerp, zoals vlucht-, rij- of besturingssimulaties (bedrijfsleven, bouw, enz.). </text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>Gatunek gier, który ma na celu jak najwierniejsze symulowanie rzeczywistości, unikając charakterystycznego dla gier uproszczonego sterowania czy mechaniki i stosując prawa fizyki w sposób realistyczny. Istnieje niezliczona ilość rodzajów gier w zależności od ich tematyki, np. symulacje lotu, jazdy samochodem czy sterowania (biznes, budownictwo itp.). </text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Um género que visa simular a realidade o mais próximo possível, evitando os controlos simplistas ou mecânicos característicos dos jogos e aplicando as leis da física de uma forma realista. Existem inúmeros tipos de jogos em função do seu tema, tais como simulações de voo, condução ou controlo (negócios, construção, etc.). </text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>Жанр, который стремится как можно ближе имитировать реальность, избегая упрощенного управления или механики, характерных для игр, и реалистично применяя законы физики. Существует бесчисленное множество типов игр в зависимости от их тематики, например, симуляторы полетов, вождения или управления (бизнес, строительство и т.д.). </text>
</text>


<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;F-22 Raptor (PC, 1997)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>The Lockheed Martin F-22 Raptor represents modern aerial combat simulation, with missions focused on air superiority, interceptions and ground attacks. Between radar, guided missiles and speed management, the game highlights the control of a stealth fighter in a more technical approach than pure arcade action.
Fun fact: Some pilots describe the F-22 cockpit as “a highly sophisticated video game” because of its screens and digital systems.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Le Lockheed Martin F-22 Raptor incarne la simulation de combat aérien moderne, avec des missions centrées sur la supériorité aérienne, les interceptions et l’attaque de cibles au sol. Entre radar, missiles guidés et gestion de la vitesse, le jeu met en avant le pilotage d’un chasseur furtif dans une approche plus technique que l’arcade pure.
Fun fact : Certains pilotes décrivent le cockpit du F-22 comme “un jeu vidéo ultra sophistiqué” à cause de ses écrans et systèmes numériques.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>El Lockheed Martin F-22 Raptor representa la simulación moderna de combate aéreo, con misiones centradas en la superioridad aérea, las intercepciones y los ataques a objetivos terrestres. Entre radar, misiles guiados y control de la velocidad, el juego destaca el pilotaje de un caza furtivo con un enfoque más técnico que arcade.
Dato curioso: Algunos pilotos describen la cabina del F-22 como “un videojuego ultra sofisticado” por sus pantallas y sistemas digitales.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Il Lockheed Martin F-22 Raptor incarna la simulazione moderna di combattimento aereo, con missioni dedicate alla superiorità aerea, alle intercettazioni e agli attacchi a bersagli terrestri. Tra radar, missili guidati e gestione della velocità, il gioco mette in risalto il pilotaggio di un caccia stealth con un approccio più tecnico che arcade.
Curiosità: Alcuni piloti descrivono l’abitacolo dell’F-22 come “un videogioco ultra sofisticato” per via dei suoi schermi e sistemi digitali.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Der Lockheed Martin F-22 Raptor steht für moderne Luftkampfsimulation mit Missionen rund um Luftüberlegenheit, Abfangeinsätze und Angriffe auf Bodenziele. Zwischen Radar, Lenkwaffen und Geschwindigkeitskontrolle zeigt das Spiel die Steuerung eines Tarnkappenjägers deutlich technischer als reine Arcade-Action.
Interessante Tatsache: Einige Piloten beschreiben das Cockpit der F-22 wegen seiner Bildschirme und digitalen Systeme als “ein hochentwickeltes Videospiel”.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>O Lockheed Martin F-22 Raptor representa a simulação moderna de combate aéreo, com missões focadas na superioridade aérea, interceções e ataques a alvos terrestres. Entre radar, mísseis guiados e gestão da velocidade, o jogo destaca o controlo de um caça furtivo numa abordagem mais técnica do que arcade.
Curiosidade: Alguns pilotos descrevem o cockpit do F-22 como “um videojogo ultra sofisticado” devido aos seus ecrãs e sistemas digitais.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
