<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>Shooter video games or shooters are a subgenre of action video games where the focus is almost entirely on the defeat of the character's enemies using the weapons given to the player.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Les jeux vidéo de tir ou shooters sont un sous-genre des jeux vidéo d'action où l'accent est presque entièrement mis sur la défaite des ennemis du personnage à l'aide des armes mises à la disposition du joueur.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Shooter-Videospiele oder Shooter sind ein Subgenre von Action-Videospielen, bei denen der Schwerpunkt fast ausschließlich auf dem Besiegen der Feinde der Spielfigur mit den dem Spieler zur Verfügung stehenden Waffen liegt.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Los videojuegos de disparos o shooters son un subgénero de los videojuegos de acción en los que la atención se centra casi por completo en la derrota de los enemigos del personaje utilizando las armas que se le dan al jugador.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>I videogiochi sparatutto o sparatutto sono un sottogenere di videogiochi d'azione in cui l'attenzione si concentra quasi esclusivamente sulla sconfitta dei nemici del personaggio utilizzando le armi a disposizione del giocatore.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>シュータービデオゲームまたはシューティングゲームは、アクションビデオゲームのサブジャンルであり、プレイヤーに与えられた武器を使ってキャラクターの敵を倒すことにほとんど焦点が当てられています。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>Shooter video games of shooters zijn een subgenre van actie video games waar de nadruk bijna volledig ligt op het verslaan van de vijanden van het personage met behulp van de wapens die de speler krijgt.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>Shooter gry wideo lub strzelanki są podgatunek akcji gier wideo, w których koncentruje się prawie całkowicie na pokonaniu wrogów bohatera za pomocą broni podanych do gracza.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Os jogos de vídeo shooters ou atiradores são um subgénero de jogos de vídeo de acção em que o foco está quase inteiramente na derrota dos inimigos da personagem usando as armas dadas ao jogador.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>Видеоигры-стрелялки или шутеры - это поджанр видеоигр в жанре экшн, где основное внимание почти полностью сосредоточено на поражении врагов персонажа с помощью оружия, предоставленного игроку.</text>
</text>


<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Terminator 2: Judgment Day (Arcade, 1991)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>The T-800 brings players back into the explosive world of Terminator 2 through an intense rail shooter where waves of machines, drones and metallic endoskeletons must be destroyed. With constant gunfire, futuristic scenery and brutal action inspired by the film, the game recreates the spectacular atmosphere of early 90s arcade machines.
Fun fact: The metallic sound effects of the Terminators were created from industrial noises slowed down and reworked in the studio.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Le T-800 replonge les joueurs dans l’univers explosif de Terminator 2 à travers un rail shooter intense où il faut repousser des vagues de machines, de drones et d’endosquelettes métalliques. Entre fusillades continues, décors futuristes et action brutale inspirée du film, le jeu recrée l’ambiance spectaculaire des grandes bornes d’arcade des années 90.
Fun fact : Les bruitages métalliques des Terminators ont été créés à partir de sons industriels ralentis et retravaillés en studio.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>El T-800 devuelve a los jugadores al universo explosivo de Terminator 2 en un intenso rail shooter donde hay que destruir oleadas de máquinas, drones y endoesqueletos metálicos. Entre disparos constantes, escenarios futuristas y acción brutal inspirada en la película, el juego recrea el ambiente espectacular de las grandes recreativas de los años 90.
Dato curioso: Los efectos metálicos de sonido de los Terminators se crearon a partir de ruidos industriales ralentizados y retocados en estudio.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Il T-800 riporta i giocatori nell’universo esplosivo di Terminator 2 con un rail shooter intenso in cui bisogna respingere ondate di macchine, droni ed endoscheletri metallici. Tra sparatorie continue, scenari futuristici e azione brutale ispirata al film, il gioco ricrea l’atmosfera spettacolare delle grandi sale arcade degli anni 90.
Curiosità: Gli effetti sonori metallici dei Terminator furono creati partendo da rumori industriali rallentati e rielaborati in studio.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Der T-800 führt die Spieler in die explosive Welt von Terminator 2 zurück, in einem intensiven Rail-Shooter voller Maschinen, Drohnen und metallischer Endoskelette. Mit Dauerfeuer, futuristischen Kulissen und brutaler Action nach dem Film fängt das Spiel die spektakuläre Atmosphäre großer Arcade-Automaten der 90er Jahre ein.
Interessante Tatsache: Die metallischen Geräusche der Terminatoren wurden aus verlangsamten Industrieklängen erzeugt und im Studio nachbearbeitet.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>O T-800 leva os jogadores de volta ao universo explosivo de Terminator 2 num rail shooter intenso, onde é preciso destruir vagas de máquinas, drones e endosqueletos metálicos. Entre tiroteios constantes, cenários futuristas e ação brutal inspirada no filme, o jogo recria a atmosfera espetacular das grandes arcades dos anos 90.
Curiosidade: Os efeitos sonoros metálicos dos Terminators foram criados a partir de sons industriais desacelerados e retrabalhados em estúdio.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
