<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>Auto gamelist. An adventure game is a video game in which the player assumes the role of a protagonist in an interactive story driven by exploration and/or puzzle-solving.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Liste de jeux automatique. Un jeu d'aventure est un jeu vidéo dans lequel le joueur joue le rôle du protagoniste d'une histoire interactive basée sur l'exploration et/ou la résolution d'énigmes.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Auto-Gameliste. Ein Abenteuerspiel ist ein Videospiel, in dem der Spieler die Rolle eines Protagonisten in einer interaktiven Geschichte übernimmt, die durch Erkundung und/oder das Lösen von Rätseln vorangetrieben wird.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Auto gamelist. Un juego de aventuras es un videojuego en el que el jugador asume el papel de un protagonista en una historia interactiva impulsada por la exploración y/o la resolución de puzles.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Elenco automatico dei giochi. Un gioco di avventura è un videogioco in cui il giocatore assume il ruolo di protagonista in una storia interattiva guidata dall'esplorazione e/o dalla risoluzione di enigmi.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>自動ゲームリスト。アドベンチャーゲームとは、プレイヤーが主人公となり、探索や謎解きによって進められるインタラクティブなストーリーを楽しむビデオゲームのことです。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>Auto gamelist. Een avonturenspel is een videospel waarin de speler de rol aanneemt van een hoofdpersoon in een interactief verhaal, gedreven door exploratie en/of het oplossen van puzzels.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>Auto gamelist. Gra przygodowa to gra wideo, w której gracz przyjmuje rolę bohatera w interaktywnej historii napędzanej eksploracją i/lub rozwiązywaniem zagadek.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Lista automática de jogos. Um jogo de aventura é um videojogo em que o jogador assume o papel de protagonista numa história interactiva impulsionada pela exploração e/ou resolução de puzzles.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>Автоматический список игр. Приключенческая игра - это видеоигра, в которой игрок берет на себя роль главного героя в интерактивной истории, движимой исследованием и/или решением головоломок.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>

