<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>Games using a steering wheel, like Gran Turismo or Forza Motorsport, deliver an immersive driving experience, simulating the precision and realism of car racing. Popular in simulation and arcade games, they are essential for motorsport enthusiasts.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Les jeux utilisant un volant, comme Gran Turismo ou Forza Motorsport, offrent une expérience de conduite immersive, simulant la précision et le réalisme des courses automobiles. Populaires dans les jeux de simulation et d'arcade, ils sont essentiels pour les fans de sports mécaniques.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;The Need for Speed (3DO, 1994)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>The Need for Speed focuses on driving prestige cars on open roads, with traffic, fast corners and police pursuits. Its more immersive approach than pure arcade racing fits perfectly with steering wheel games, where every acceleration, braking move and change of line strengthens the feeling of being behind the wheel.
Fun fact: The game was developed with help from Road & Track magazine to give the cars and driving feel more credibility.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>The Need for Speed met en avant la conduite de voitures de prestige sur routes ouvertes, avec trafic, virages rapides et poursuites policières. Son approche plus immersive que l’arcade pure colle parfaitement aux jeux au volant, où chaque accélération, freinage et changement de trajectoire renforce les sensations de course.
Fun fact : Le jeu a été développé avec l’aide du magazine Road & Track, afin de donner plus de crédibilité aux véhicules et aux sensations de conduite.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>The Need for Speed se centra en conducir coches de prestigio por carreteras abiertas, con tráfico, curvas rápidas y persecuciones policiales. Su enfoque más inmersivo que la conducción arcade pura encaja muy bien con los juegos de volante, donde cada aceleración, frenada y cambio de trazada refuerza la sensación de estar al mando.
Dato curioso: El juego se desarrolló con la ayuda de la revista Road & Track para dar más credibilidad a los vehículos y a las sensaciones de conducción.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>The Need for Speed mette al centro la guida di auto prestigiose su strade aperte, con traffico, curve veloci e inseguimenti della polizia. Il suo approccio più immersivo rispetto alla corsa arcade pura si adatta bene ai giochi con volante, dove ogni accelerazione, frenata e cambio di traiettoria aumenta la sensazione di guida.
Curiosità: Il gioco fu sviluppato con l’aiuto della rivista Road & Track per dare più credibilità alle auto e alle sensazioni di guida.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>The Need for Speed rückt das Fahren exklusiver Sportwagen auf offenen Straßen in den Mittelpunkt, mit Verkehr, schnellen Kurven und Polizeiverfolgungen. Der stärker immersive Ansatz passt gut zu Lenkradspielen, bei denen jede Beschleunigung, Bremsung und Linienwahl das Fahrgefühl verstärkt.
Interessante Tatsache: Das Spiel wurde mit Unterstützung des Magazins Road & Track entwickelt, um Fahrzeugen und Fahrgefühl mehr Glaubwürdigkeit zu verleihen.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>The Need for Speed destaca a condução de carros de prestígio em estradas abertas, com trânsito, curvas rápidas e perseguições policiais. A sua abordagem mais imersiva do que a corrida arcade pura combina bem com jogos de volante, onde cada aceleração, travagem e mudança de trajetória reforça a sensação de condução.
Curiosidade: O jogo foi desenvolvido com a ajuda da revista Road & Track para dar mais credibilidade aos carros e às sensações de condução.</text>
</text>
</view>
</theme>
