<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>The shoot 'em up (shmup) originated in the arcade, with Space Invaders generally credited with the birth of the genre. The genre reached a peak in popularity in the late 1980s and early 1990s. Game styles range from cute to serious, fantasy, science fiction and even historical fact.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Le shoot 'em up (shmup) est originaire des salles d'arcade, avec Space Invaders généralement crédité de la naissance du genre. Le genre atteint un niveau record de popularité à la fin des années 1980 et au début des années 1990. Les styles de jeu varie du mignon au sérieux, de la fantasy, de la science-fiction voir même des faits historiques.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Shoot 'em up (Shmup) hat seinen Ursprung in den Arcade-Hallen, wobei Space Invaders allgemein als Geburtsstunde des Genres angesehen wird. Das Genre erreichte in den späten 1980er und frühen 1990er Jahren einen Popularitätsrekord. Die Spielstile reichen von niedlich bis ernst, von Fantasy über Science-Fiction bis hin zu historischen Fakten.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Los juegos de disparos (shmup) se originaron en los salones recreativos, y se suele atribuir a Space Invaders el nacimiento del género. El género alcanzó su máxima popularidad a finales de los ochenta y principios de los noventa. Los estilos de juego van de lo simpático a lo serio, pasando por la fantasía, la ciencia ficción e incluso los hechos históricos.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Gli shoot 'em up (shmup) hanno avuto origine nelle sale giochi, e Space Invaders è generalmente accreditato come l'ideatore del genere. Il genere ha raggiunto il picco di popolarità tra la fine degli anni '80 e l'inizio degli anni '90. Gli stili di gioco vanno dal simpatico al serio, al fantasy, alla fantascienza e persino ai fatti storici.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>シューティングゲーム（shmup）はアーケードで生まれたもので、一般的には『スペースインベーダー』がこのジャンルの発祥とされています。1980年代後半から1990年代前半にかけて、その人気はピークに達した。ゲームのスタイルは、かわいいものからシリアスなもの、ファンタジー、SF、歴史的事実まで、さまざまなものがあります。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>De shoot 'em up (shmup) vindt zijn oorsprong in de arcades, waarbij Space Invaders over het algemeen wordt beschouwd als de geboorte van het genre. Het genre bereikte een piek in populariteit eind jaren tachtig en begin jaren negentig. Spelstijlen variëren van schattig tot serieus, fantasie, sciencefiction en zelfs historische feiten.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>Shoot 'em up (shmup) wywodzi się z salonów gier, a za narodziny gatunku powszechnie uznaje się Space Invaders. Gatunek ten osiągnął szczyt popularności w późnych latach 80. i wczesnych 90. Style gry wahają się od słodkich do poważnych, fantasy, science fiction, a nawet faktów historycznych.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>O shoot 'em up (shmup) teve origem nas arcadas, sendo os Space Invaders geralmente creditados com o nascimento do género. O género atingiu um pico de popularidade no final da década de 1980 e início da década de 1990. Os estilos de jogo vão desde o engraçado ao sério, à fantasia, à ficção científica e mesmo ao facto histórico.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>Жанр shoot 'em up (shmup) зародился в игровых автоматах, а рождение жанра обычно приписывают Space Invaders. Жанр достиг пика популярности в конце 1980-х - начале 1990-х годов. Стили игр варьируются от милых до серьезных, фэнтези, научной фантастики и даже исторических фактов.</text>
</text>


<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Raiden (Arcade, 1990)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>Raiden puts the player in control of a futuristic fighter sent to repel an alien invasion through vertical stages packed with bullets, tanks and massive bosses. Its direct action, upgradeable weapons and two-player mode make it a fast and intense arcade shoot ’em up classic.
Fun fact: The name Raiden means “thunder and lightning” in Japanese, a fitting choice for a game where the screen erupts with shots and impacts.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Raiden place le joueur aux commandes d’un chasseur futuriste chargé de repousser une invasion extraterrestre à travers des stages verticaux remplis de tirs, de tanks et de boss imposants. Son action directe, ses armes évolutives et son mode deux joueurs en font un classique nerveux du shoot ’em up arcade.
Fun fact : Le nom Raiden signifie “tonnerre et éclair” en japonais, un choix parfait pour un jeu où l’écran explose sous les tirs et les impacts.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Raiden pone al jugador a los mandos de un caza futurista encargado de repeler una invasión alienígena a través de fases verticales llenas de disparos, tanques y enormes jefes. Su acción directa, armas mejorables y modo para dos jugadores lo convierten en un clásico arcade intenso.
Dato curioso: El nombre Raiden significa “trueno y relámpago” en japonés, una elección perfecta para un juego donde la pantalla estalla entre disparos e impactos.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Raiden mette il giocatore ai comandi di un caccia futuristico incaricato di respingere un’invasione aliena attraverso livelli verticali pieni di proiettili, carri armati e boss imponenti. Azione diretta, armi potenziabili e modalità a due giocatori lo rendono un classico arcade frenetico.
Curiosità: Il nome Raiden significa “tuono e fulmine” in giapponese, una scelta perfetta per un gioco in cui lo schermo esplode tra colpi e impatti.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Raiden setzt den Spieler in einen futuristischen Jäger, der eine Alien-Invasion in vertikalen Levels voller Geschosse, Panzer und riesiger Bosse zurückschlagen muss. Direkte Action, aufrüstbare Waffen und der Zwei-Spieler-Modus machen es zu einem schnellen Arcade-Klassiker.
Interessante Tatsache: Der Name Raiden bedeutet auf Japanisch “Donner und Blitz”, passend zu einem Spiel, in dem der Bildschirm vor Schüssen und Treffern explodiert.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Raiden coloca o jogador no comando de um caça futurista encarregado de travar uma invasão alienígena em fases verticais cheias de tiros, tanques e bosses enormes. A ação direta, as armas evolutivas e o modo para dois jogadores fazem dele um clássico arcade intenso.
Curiosidade: O nome Raiden significa “trovão e relâmpago” em japonês, uma escolha perfeita para um jogo onde o ecrã explode entre tiros e impactos.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
