<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
"<text>Auto gamelist.
Keep out of the reach of children... ;)</text>"
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
"<text>Liste de jeux automatique à tenir hors de portée des enfants... ;)</text>"
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
"<text>Automatische Gameliste.
Außerhalb der Reichweite von Kindern aufbewahren... ;)</text>"
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
"<text>Auto gamelist.
Mantener fuera del alcance de los niños... ;)</text>"
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
"<text>Elenco automatico dei giochi.
Tenere fuori dalla portata dei bambini... ;)</text>"
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
"<text>オートゲームリストです。
お子様の手の届かないところに保管してください... ;)</text>"
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
"<text>Auto gamelist.
Buiten het bereik van kinderen houden... ;)</text>"
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
"<text>Auto gamelist.
Przechowywać w miejscu niedostępnym dla dzieci... ;)</text>"
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
"<text>Lista automática de jogos.
Manter fora do alcance das crianças... ;)</text>"
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
"<text>Автоматический игровой список.
Хранить в недоступном для детей месте... ;)</text>"
</text>


<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Gals Panic S3 (Arcade, 2002)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>Gals Panic S3 mixes arcade puzzle gameplay, reflexes and light erotic content, with the player gradually revealing female illustrations by claiming areas of the screen without being hit. The larger the risk, the more space is uncovered, giving the game a tense and addictive rhythm typical of early 2000s Japanese arcades.
Fun fact: The Gals Panic series helped popularize adult Qix-like games in Japan and became one of Kaneko’s best-known arcade licenses.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Gals Panic S3 mélange puzzle arcade, réflexes et contenu érotique léger dans un gameplay où le joueur dévoile progressivement des illustrations féminines en capturant des zones de l’écran sans se faire toucher. Plus le risque pris est élevé, plus les portions découvertes sont importantes, donnant au jeu un rythme tendu et addictif.
Fun fact : La série Gals Panic a popularisé les Qix-like adultes au Japon et fait partie des licences arcade les plus connues de Kaneko.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Gals Panic S3 mezcla puzle arcade, reflejos y contenido erótico ligero en una mecánica donde el jugador revela poco a poco ilustraciones femeninas capturando zonas de la pantalla sin ser golpeado. Cuanto mayor es el riesgo, más espacio se descubre, creando un ritmo tenso y adictivo.
Dato curioso: La serie Gals Panic popularizó los Qix-like adultos en Japón y es una de las licencias arcade más conocidas de Kaneko.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Gals Panic S3 unisce puzzle arcade, riflessi e contenuti erotici leggeri in un gameplay in cui il giocatore scopre gradualmente illustrazioni femminili conquistando zone dello schermo senza farsi colpire. Più alto è il rischio, maggiore è l’area rivelata, con un ritmo teso e coinvolgente.
Curiosità: La serie Gals Panic rese popolari i Qix-like per adulti in Giappone ed è tra le licenze arcade più note di Kaneko.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Gals Panic S3 verbindet Arcade-Puzzle, schnelle Reaktionen und leichte erotische Inhalte, während der Spieler nach und nach weibliche Illustrationen freilegt, indem er Bildschirmbereiche erobert, ohne getroffen zu werden. Je größer das Risiko, desto mehr Fläche wird sichtbar, was für ein angespanntes Tempo sorgt.
Interessante Tatsache: Die Gals Panic-Reihe machte erwachsene Qix-ähnliche Spiele in Japan populär und zählt zu Kanekos bekanntesten Arcade-Lizenzen.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Gals Panic S3 mistura puzzle arcade, reflexos e conteúdo erótico leve num sistema em que o jogador revela gradualmente ilustrações femininas ao capturar áreas do ecrã sem ser atingido. Quanto maior o risco, maior a parte revelada, criando um ritmo tenso e viciante.
Curiosidade: A série Gals Panic popularizou os Qix-like adultos no Japão e tornou-se uma das licenças arcade mais conhecidas da Kaneko.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>

