<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>Auto gamelist. They are basically mahjong games and variants of this classic Chines board game.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Liste de jeux automatique. Il s'agit essentiellement de jeux de mahjong et de variantes de ce jeu de société chinois classique.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Auto-Gameliste. Sie sind im Grunde Mahjong-Spiele und Varianten dieses klassischen chinesischen Brettspiels.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Auto gamelist. Básicamente son juegos de mahjong y variantes de este clásico juego de mesa chino.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Elenco automatico dei giochi. Si tratta essenzialmente di giochi di mahjong e di varianti di questo classico gioco da tavolo cinese.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>自動ゲームリスト。これらは基本的に麻雀ゲームと、この古典的な中国のボードゲームの亜種である。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>Auto gamelist. Het zijn mahjongspellen en varianten van dit klassieke Chinese bordspel.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>Auto gamelist. Są to w zasadzie gry typu mahjong i warianty tej klasycznej gry planszowej Chines.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Lista automática de jogos. São basicamente jogos de mahjong e variantes deste clássico jogo de tabuleiro chinês.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>Автоматический список игр. В основном это игры маджонг и варианты этой классической китайской настольной игры.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>

