<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>List of automatic games. An educational video game provides players with learning or training value. Very popular with parents who still hope to do something with their offspring.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Liste de jeux automatique. Un jeu vidéo éducatif offre aux joueurs une valeur d'apprentissage ou de formation. Très prisée des parents qui espèrent encore pouvoir faire quelque chose de leurs rejetons.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Liste von automatischen Spielen. Ein Lernvideospiel bietet den Spielern einen Lern- oder Ausbildungswert. Beliebt bei Eltern, die noch hoffen, mit ihren Sprösslingen etwas anfangen zu können.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Lista de juegos automáticos. Un videojuego educativo ofrece a los jugadores un valor de aprendizaje o formación. Muy popular entre los padres que aún esperan hacer algo con sus hijos.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Elenco dei giochi automatici. Un videogioco educativo offre ai giocatori un valore di apprendimento o di formazione. Molto popolare tra i genitori che sperano ancora di fare qualcosa con i propri figli.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>自動ゲーム一覧。教育用ビデオゲームは、プレイヤーに学習やトレーニングの価値を提供するものです。子供と一緒に何かをすることを望む親に非常に人気がある。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>Lijst van automatische spelletjes. Een educatief videospel biedt spelers een leer- of trainingswaarde. Zeer populair bij ouders die nog iets met hun kinderen willen doen.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>Lista gier automatycznych. Edukacyjna gra wideo oferuje graczom wartość edukacyjną lub szkoleniową. Bardzo popularna wśród rodziców, którzy wciąż mają nadzieję, że zrobią coś ze swoimi dziećmi.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Lista de jogos automáticos. Um jogo de vídeo educativo oferece aos jogadores um valor de aprendizagem ou formação. Muito popular entre pais que ainda esperam fazer algo com os seus filhos.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>Список автоматических игр. Образовательная видеоигра предлагает игрокам обучающую или тренировочную ценность. Очень популярна среди родителей, которые все еще надеются чем-то занять своих детей.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;ADI (PC, 1992)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>ADI is an educational companion designed to help children learn French, mathematics and other school subjects. With his friendly little alien look, he guides exercises, encourages progress and turns revision into an interactive journey, in a style typical of family educational software from the 1990s.
Fun fact: ADI left a strong mark on a whole generation in France thanks to its school software, which was everywhere on family computers in the 1990s.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>ADI est un compagnon éducatif conçu pour accompagner les enfants dans l’apprentissage du français, des mathématiques et d’autres matières scolaires. Avec son style de petit extraterrestre sympathique, il guide les exercices, encourage les progrès et transforme les révisions en parcours interactif, dans une approche typique du logiciel ludo-éducatif familial des années 90.
Fun fact : ADI a marqué toute une génération en France grâce à ses logiciels scolaires omniprésents sur les ordinateurs familiaux des années 90.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>ADI es un compañero educativo creado para ayudar a los niños a aprender francés, matemáticas y otras materias escolares. Con su aspecto de pequeño extraterrestre simpático, guía los ejercicios, anima el progreso y convierte el repaso en un recorrido interactivo típico del software educativo familiar de los años 90.
Dato curioso: ADI marcó a toda una generación en Francia gracias a sus programas escolares, muy presentes en los ordenadores familiares de los años 90.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>ADI è un compagno educativo pensato per aiutare i bambini nello studio del francese, della matematica e di altre materie scolastiche. Con il suo aspetto da piccolo extraterrestre simpatico, guida gli esercizi, incoraggia i progressi e trasforma il ripasso in un percorso interattivo tipico dei software didattici familiari degli anni 90.
Curiosità: ADI ha segnato un’intera generazione in Francia grazie ai suoi programmi scolastici, diffusissimi sui computer di casa negli anni 90.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>ADI ist ein Lernbegleiter, der Kindern beim Üben von Französisch, Mathematik und anderen Schulfächern hilft. Mit seinem freundlichen kleinen Alien-Look führt er durch Aufgaben, motiviert zu Fortschritten und verwandelt Wiederholung in eine interaktive Reise, typisch für Lernsoftware der 1990er Jahre.
Interessante Tatsache: ADI prägte in Frankreich eine ganze Generation, weil seine Schulprogramme auf Familiencomputern der 1990er Jahre allgegenwärtig waren.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>ADI é um companheiro educativo criado para ajudar as crianças a aprender francês, matemática e outras matérias escolares. Com o seu visual de pequeno extraterrestre simpático, orienta os exercícios, incentiva o progresso e transforma a revisão num percurso interativo típico dos softwares educativos familiares dos anos 90.
Curiosidade: ADI marcou toda uma geração em França graças aos seus programas escolares, muito presentes nos computadores familiares dos anos 90.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>

