<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>Bomberman is a video game series centered on characters who use bombs to fight their way through mazes. Gameplay focuses on destroying blocks to open paths and defeat opponents. The series has evolved through various versions, introducing new game modes and characters while retaining the central concept of bombs.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Bomberman est une série de jeux vidéo centrée sur des personnages qui utilisent des bombes pour se battre dans des labyrinthes. Le gameplay met l'accent sur la destruction de blocs pour ouvrir des chemins et vaincre les adversaires. La série a évolué avec différentes versions, introduisant de nouveaux modes de jeu et des personnages tout en conservant le concept central des bombes.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Bomberman es una serie de videojuegos centrada en personajes que usan bombas para abrirse camino y luchar en laberintos. La jugabilidad se basa en destruir bloques para crear rutas y derrotar adversarios. La serie ha evolucionado con distintas versiones, nuevos modos de juego y personajes, manteniendo siempre el concepto central de las bombas.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Bomberman è una serie di videogiochi incentrata su personaggi che usano bombe per combattere e farsi strada nei labirinti. Il gameplay si basa sulla distruzione dei blocchi per aprire passaggi e sconfiggere gli avversari. La serie si è evoluta con varie versioni, nuovi personaggi e modalità, conservando il concetto centrale delle bombe.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Bomberman ist eine Videospielreihe über Figuren, die Bomben nutzen, um sich durch Labyrinthe zu kämpfen. Das Spielprinzip konzentriert sich darauf, Blöcke zu zerstören, Wege zu öffnen und Gegner zu besiegen. Die Reihe entwickelte sich über viele Versionen weiter, führte neue Modi und Figuren ein und behielt das zentrale Bombenkonzept bei.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Bomberman é uma série de jogos eletrônicos centrada em personagens que usam bombas para lutar e avançar por labirintos. A jogabilidade se concentra em destruir blocos para abrir caminhos e derrotar adversários. A série evoluiu por várias versões, com novos modos e personagens, mantendo sempre o conceito central das bombas.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Bomberman (MSX, 1983)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>Bomberman stands upright, his clean suit, glossy helmet and focused stare giving him a calm presence as he holds a bomb with a sparking fuse, ready to throw it through a trapped maze where timing and placement matter as much as speed.
Fun fact: In Europe, the early computer version was released as Eric and the Floaters, giving the original Bomberman an unusual human name that never became standard.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Bomberman se tient droit, combinaison impeccable, casque brillant et regard déterminé, tenant une bombe dont la mèche grésille entre ses doigts, prêt à la lancer dans un dédale piégé où le timing et le placement comptent autant que la vitesse.
Fun fact : En Europe, une ancienne version micro-ordinateur est sortie sous le titre Eric and the Floaters, donnant au premier Bomberman un prénom humain qui sera vite oublié.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Bomberman se mantiene erguido, con traje impecable, casco brillante y mirada decidida, sujetando una bomba cuya mecha chispea entre sus dedos, listo para lanzarla en un laberinto lleno de trampas donde el tiempo y la posición son esenciales.
Dato curioso: En Europa, una antigua versión para microordenadores se lanzó como Eric and the Floaters, dando al primer Bomberman un nombre humano que nunca se volvió habitual.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Bomberman resta dritto, con tuta impeccabile, casco lucido e sguardo deciso, tenendo una bomba dalla miccia accesa tra le dita, pronto a lanciarla in un labirinto pieno di trappole dove contano tempismo e posizione.
Curiosità: In Europa, una vecchia versione per microcomputer uscì come Eric and the Floaters, dando al primo Bomberman un nome umano mai diventato standard.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Bomberman steht aufrecht da, mit sauberem Anzug, glänzendem Helm und entschlossenem Blick, während er eine Bombe mit zischender Lunte hält, bereit, sie in ein gefährliches Labyrinth zu werfen, in dem Timing und Position zählen.
Interessante Tatsache: In Europa erschien eine frühe Heimcomputerfassung als Eric and the Floaters und gab dem ersten Bomberman einen menschlichen Namen, der nie zum Standard wurde.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Bomberman fica em pé, com roupa impecável, capacete brilhante e olhar determinado, segurando uma bomba com o pavio aceso entre os dedos, pronto para lançá-la em um labirinto cheio de armadilhas onde tempo e posição são decisivos.
Curiosidade: Na Europa, uma antiga versão para microcomputadores saiu como Eric and the Floaters, dando ao primeiro Bomberman um nome humano que nunca virou padrão.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
