<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>The Commodore 64 is a personal computer designed by Commodore Business Machines Inc. under the leadership of Jack Tramiel. It was the first machine to sell several million copies (from 17 to 25 million according to estimates), and it remains the best-selling personal computer model to date, according to the Guinness Book of Records.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Le Commodore 64 est un ordinateur personnel conçu par Commodore Business Machines Inc. sous l'égide de Jack Tramiel. Il fut la première machine vendue à plusieurs millions d'exemplaires (de 17 à 25 millions selon les estimations), et il reste le modèle d'ordinateur personnel le plus vendu à ce jour, selon le Livre Guinness des records.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Der Commodore 64 ist ein Personal Computer, der von Commodore Business Machines Inc. unter der Leitung von Jack Tramiel entwickelt wurde. Er war das erste Gerät, von dem mehrere Millionen Exemplare verkauft wurden (je nach Schätzung zwischen 17 und 25 Millionen), und ist laut Guinness-Buch der Rekorde bis heute das meistverkaufte Modell eines Personalcomputers.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>El Commodore 64 es un ordenador personal diseñado por Commodore Business Machines Inc. bajo la dirección de Jack Tramiel. Fue la primera máquina en vender varios millones de unidades (se calcula que entre 17 y 25 millones), y sigue siendo el modelo de ordenador personal más vendido hasta la fecha, según el Libro Guinness de los Récords.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Il Commodore 64 è un personal computer progettato da Commodore Business Machines Inc. sotto la guida di Jack Tramiel. È stato il primo computer a vendere diversi milioni di unità (si stima tra i 17 e i 25 milioni) e, secondo il Guinness dei primati, è tuttora il personal computer più venduto.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>コモドール64は、コモドール・ビジネス・マシーンズ社がジャック・トラミエルの主導で設計したパーソナルコンピュータである。数百万台（推定1700～2500万台）を販売した最初のマシンであり、ギネスブックによれば、現在でも最も売れたパーソナルコンピュータである。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>De Commodore 64 is een personal computer ontworpen door Commodore Business Machines Inc. onder leiding van Jack Tramiel. Het was de eerste machine die enkele miljoenen exemplaren verkocht (naar schatting 17 tot 25 miljoen), en blijft de best verkochte personal computer tot op heden, volgens het Guinness Book of World Records.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>Commodore 64 to komputer osobisty zaprojektowany przez Commodore Business Machines Inc. pod kierownictwem Jacka Tramiela. Była to pierwsza maszyna, która sprzedała się w ilości kilku milionów sztuk (szacunkowo od 17 do 25 milionów) i do dziś pozostaje najlepiej sprzedającym się komputerem osobistym, według Księgi Rekordów Guinnessa.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>O Commodore 64 é um computador pessoal concebido pela Commodore Business Machines Inc., sob a liderança de Jack Tramiel. Foi a primeira máquina a vender vários milhões de unidades (estimado em 17 a 25 milhões), e continua a ser o computador pessoal mais vendido até à data, de acordo com o Livro dos Recordes do Guinness.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>Commodore 64 - это персональный компьютер, разработанный компанией Commodore Business Machines Inc. под руководством Джека Трамиэля. Он стал первым компьютером, проданным тиражом в несколько миллионов единиц (по оценкам, от 17 до 25 миллионов), и до сих пор остается самым продаваемым персональным компьютером, согласно Книге рекордов Гиннесса.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Bruce Lee (1984)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>Bruce Lee is an iconic video game adaptation of the famous martial artist. On C64, the character benefits from fluid animation and precise controls that strengthen his presence on screen. The great popularity of the game and character inspired excellent homebrews such as Bruce Lee 2 and Bruce Lee 3: Return of Fury.
Fun fact: The game lets a second player control the green Yamo, adding a direct rivalry that was quite unusual at the time.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Bruce Lee est une adaptation vidéoludique emblématique du célèbre artiste martial. Sur C64, le personnage bénéficie d’une animation fluide et d’un contrôle précis qui renforcent son impact à l’écran. La grande popularité du jeu et du personnage a inspiré d’excellents homebrews comme Bruce Lee 2 et Bruce Lee 3: Return of Fury.
Fun fact : Le jeu permet à un deuxième joueur de contrôler le Yamo vert, ajoutant une rivalité directe assez rare pour l’époque.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Bruce Lee es una adaptación videolúdica emblemática del célebre artista marcial. En C64, el personaje destaca por una animación fluida y un control preciso que refuerzan su impacto en pantalla. La gran popularidad del juego y del personaje inspiró excelentes homebrews como Bruce Lee 2 y Bruce Lee 3: Return of Fury.
Dato curioso: El juego permite que un segundo jugador controle al Yamo verde, añadiendo una rivalidad directa bastante rara para la época.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Bruce Lee è un adattamento videoludico emblematico del celebre artista marziale. Su C64, il personaggio si distingue per un’animazione fluida e un controllo preciso che ne rafforzano l’impatto a schermo. La grande popolarità del gioco e del personaggio ha ispirato eccellenti homebrew come Bruce Lee 2 e Bruce Lee 3: Return of Fury.
Curiosità: Il gioco permette a un secondo giocatore di controllare lo Yamo verde, aggiungendo una rivalità diretta piuttosto rara per l’epoca.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Bruce Lee ist eine bekannte Videospieladaption des berühmten Kampfkünstlers. Auf dem C64 überzeugt die Figur durch flüssige Animation und präzise Steuerung, die ihre Wirkung auf dem Bildschirm verstärken. Die große Beliebtheit des Spiels und der Figur inspirierte hervorragende Homebrews wie Bruce Lee 2 und Bruce Lee 3: Return of Fury.
Interessante Tatsache: Das Spiel erlaubt einem zweiten Spieler, den grünen Yamo zu steuern, was für die damalige Zeit eine direkte Rivalität ungewöhnlich machte.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Bruce Lee é uma adaptação videolúdica emblemática do célebre artista marcial. No C64, a personagem destaca-se pela animação fluida e pelo controlo preciso, reforçando o seu impacto no ecrã. A grande popularidade do jogo e da personagem inspirou excelentes homebrews como Bruce Lee 2 e Bruce Lee 3: Return of Fury.
Curiosidade: O jogo permite que um segundo jogador controle o Yamo verde, criando uma rivalidade direta bastante rara para a época.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
