<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>The Lynx was a British 8-bit home computer. Several models were available with 48 kB, 96 kB or 128 kB of RAM. It was possible to reach 192 kB with on-board RAM extensions. The machine was quite advanced for its time.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Le Lynx était un ordinateur domestique britannique 8 bits Plusieurs modèles étaient disponibles avec 48 kB, 96 kB ou 128 kB de RAM. Il était possible d'atteindre 192 ko avec des extensions de RAM embarquées. La machine était assez avancée pour l'époque.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Der Lynx war ein britischer 8-Bit-Heimcomputer. Es gab mehrere Modelle mit 48 kB, 96 kB oder 128 kB RAM. Mit Onboard-RAM-Erweiterungen war es möglich, bis zu 192 KB zu erreichen. Der Rechner war für die damalige Zeit recht fortschrittlich.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>El Lynx era un ordenador doméstico británico de 8 bits. Había varios modelos disponibles con 48 kB, 96 kB o 128 kB de RAM. Era posible llegar hasta 192 kB con extensiones de RAM a bordo. La máquina era bastante avanzada para su época.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Il Lynx era un home computer britannico a 8 bit. Erano disponibili diversi modelli con 48 kB, 96 kB o 128 kB di RAM. Era possibile arrivare a 192 kB con estensioni di RAM a bordo. La macchina era piuttosto avanzata per l'epoca.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>Lynxはイギリスの8ビットホームコンピュータで、48kB、96kB、128kBのRAMを搭載したいくつかのモデルが用意されていた。オンボードのRAM拡張で192kBまで可能だった。このマシンは当時としてはかなり先進的なものだった。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>De Lynx was een Britse 8-bit thuiscomputer. Er waren verschillende modellen beschikbaar met 48 kB, 96 kB of 128 kB RAM. Het was mogelijk om tot 192 kB te gaan met on-board RAM uitbreidingen. De machine was vrij geavanceerd voor zijn tijd.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>Lynx był brytyjskim 8-bitowym komputerem domowym. Kilka modeli było dostępnych z 48 kB, 96 kB lub 128 kB pamięci RAM. Możliwe było zwiększenie do 192 kB dzięki pokładowym rozszerzeniom pamięci RAM. Maszyna była dość zaawansowana jak na swoje czasy.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>O lince era um computador doméstico britânico de 8 bits. Vários modelos estavam disponíveis com 48 kB, 96 kB ou 128 kB de RAM. Era possível ir até 192 kB com extensões de RAM a bordo. A máquina era bastante avançada para o seu tempo.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>Lynx - это британский 8-битный домашний компьютер. Выпускалось несколько моделей с 48, 96 или 128 кБ оперативной памяти. С помощью встроенных расширений ОЗУ можно было увеличить до 192 кБ. Для своего времени эта машина была довольно продвинутой.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
