<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>CannonBall is an souped up game engine for the OutRun arcade game. The original 68000 and Z80 assembler code has been rewritten in C++.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>CannonBall est un moteur de jeu amélioré pour le jeu d'arcade OutRun. Le code assembleur 68000 et Z80 original a été réécrit en C++.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>CannonBall ist eine aufgemotzte Spiel-Engine für das OutRun Arcade-Spiel. Der ursprüngliche 68000- und Z80-Assembler-Code wurde in C++ umgeschrieben.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>CannonBall es un motor de juego mejorado para el juego arcade OutRun. El código ensamblador original de 68000 y Z80 ha sido reescrito en C++.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>CannonBall è un motore di gioco potenziato per il gioco arcade OutRun. Il codice assembler originale per 68000 e Z80 è stato riscritto in C++.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>CannonBallは、OutRunアーケードゲーム用のスープアップされたゲームエンジンです。オリジナルの68000とZ80のアセンブラコードは、C++で書き直されています。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>CannonBall is een opgevoerde game engine voor het OutRun arcade spel. De originele 68000 en Z80 assembler code is herschreven in C++.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>CannonBall jest ulepszonym silnikiem gry dla gry zręcznościowej OutRun. Oryginalny kod z asemblera 68000 i Z80 został przepisany w C++.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>CannonBall é um motor de jogo com sopa para o jogo arcade OutRun. O código de montagem original 68000 e Z80 foi reescrito em C++.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>CannonBall - это усовершенствованный игровой движок для аркадной игры OutRun. Оригинальный код на ассемблере 68000 и Z80 был переписан на C++.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
