<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
"<text>Capcom Co, Ltd (株式会社カプコン) is a Japanese company, founded in 1983, that develops and publishes video games worldwide through subsidiaries and branches located in North America, Europe, as well as East Asia.

The company is known as the creator of several famous video game franchises that have sold millions of copies, including the Monster Hunter, Resident Evil, Street Fighter, and Megaman series.</text>"
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
"<text>Capcom Co., Ltd. (株式会社カプコン) est une société japonaise, fondée en 1983, qui développe et édite des jeux vidéo dans le monde entier, par le biais de filiales et succursales situées en Amérique du Nord, en Europe, ainsi qu'en Asie orientale.

L'entreprise est connue pour être à l'origine de plusieurs franchises de jeux vidéo célèbres dont les épisodes se sont vendus à plusieurs millions d'exemplaires, notamment pour les séries Monster Hunter, Resident Evil, Street Fighter, ou encore Megaman.</text>"
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
"<text>Capcom Co, Ltd (株式会社カプコン) ist ein japanisches Unternehmen, das 1983 gegründet wurde und über Tochtergesellschaften und Niederlassungen in Nordamerika, Europa sowie Ostasien weltweit Videospiele entwickelt und veröffentlicht.

Das Unternehmen ist bekannt dafür, dass es hinter mehreren berühmten Videospiel-Franchises steht, deren Episoden sich millionenfach verkauft haben, darunter die Serien Monster Hunter, Resident Evil, Street Fighter und Megaman.</text>"
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
"<text>Capcom Co, Ltd (株式会社カプコン) es una empresa japonesa, fundada en 1983, que desarrolla y publica videojuegos en todo el mundo a través de filiales y sucursales situadas en Norteamérica, Europa y Asia Oriental.

La empresa es conocida por ser la creadora de varias famosas franquicias de videojuegos que han vendido millones de copias, como las series Monster Hunter, Resident Evil, Street Fighter y Megaman.</text>"
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
"<text>Capcom Co, Ltd (株式会社カプコン) è una società giapponese, fondata nel 1983, che sviluppa e pubblica videogiochi in tutto il mondo attraverso filiali e succursali situate in Nord America, Europa e Asia orientale.

L'azienda è nota per essere la creatrice di numerosi e famosi franchise di videogiochi che hanno venduto milioni di copie, tra cui le serie Monster Hunter, Resident Evil, Street Fighter e Megaman.</text>"
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
"<text>株式会社カプコンは、1983年に設立された日本の企業であり、北米、ヨーロッパ、東アジアにある子会社や支店を通じて、世界中でビデオゲームを開発し、パブリッシングしています。

モンスターハンター」「バイオハザード」「ストリートファイター」「ロックマン」シリーズなど、数百万本を売り上げた有名なビデオゲームフランチャイズのクリエイターとして知られています。</text>"
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
"<text>Capcom Co, Ltd (株式会社カプコン) is een Japanse onderneming, opgericht in 1983, die wereldwijd videospelletjes ontwikkelt en uitgeeft via dochterondernemingen en filialen in Noord-Amerika, Europa en Oost-Azië.

Het bedrijf staat bekend als de maker van verschillende beroemde videospelfranchises waarvan miljoenen exemplaren zijn verkocht, waaronder de series Monster Hunter, Resident Evil, Street Fighter en Megaman.</text>"
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
"<text>Capcom Co, Ltd (株式会社カプコン) to japońska firma, założona w 1983 roku, która rozwija i wydaje gry wideo na całym świecie poprzez filie i oddziały zlokalizowane w Ameryce Północnej, Europie, a także Azji Wschodniej.

Firma jest znana jako twórca kilku słynnych franczyz gier wideo, które sprzedały się w milionach egzemplarzy, w tym serii Monster Hunter, Resident Evil, Street Fighter i Megaman.</text>"
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
"<text>Capcom Co, Ltd (株式会社カプコン) é uma empresa japonesa, fundada em 1983, que desenvolve e publica jogos de vídeo a nível mundial através de filiais e sucursais localizadas na América do Norte, Europa, bem como na Ásia Oriental.

A empresa é conhecida como a criadora de várias famosas franquias de videojogos que venderam milhões de cópias, incluindo a série Monster Hunter, Resident Evil, Street Fighter, e Megaman.</text>"
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
"<text>Capcom Co, Ltd (株式会社カプコン) - японская компания, основанная в 1983 году, которая разрабатывает и издает видеоигры по всему миру через дочерние компании и филиалы, расположенные в Северной Америке, Европе, а также Восточной Азии.

Компания известна как создатель нескольких известных франшиз видеоигр, проданных миллионными тиражами, включая серии Monster Hunter, Resident Evil, Street Fighter и Megaman.</text>"
</text>


<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Strider (1989)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>Strider Hiryu is a futuristic ninja sent to fight Grandmaster Meio in a world mixing dictatorship, science fiction and monumental settings. Agile, fast and armed with his Cypher, he crosses stages with spectacular mobility, using climbs, slides, circular attacks and battles against mechanical or mutant enemies.
Fun fact: Strider began as a shared project between a manga, Capcom's arcade game and the NES version, all built around the same hero.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Strider Hiryu est un ninja futuriste envoyé combattre Grandmaster Meio dans un monde mêlant dictature, science-fiction et décors monumentaux. Agile, rapide et armé de son Cypher, il traverse les niveaux avec une mobilité spectaculaire, entre escalades, glissades, attaques circulaires et affrontements contre des ennemis mécaniques ou mutants.
Fun fact : Strider partage ses origines entre le manga, le jeu arcade Capcom et la version NES, tous conçus comme un projet commun autour du même héros.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Strider Hiryu es un ninja futurista enviado a combatir a Grandmaster Meio en un mundo que mezcla dictadura, ciencia ficción y escenarios monumentales. Ágil, veloz y armado con su Cypher, recorre los niveles con una movilidad espectacular, entre escaladas, deslizamientos, ataques circulares y combates contra enemigos mecánicos o mutantes.
Dato curioso: Strider nació como un proyecto compartido entre un manga, el arcade de Capcom y la versión de NES, todos centrados en el mismo héroe.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Strider Hiryu è un ninja futuristico inviato a combattere Grandmaster Meio in un mondo che unisce dittatura, fantascienza e scenari monumentali. Agile, veloce e armato del suo Cypher, attraversa i livelli con una mobilità spettacolare, tra arrampicate, scivolate, attacchi circolari e scontri contro nemici meccanici o mutanti.
Curiosità: Strider nacque come progetto condiviso tra un manga, l'arcade Capcom e la versione NES, tutti costruiti attorno allo stesso eroe.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Strider Hiryu ist ein futuristischer Ninja, der Grandmaster Meio in einer Welt aus Diktatur, Science-Fiction und monumentalen Schauplätzen bekämpft. Wendig, schnell und mit seinem Cypher bewaffnet, bewegt er sich spektakulär durch die Level, mit Klettern, Rutschen, Rundumschlägen und Kämpfen gegen mechanische oder mutierte Feinde.
Interessante Tatsache: Strider entstand als gemeinsames Projekt aus Manga, Capcoms Arcade-Spiel und der NES-Version, alle rund um denselben Helden.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Strider Hiryu é um ninja futurista enviado para enfrentar Grandmaster Meio num mundo que mistura ditadura, ficção científica e cenários monumentais. Ágil, rápido e armado com o seu Cypher, atravessa as fases com mobilidade espetacular, entre escaladas, deslizes, ataques circulares e combates contra inimigos mecânicos ou mutantes.
Curiosidade: Strider nasceu como um projeto partilhado entre um manga, o arcade da Capcom e a versão NES, todos centrados no mesmo herói.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
