<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>Cave Co, Ltd (株式会社ケイブ?), an acronym for Computer Art Visual Entertainment, is a Japanese company that creates arcade, console and mobile video games.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Cave Co., Ltd. (株式会社ケイブ?), acronyme de Computer Art Visual Entertainment, est une société japonaise de création de jeux vidéo en arcade, sur console et sur téléphone portable.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Cave Co., Ltd. (株式会社ケイブ?), Abkürzung für Computer Art Visual Entertainment, ist ein japanisches Unternehmen, das Videospiele für Arcade, Konsole und Mobiltelefon entwickelt.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Cave Co, Ltd (株式会社ケイブ?), acrónimo de Computer Art Visual Entertainment, es una empresa japonesa creadora de videojuegos arcade, para consolas y móviles.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Cave Co, Ltd (株式会社ケイブ?), acronimo di Computer Art Visual Entertainment, è un'azienda giapponese che crea videogiochi arcade, per console e per cellulari.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>株式会社ケイブ（Cave Co, Ltd）は、Computer Art Visual Entertainmentの頭文字をとったもので、アーケードゲーム、コンソールゲーム、モバイルゲームを制作する日本の企業である。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>Cave Co, Ltd (株式会社ケイブ?), een acroniem voor Computer Art Visual Entertainment, is een Japans bedrijf dat arcade-, console- en mobiele videospelletjes maakt.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>Cave Co, Ltd (株式会社ケイブ?), czyli skrót od Computer Art Visual Entertainment, to japońska firma zajmująca się tworzeniem gier wideo na zręcznościówki, konsole i urządzenia mobilne.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Cave Co, Ltd (株式会社ケイブ?), um acrónimo de Computer Art Visual Entertainment, é uma empresa japonesa que cria arcade, consola e videojogos móveis.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>Cave Co, Ltd (株式会社ケイブ?), аббревиатура от Computer Art Visual Entertainment, - японская компания, создающая аркадные, консольные и мобильные видеоигры.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
