<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>Chihiro is an arcade system for arcade terminals, created by Sega. The system is based on the architecture of the Xbox home console from Microsoft, which is itself built on a PC architecture.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Le Chihiro est un système d'arcade destiné aux bornes d'arcade, créé par Sega. Le système est basé sur l'architecture de la console de salon Xbox de Microsoft celle-ci étant elle-même construite sur une architecture PC.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Chihiro ist ein Arcade-System für Spielhallen, das von Sega entwickelt wurde. Das System basiert auf der Architektur der Xbox-Heimkonsole von Microsoft, die wiederum auf einer PC-Architektur basiert.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Chihiro es un sistema arcade para terminales recreativas, creado por Sega. El sistema se basa en la arquitectura de la consola doméstica Xbox de Microsoft, que a su vez está construida sobre una arquitectura de PC.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Chihiro è un sistema arcade per terminali arcade, creato da Sega. Il sistema è basato sull'architettura della console domestica Microsoft Xbox, a sua volta costruita su un'architettura PC.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>ちひろは、セガが制作したアーケード端末用のシステムである。このシステムは、マイクロソフトの家庭用ゲーム機「Xbox」のアーキテクチャをベースにしており、それ自体はPCのアーキテクチャをベースに作られている。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>Chihiro is een systeem voor arcade-terminals, gemaakt door Sega. Het systeem is gebaseerd op de architectuur van de Microsoft Xbox thuisconsole, die zelf is gebouwd op een PC-architectuur.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>Chihiro to system dla terminali arcade, stworzony przez firmę Sega. System oparty jest na architekturze konsoli domowej Microsoft Xbox, która sama jest zbudowana na architekturze PC.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Chihiro é um sistema de arcada para terminais de arcada, criado pela Sega. O sistema é baseado na arquitectura da consola doméstica Microsoft Xbox, que por sua vez é construída sobre uma arquitectura de PC.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>Chihiro - это система для аркадных терминалов, созданная компанией Sega. Система основана на архитектуре домашней консоли Microsoft Xbox, которая сама построена на архитектуре ПК.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
