<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>The CP System III (Capcom Play System 3), more commonly known as CPS-3, is an arcade system that was introduced by Capcom in 1996 with the game Red Earth, as a successor to the CP System II arcade system. It is the latest arcade system designed and manufactured by Capcom.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Le CP System III (Capcom Play System 3), plus communément appelé CPS-3, est un système d'arcade qui a été introduit par Capcom en 1996 avec le jeu Red Earth, afin de succéder au système d'arcade CP System II. C'est le dernier système d'arcade en date conçu et fabriqué par Capcom.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Das CP System III (Capcom Play System 3), allgemein bekannt als CPS-3, ist ein Arcade-System, das 1996 von Capcom mit dem Spiel Red Earth als Nachfolger des Arcade-Systems CP System II eingeführt wurde. Es ist das neueste Arcade-System, das von Capcom entwickelt und hergestellt wurde.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>El CP System III (Capcom Play System 3), más comúnmente conocido como CPS-3, es un sistema arcade que fue introducido por Capcom en 1996 con el juego Red Earth, como sucesor del sistema arcade CP System II. Es el último sistema arcade diseñado y fabricado por Capcom.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Il CP System III (Capcom Play System 3), più comunemente noto come CPS-3, è un sistema arcade introdotto da Capcom nel 1996 con il gioco Red Earth, come successore del sistema arcade CP System II. È l'ultimo sistema arcade progettato e prodotto da Capcom.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>CPシステムIII（カプコンプレイシステム3）、通称CPS-3は、1996年にカプコンがCPシステムIIアーケードシステムの後継機として、ゲーム『レッドアース』で発表したアーケードシステムである。カプコンが設計・製造した最新のアーケードシステムである。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>Het CP System III (Capcom Play System 3), beter bekend als CPS-3, is een arcadesysteem dat in 1996 door Capcom werd geïntroduceerd met het spel Red Earth, als opvolger van het CP System II arcadesysteem. Het is het laatste door Capcom ontworpen en geproduceerde arcadesysteem.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>CP System III (Capcom Play System 3), bardziej znany jako CPS-3, to system arcade, który został wprowadzony przez Capcom w 1996 roku wraz z grą Red Earth, jako następca systemu arcade CP System II. Jest to ostatni system arcade zaprojektowany i wyprodukowany przez Capcom.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>O Sistema CP III (Capcom Play System 3), mais conhecido como CPS-3, é um sistema arcade que foi introduzido pela Capcom em 1996 com o jogo Red Earth, como um sucessor do sistema arcade CP System II. É o mais recente sistema de arcada concebido e fabricado pela Capcom.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>CP System III (Capcom Play System 3), более известная как CPS-3, - это аркадная система, которая была представлена компанией Capcom в 1996 году с игрой Red Earth, как преемник аркадной системы CP System II. Это последняя аркадная система, разработанная и произведенная компанией Capcom.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
	<text>&#160;&#160;JoJo’s Venture (1998)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
	<text>Jotaro Kujo is the central hero of Stardust Crusaders, recognizable by his dark uniform, cap, and cold attitude. In JoJo’s Venture, he fights with Star Platinum, an exceptionally powerful Stand able to strike at very high speed and support a direct, precise, and brutal fighting style.
Fun fact: The game helped introduce JoJo’s Bizarre Adventure to Western audiences through the arcade scene.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
	<text>Jotaro Kujo est le héros central de Stardust Crusaders, reconnaissable à son uniforme sombre, sa casquette et son attitude froide. Dans JoJo’s Venture, il combat avec Star Platinum, un Stand d’une puissance exceptionnelle, capable de frapper à très grande vitesse et de soutenir un style de combat direct, précis et brutal.
Fun fact : Le jeu a contribué à faire découvrir JoJo’s Bizarre Adventure au public occidental via l’arcade.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
	<text>Jotaro Kujo es el protagonista central de Stardust Crusaders, reconocible por su uniforme oscuro, su gorra y su actitud fría. En JoJo’s Venture, combate con Star Platinum, un Stand de gran poder capaz de golpear a gran velocidad y sostener un estilo de lucha directo, preciso y brutal.
Dato curioso: El juego ayudó a dar a conocer JoJo’s Bizarre Adventure al público occidental a través de las salas arcade.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
	<text>Jotaro Kujo è il protagonista di Stardust Crusaders, riconoscibile per la sua uniforme scura, il cappello e il suo atteggiamento freddo. In JoJo’s Venture combatte con Star Platinum, uno Stand estremamente potente capace di colpire ad altissima velocità e sostenere uno stile di combattimento diretto, preciso e brutale.
Curiosità: Il gioco ha contribuito a far conoscere JoJo’s Bizarre Adventure al pubblico occidentale attraverso le sale giochi.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
	<text>Jotaro Kujo ist der zentrale Held von Stardust Crusaders, erkennbar an seiner dunklen Uniform, seiner Mütze und seiner kühlen Art. In JoJo’s Venture kämpft er mit Star Platinum, einem extrem mächtigen Stand, der mit sehr hoher Geschwindigkeit zuschlagen kann und einen direkten, präzisen und brutalen Kampfstil unterstützt.
Interessante Tatsache: Das Spiel trug dazu bei, JoJo’s Bizarre Adventure über die Arcade-Szene einem westlichen Publikum bekannt zu machen.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
	<text>Jotaro Kujo é o protagonista central de Stardust Crusaders, reconhecido por seu uniforme escuro, seu boné e sua atitude fria. Em JoJo’s Venture, ele luta com Star Platinum, um Stand extremamente poderoso capaz de atacar em altíssima velocidade e sustentar um estilo de combate direto, preciso e brutal.
Curiosidade: O jogo ajudou a apresentar JoJo’s Bizarre Adventure ao público ocidental através dos arcades.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
