<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>DevilutionX is a source port of Diablo and Hellfire that strives to make it simple to run the game while providing engine improvements, bugfixes, and some optional quality features.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>DevilutionX est un portage source de Diablo et Hellfire qui s'efforce de simplifier l'exécution du jeu tout en apportant des améliorations au moteur, des corrections de bugs et quelques fonctionnalités optionnelles de qualité.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>DevilutionX ist eine Quellcode-Portierung von Diablo und Hellfire, die darauf abzielt, die Ausführung des Spiels zu vereinfachen und gleichzeitig Verbesserungen an der Engine, Fehlerbehebungen und einige optionale Qualitätsmerkmale zu bieten.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>DevilutionX es un port fuente de Diablo y Hellfire que se esfuerza por simplificar la ejecución del juego a la vez que proporciona mejoras en el motor, corrección de errores y algunas características de calidad opcionales.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>DevilutionX è un porting sorgente di Diablo e Hellfire che si sforza di rendere semplice l'esecuzione del gioco, fornendo al contempo miglioramenti al motore, correzioni di bug e alcune caratteristiche opzionali di qualità.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>DevilutionXは、DiabloとHellfireのソース移植で、エンジンの改善、バグフィックス、いくつかのオプションの品質機能を提供しながら、ゲームを実行するためにシンプルに努めています。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>DevilutionX is een source port van Diablo en Hellfire die ernaar streeft om het eenvoudig te maken om het spel te draaien en tegelijkertijd engine verbeteringen, bugfixes en enkele optionele kwaliteitsfuncties te bieden.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>DevilutionX jest portem źródłowym Diablo i Hellfire, który stara się ułatwić uruchamianie gry, zapewniając jednocześnie ulepszenia silnika, poprawki błędów i kilka opcjonalnych funkcji jakościowych.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>DevilutionX é uma porta de origem de Diablo e Hellfire que se esforça por tornar simples o funcionamento do jogo ao mesmo tempo que fornece melhorias no motor, correcções de bugs, e algumas características opcionais de qualidade.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>DevilutionX - это исходный порт Diablo и Hellfire, который стремится упростить запуск игры, одновременно предоставляя улучшения движка, исправления ошибок и некоторые дополнительные качественные функции.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
