<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>

	<view name="system">

		<!-- Default language (EN) -->
		<text name="system_description" extra="true">
			<text>DICE simulates the earliest dedicated electronic game consoles inspired by the Pong concept. Reproducing very simple systems without cartridges or complex processors, it offers minimalist game variations based on tennis, squash, or hockey. With its immediate gameplay and historical perspective, DICE provides a glimpse into the origins of home video gaming.</text>
		</text>

		<!-- French -->
		<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
			<text>DICE permet de simuler les premières consoles de jeux électroniques dédiées, inspirées du concept de Pong. Reproduisant des systèmes très simples sans cartouches ni processeur complexe, il propose des variantes de jeux minimalistes basées sur le tennis, le squash ou le hockey. Avec son gameplay immédiat et son approche historique, DICE offre un aperçu des origines du jeu vidéo domestique.</text>
		</text>

		<!-- Spanish -->
		<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
			<text>DICE permite simular las primeras consolas electrónicas dedicadas, inspiradas en el concepto de Pong. Reproduciendo sistemas muy simples sin cartuchos ni procesadores complejos, ofrece variantes de juego minimalistas basadas en tenis, squash o hockey. Con su jugabilidad inmediata y su enfoque histórico, DICE ofrece una visión de los orígenes del videojuego doméstico.</text>
		</text>

		<!-- Portuguese -->
		<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
			<text>DICE permite simular os primeiros consoles eletrônicos dedicados, inspirados no conceito de Pong. Reproduzindo sistemas muito simples, sem cartuchos nem processadores complexos, oferece variantes de jogo minimalistas baseadas em tênis, squash ou hóquei. Com sua jogabilidade imediata e abordagem histórica, DICE oferece uma visão das origens dos videogames domésticos.</text>
		</text>

		<!-- German -->
		<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
			<text>DICE simuliert die ersten eigenständigen elektronischen Spielkonsolen, die vom Pong-Konzept inspiriert wurden. Es bildet sehr einfache Systeme ohne Module oder komplexe Prozessoren nach und bietet minimalistische Spielvarianten auf Basis von Tennis, Squash oder Hockey. Mit seinem direkten Gameplay und seinem historischen Ansatz vermittelt DICE einen Einblick in die Ursprünge des Heimvideospiels.</text>
		</text>

		<!-- Italian -->
		<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
			<text>DICE permette di simulare le prime console elettroniche dedicate, ispirate al concetto di Pong. Riproducendo sistemi molto semplici senza cartucce né processori complessi, propone varianti di gioco minimaliste basate su tennis, squash o hockey. Con il suo gameplay immediato e il suo approccio storico, DICE offre uno sguardo alle origini del videogioco domestico.</text>
		</text>

		<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
			<text>&#160;&#160;Pong (1972)&#160;&#160;</text>
		</text>

		<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
			<text>This figurine imagines an original mascot for DICE, featuring a character with a dice-shaped head that echoes the emulator’s name rather than any official figure. It accompanies Pong, a foundational arcade game built on simple electronic logic without a CPU, where two paddles and a ball capture the raw beginnings of video games.</text>
		</text>
		<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
			<text>Cette figurine imagine une mascotte originale pour DICE, avec un personnage à tête de dé représentant le nom de l’émulateur plutôt qu’un héros officiel. Elle accompagne Pong, jeu d’arcade fondateur basé sur une logique électronique sans CPU, où deux raquettes et une balle suffisent à illustrer les débuts les plus bruts du jeu vidéo.</text>
		</text>
		<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
			<text>Esta figura imagina una mascota original para DICE, con un personaje de cabeza de dado que refleja el nombre del emulador más que un personaje oficial. Acompaña a Pong, un juego arcade fundamental basado en lógica electrónica sin CPU, donde dos palas y una pelota representan los inicios más básicos del videojuego.</text>
		</text>
		<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
			<text>Questa figurina immagina una mascotte originale per DICE, con un personaggio dalla testa a forma di dado che richiama il nome dell’emulatore più che un eroe ufficiale. Accompagna Pong, gioco arcade fondamentale basato su logica elettronica senza CPU, dove due racchette e una palla rappresentano gli inizi più essenziali del videogioco.</text>
		</text>
		<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
			<text>Diese Figur stellt ein originales Maskottchen für DICE dar, mit einer Figur mit Würfelkopf, die eher auf den Namen des Emulators als auf eine offizielle Figur anspielt. Sie begleitet Pong, ein grundlegendes Arcade-Spiel auf Basis einfacher Elektronik ohne CPU, bei dem zwei Schläger und ein Ball die rohesten Anfänge des Videospiels darstellen.</text>
		</text>
		<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
			<text>Esta figura imagina uma mascote original para o DICE, com um personagem de cabeça em forma de dado que remete ao nome do emulador e não a um herói oficial. Ela acompanha Pong, um jogo arcade fundamental baseado em lógica eletrônica sem CPU, onde duas raquetes e uma bola representam os primórdios mais simples dos videogames.</text>
		</text>

	</view>
</theme>
