<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>The Dreamcast (ドリームキャスト) is the successor to the Saturn. Ahead of its time, it came to market before its competitors the PS2, Xbox and GameCube. Its name is composed of the words dream and cast. It was the first console to come with a modem as standard, allowing it to support online gaming.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>La Dreamcast (ドリームキャスト) est le successeur de la Saturn. En avance sur son temps, elle se présente sur le marché avant ses concurrentes la PS2, la Xbox  et la GameCube. Son nom est composé des mots dream (rêve) et cast (de broadcast : diffuser). Elle est la première console livrée en standard avec un modem lui permettant un support de jeu en ligne.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Die Dreamcast (ドリームキャスト) ist der Nachfolger des Saturn. Da sie ihrer Zeit voraus war, kam sie vor ihren Konkurrenten PS2, Xbox und GameCube auf den Markt. Ihr Name setzt sich aus den Wörtern dream (Traum) und cast (von broadcast: ausstrahlen) zusammen. Sie war die erste Konsole, die standardmäßig mit einem Modem ausgeliefert wurde, das ihr die Unterstützung von Online-Spielen ermöglichte.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>La Dreamcast (ドリームキャスト) es la sucesora de la Saturn. Adelantada a su tiempo, salió al mercado antes que sus competidoras la PS2, la Xbox y la GameCube. Su nombre se compone de las palabras dream y cast. Fue la primera consola que incorporaba un módem de serie, lo que le permitía soportar juegos en línea.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Il Dreamcast (ドリームキャスト) è il successore del Saturn. In anticipo sui tempi, è arrivato sul mercato prima dei suoi concorrenti PS2, Xbox e GameCube. Il suo nome è composto dalle parole dream e cast. È stata la prima console a disporre di un modem di serie, che le ha permesso di supportare il gioco online.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>ドリームキャスト（Dreamcast）はサターンの後継機である。PS2、Xbox、ゲームキューブといった競合他社に先駆けて発売された。名前の由来は、dream（夢）とcast（キャスト）からなる。ゲーム機として初めてモデムを標準装備し、オンラインゲームに対応した。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>De Dreamcast (ドリームキャスト) is de opvolger van de Saturn. Hij was zijn tijd ver vooruit en kwam eerder op de markt dan zijn concurrenten de PS2, Xbox en GameCube. De naam is samengesteld uit de woorden droom en cast. Het was de eerste console met standaard een modem, waardoor het online gaming kon ondersteunen.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>Dreamcast (ドリームキャスト) jest następcą Saturna. Wyprzedzając swoje czasy, pojawił się na rynku przed swoimi konkurentami - PS2, Xboxem i GameCube. Jej nazwa składa się ze słów dream i cast. Była to pierwsza konsola, która standardowo wyposażona była w modem, dzięki czemu mogła obsługiwać gry online.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>O Dreamcast (ドリームキャスト) é o sucessor do Saturn. À frente do seu tempo, chegou ao mercado antes dos seus concorrentes a PS2, Xbox e GameCube. O seu nome é composto pelas palavras sonho e elenco. Foi a primeira consola a vir com um modem como padrão, permitindo-lhe suportar jogos online.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>Dreamcast (ドリームキャスト) является преемником Saturn. Опередив свое время, она появилась на рынке раньше своих конкурентов PS2, Xbox и GameCube. Ее название состоит из слов dream и cast. Это была первая консоль, в стандартную комплектацию которой входил модем, что позволило ей поддерживать онлайновые игры.</text>
</text>


<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Shenmue (1999)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>Ryo Hazuki is a young martial artist from Yokosuka, marked by his father's death and driven by a search for truth. Reserved and determined, he moves with an almost stoic discipline inherited from his martial upbringing. His leather jacket, jeans and closed expression define a restrained hero, rooted in a realistic and carefully recreated Japan.
Fun fact: Shenmue combined a day-night cycle, changing weather and NPC routines to give Yokosuka a credible daily rhythm.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Ryo Hazuki est un jeune pratiquant d’arts martiaux de Yokosuka, marqué par la mort de son père et animé par une quête de vérité. Réservé et déterminé, il avance avec une rigueur presque stoïque, héritée de son éducation martiale. Sa veste en cuir, son jean et son regard fermé incarnent un héros sobre, ancré dans un Japon réaliste et minutieusement reconstitué.
Fun fact : Shenmue combinait cycle jour-nuit, météo variable et routines de PNJ pour donner à Yokosuka un rythme quotidien crédible.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Ryo Hazuki es un joven practicante de artes marciales de Yokosuka, marcado por la muerte de su padre y movido por una búsqueda de la verdad. Reservado y decidido, avanza con una disciplina casi estoica heredada de su educación marcial. Su chaqueta de cuero, sus vaqueros y su mirada cerrada definen a un héroe sobrio, ligado a un Japón realista y cuidado.
Dato curioso: Shenmue combinaba ciclo día-noche, clima variable y rutinas de PNJ para dar a Yokosuka un ritmo diario creíble.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Ryo Hazuki è un giovane praticante di arti marziali di Yokosuka, segnato dalla morte del padre e spinto da una ricerca di verità. Riservato e determinato, avanza con una disciplina quasi stoica ereditata dalla sua educazione marziale. Giacca di pelle, jeans e sguardo chiuso definiscono un eroe sobrio, legato a un Giappone realistico e curato.
Curiosità: Shenmue combinava ciclo giorno-notte, meteo variabile e routine dei PNG per dare a Yokosuka un ritmo quotidiano credibile.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Ryo Hazuki ist ein junger Kampfkünstler aus Yokosuka, geprägt vom Tod seines Vaters und angetrieben von der Suche nach Wahrheit. Zurückhaltend und entschlossen folgt er einer fast stoischen Disziplin aus seiner Kampfkunsterziehung. Lederjacke, Jeans und verschlossener Blick zeigen einen nüchternen Helden in einem realistischen Japan.
Interessante Tatsache: Shenmue kombinierte Tag-Nacht-Wechsel, Wetter und NPC-Routinen zu einem glaubwürdigen Alltag in Yokosuka.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Ryo Hazuki é um jovem praticante de artes marciais de Yokosuka, marcado pela morte do pai e movido por uma busca pela verdade. Reservado e determinado, avança com uma disciplina quase estoica herdada da sua formação marcial. O casaco de couro, os jeans e o olhar fechado definem um herói sóbrio, ligado a um Japão realista e cuidado.
Curiosidade: Shenmue combinava ciclo dia-noite, clima variável e rotinas de NPCs para dar a Yokosuka um ritmo diário credível.</text>
</text>
</view>
</theme>
