<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>EasyRPG is a community project aiming to create a free, open source role-playing game creation tool compatible with RPG Maker 2000/2003 games. The project allows you to enjoy these games on different media.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>EasyRPG est un projet communautaire visant à créer un outil de création de jeux de rôle gratuit, open source, compatible avec les jeux RPG Maker 2000/2003. Le projet permet de profiter de ces jeux sur différents supports.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>EasyRPG ist ein Gemeinschaftsprojekt zur Entwicklung eines kostenlosen Open-Source-Tools zur Erstellung von Rollenspielen, das mit den RPG Maker 2000/2003-Spielen kompatibel ist. Das Projekt ermöglicht es, diese Spiele auf verschiedenen Medien zu genießen.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>EasyRPG es un proyecto comunitario cuyo objetivo es crear una herramienta de creación de juegos de rol gratuita y de código abierto compatible con los juegos RPG Maker 2000/2003. El proyecto permite disfrutar de estos juegos en diferentes soportes.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>EasyRPG è un progetto comunitario che mira a creare uno strumento gratuito e open source per la creazione di giochi di ruolo compatibile con i giochi RPG Maker 2000/2003. Il progetto permette di godere di questi giochi su diversi supporti.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>EasyRPGは、RPG Maker 2000/2003のゲームに対応した、フリーでオープンソースのロールプレイングゲーム作成ツールを作ることを目的としたコミュニティプロジェクトです。このプロジェクトにより、これらのゲームをさまざまなメディアで楽しむことができるようになります。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>EasyRPG is een gemeenschapsproject met als doel een gratis, open source tool voor het maken van rollenspellen, compatibel met de RPG Maker 2000/2003 spellen. Het project maakt het mogelijk om van deze spellen te genieten op verschillende media.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>EasyRPG to projekt społecznościowy mający na celu stworzenie darmowego, otwartego narzędzia do tworzenia gier fabularnych, kompatybilnego z grami RPG Maker 2000/2003. Projekt pozwala cieszyć się tymi grami na różnych nośnikach.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>EasyRPG é um projecto comunitário que visa criar uma ferramenta de criação de jogos de RPG gratuita e de código aberto compatível com os jogos do RPG Maker 2000/2003. O projecto permite desfrutar destes jogos em diferentes suportes.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>EasyRPG - это проект сообщества, целью которого является создание бесплатного инструмента для создания игр RPG Maker 2000/2003 с открытым исходным кодом. Проект позволяет вам наслаждаться этими играми на различных носителях.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;RPG Maker 2000 (2000)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>This young red-haired archer wears a light dress and handles a short bow with confidence. Agile and quick, she favors ranged attacks and precise movement to avoid blows. Her simple, practical gear suggests the start of an adventure, where each fight depends on timing and positioning more than raw power.
Fun fact: In RPG Maker 2000 games, archers often use the same animations as other weapons because there is no dedicated ranged-attack system.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Cette jeune archère aux cheveux rouges porte une robe légère et manie un arc court avec assurance. Agile et rapide, elle privilégie les attaques à distance et les déplacements précis pour éviter les coups. Son équipement simple et fonctionnel évoque les débuts d’aventure, où chaque combat repose sur le timing et la position plutôt que sur la puissance brute.
Fun fact : Dans les jeux RPG Maker 2000, les archers utilisent souvent les mêmes animations que les autres armes, faute de système dédié aux tirs à distance.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Esta joven arquera pelirroja lleva un vestido ligero y maneja un arco corto con seguridad. Ágil y rápida, prefiere los ataques a distancia y los movimientos precisos para esquivar golpes. Su equipo simple y funcional evoca el inicio de una aventura, donde cada combate depende más del ritmo y la posición que de la fuerza bruta.
Dato curioso: En los juegos de RPG Maker 2000, los arqueros suelen usar las mismas animaciones que otras armas, al no existir un sistema dedicado a disparos a distancia.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Questa giovane arciera dai capelli rossi indossa un abito leggero e usa un arco corto con sicurezza. Agile e rapida, preferisce gli attacchi a distanza e i movimenti precisi per evitare i colpi. Il suo equipaggiamento semplice e funzionale richiama l’inizio di un’avventura, dove ogni scontro dipende più dal tempismo e dalla posizione che dalla forza bruta.
Curiosità: Nei giochi RPG Maker 2000, gli arcieri usano spesso le stesse animazioni delle altre armi, perché manca un sistema dedicato ai tiri a distanza.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Diese junge rothaarige Bogenschützin trägt ein leichtes Kleid und führt einen kurzen Bogen mit sicherer Hand. Beweglich und schnell, setzt sie auf Fernangriffe und präzise Schritte, um Treffer zu vermeiden. Ihre einfache, zweckmäßige Ausrüstung erinnert an den Beginn eines Abenteuers, in dem Timing und Position wichtiger sind als rohe Kraft.
Interessante Tatsache: In RPG Maker 2000-Spielen nutzen Bogenschützen oft dieselben Animationen wie andere Waffen, da es kein eigenes System für Fernkampfschüsse gibt.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Esta jovem arqueira ruiva usa um vestido leve e maneja um arco curto com confiança. Ágil e rápida, prefere ataques à distância e movimentos precisos para evitar golpes. O seu equipamento simples e funcional evoca o início de uma aventura, onde cada combate depende mais do timing e da posição do que da força bruta.
Curiosidade: Nos jogos RPG Maker 2000, arqueiros costumam usar as mesmas animações de outras armas, pois não há um sistema dedicado a disparos à distância.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
