<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>EDuke32 is a source port of Duke Nukem 3D. Under the bonnet are tons of new features, a free, multi-platform engine, a modern interface, graphics acceleration, Polymer rendering, compatibility with the high-resolution pack, high-performance scripting for mods, an advanced console, bug fixes and more.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>EDuke32 est un port source de Duke Nukem 3D. Sous le capot, des tonnes de nouvelles fonctionnalités, un moteur libre et multi-plateforme, une interface moderne, l'accélération graphique, le rendu "Polymer", la compatibilité avec le pack haute résolution, un scripting performant pour les mods, une console évoluée, la correction de bugs, ...</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>EDuke32 ist ein Quellport von Duke Nukem 3D. Unter der Haube befinden sich tonnenweise neue Funktionen, eine freie und plattformübergreifende Engine, eine moderne Benutzeroberfläche, Grafikbeschleunigung, "Polymer"-Rendering, Kompatibilität mit dem High-Resolution-Pack, leistungsstarkes Scripting für Mods, eine weiterentwickelte Konsole, Fehlerkorrekturen, ...</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>EDuke32 es un port fuente de Duke Nukem 3D. Bajo el capó hay toneladas de nuevas características, un motor libre y multiplataforma, una interfaz moderna, aceleración de gráficos, renderizado Polymer, compatibilidad con el pack de alta resolución, scripting de alto rendimiento para mods, una consola avanzada, corrección de errores y mucho más.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>EDuke32 è un porting sorgente di Duke Nukem 3D. Sotto il cofano ci sono tonnellate di nuove funzionalità, un motore gratuito e multipiattaforma, un'interfaccia moderna, l'accelerazione grafica, il rendering Polymer, la compatibilità con il pacchetto ad alta risoluzione, lo scripting ad alte prestazioni per le mod, una console avanzata, la correzione di bug e molto altro.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>EDuke32はDuke Nukem 3Dのソース移植版です。大量の新機能、フリーのマルチプラットフォームエンジン、モダンなインターフェイス、グラフィックアクセラレーション、ポリマーレンダリング、高解像度パックとの互換性、MOD用の高性能スクリプト、高度なコンソール、バグ修正などが含まれています。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>EDuke32 is een broncode-port van Duke Nukem 3D. Onder de motorkap zitten tonnen nieuwe functies, een vrije, multiplatform engine, een moderne interface, grafische versnelling, Polymer rendering, compatibiliteit met het hoge-resolutie pakket, high-performance scripting voor mods, een geavanceerde console, bugfixes en nog veel meer.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>EDuke32 to źródłowy port gry Duke Nukem 3D. Pod maską znajduje się mnóstwo nowych funkcji, darmowy, wieloplatformowy silnik, nowoczesny interfejs, akceleracja grafiki, renderowanie Polymer, kompatybilność z pakietem wysokiej rozdzielczości, wydajne skrypty dla modów, zaawansowana konsola, poprawki błędów i wiele więcej.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>O EDuke32 é uma versão de origem do Duke Nukem 3D. Sob o capô estão toneladas de novas funcionalidades, um motor gratuito e multiplataforma, uma interface moderna, aceleração gráfica, renderização Polymer, compatibilidade com o pacote de alta resolução, scripting de alto desempenho para mods, uma consola avançada, correcções de erros e muito mais.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>EDuke32 - это порт Duke Nukem 3D с исходным кодом. Под капотом - масса новых возможностей, бесплатный мультиплатформенный движок, современный интерфейс, ускорение графики, рендеринг Polymer, совместимость с пакетом высокого разрешения, высокопроизводительный скриптинг для модов, продвинутая консоль, исправление ошибок и многое другое.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Duke Nukem 3D (1996)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>
<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>Duke stands tall with black sunglasses, a red tank top and two pistols in hand, ready to face the alien invasion with his usual confidence. A muscular and provocative figure of 90s FPS games, he moves through interactive urban levels filled with brutal action, irreverent humour and cult one-liners. His exaggerated attitude is central to the series identity.
Fun fact: Duke Nukem 3D was remembered for its adult content, with explicit violence, sexual humour and controversial interactions for its time.</text>
</text>
<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Duke se tient debout, lunettes noires, débardeur rouge et deux pistolets en main, prêt à affronter l’invasion alien avec son assurance habituelle. Figure musclée et provocatrice du FPS des années 90, il traverse des environnements urbains interactifs entre action brutale, humour irrévérencieux et répliques cultes. Son attitude exagérée participe pleinement à l’identité unique de la série.
Fun fact : Duke Nukem 3D a marqué les esprits par son contenu adulte assumé, avec violence explicite, humour sexuel et interactions controversées pour l’époque.</text>
</text>
<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Duke se mantiene erguido, con gafas negras, camiseta roja y dos pistolas en las manos, listo para enfrentarse a la invasión alienígena con su confianza habitual. Figura musculosa y provocadora del FPS de los años 90, recorre escenarios urbanos interactivos entre acción brutal, humor irreverente y frases de culto. Su actitud exagerada define la identidad de la serie.
Dato curioso: Duke Nukem 3D llamó la atención por su contenido adulto, con violencia explícita, humor sexual e interacciones controvertidas para su época.</text>
</text>
<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Duke sta in piedi con occhiali neri, canotta rossa e due pistole in mano, pronto ad affrontare l’invasione aliena con la sua solita sicurezza. Figura muscolosa e provocatoria degli FPS anni 90, attraversa ambienti urbani interattivi tra azione brutale, umorismo irriverente e battute di culto. Il suo atteggiamento esagerato definisce l’identità della serie.
Curiosità: Duke Nukem 3D colpì per i suoi contenuti adulti, con violenza esplicita, umorismo sessuale e interazioni controverse per l’epoca.</text>
</text>
<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Duke steht mit schwarzer Sonnenbrille, rotem Tanktop und zwei Pistolen in den Händen bereit, die Alieninvasion mit gewohnter Selbstsicherheit zu bekämpfen. Als muskulöse und provokante FPS-Figur der 90er bewegt er sich durch interaktive Stadtszenen voller brutaler Action, respektlosem Humor und Kultsprüchen. Seine überzeichnete Haltung prägt die Reihe.
Interessante Tatsache: Duke Nukem 3D fiel durch erwachsene Inhalte auf, mit expliziter Gewalt, sexuellem Humor und damals umstrittenen Interaktionen.</text>
</text>
<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Duke aparece de pé, com óculos escuros, regata vermelha e duas pistolas nas mãos, pronto para enfrentar a invasão alienígena com a sua confiança habitual. Figura musculosa e provocadora dos FPS dos anos 90, percorre cenários urbanos interativos entre ação brutal, humor irreverente e frases de culto. A sua atitude exagerada define a identidade da série.
Curiosidade: Duke Nukem 3D ficou marcado pelo conteúdo adulto, com violência explícita, humor sexual e interações controversas para a época.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
