<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>Final Burn Neo is an arcade game emulator based on the Final Burn emulator, which emulates various systems such as the MVS, CPS1 and CPS2, System 16, System 18, X and Y Board from Sega, as well as a whole list of Cave Toaplan, Taito, Psikyo, Kaneko, ... It runs on Windows but is also ported to Linux, OSX and Android.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Final Burn Neo est un émulateur de jeu vidéo d'arcade basé sur l'émulateur Final Burn, qui émule différents systèmes tel que le MVS, le CPS1 et CPS2, le System 16, System 18, X et Y Board de Sega, ainsi que toute une liste de jeux Cave Toaplan, Taito, Psikyo, Kaneko, ... Il fonctionne sous Windows mais est également porté sous Linux, OSX et Android.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Final Burn Neo ist ein Arcade-Videospiel-Emulator, der auf dem Final Burn-Emulator basiert und verschiedene Systeme wie das MVS, CPS1 und CPS2, System 16, System 18, Sega X und Y Board sowie eine ganze Liste von Spielen von Cave Toaplan, Taito, Psikyo, Kaneko, ... emuliert. Es läuft unter Windows, wird aber auch auf Linux, OSX und Android portiert.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Final Burn Neo es un emulador de juegos arcade basado en el emulador Final Burn, que emula varios sistemas como la MVS, CPS1 y CPS2, System 16, System 18, X e Y Board de Sega, así como toda una lista de juegos de Cave Toaplan, Taito, Psikyo, Kaneko, .... Funciona en Windows pero también está portado a Linux, OSX y Android.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Final Burn Neo è un emulatore di giochi arcade basato sull'emulatore Final Burn, che emula vari sistemi come MVS, CPS1 e CPS2, System 16, System 18, X e Y Board di Sega, così come un'intera lista di Cave Toaplan, Taito, Psikyo, Kaneko, ... Funziona su Windows, ma è anche disponibile per Linux, OSX e Android.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>Final Burn Neoは、Final Burnエミュレータをベースにしたアーケードゲームエミュレータで、セガのMVS、CPS1、CPS2、システム16、システム18、X、Yボードなどの各種システムや、ケイブトープラン、タイトー、プシキョ、金子、・・・のゲーム一式をエミュレートします。Windowsで動作しますが、Linux、OSX、Androidにも移植されています。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>Final Burn Neo is een arcade game emulator gebaseerd op de Final Burn emulator, die verschillende systemen emuleert zoals de MVS, CPS1 en CPS2, System 16, System 18, X en Y Board van Sega, alsook een hele lijst van Cave Toaplan, Taito, Psikyo, Kaneko, ... games. Het draait op Windows maar is ook geport naar Linux, OSX en Android.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>Final Burn Neo to emulator gier zręcznościowych oparty na emulatorze Final Burn, który emuluje różne systemy, takie jak MVS, CPS1 i CPS2, System 16, System 18, X i Y Board od Sega, a także całą listę gier Cave Toaplan, Taito, Psikyo, Kaneko, ..... Działa na Windowsie, ale jest też portowany na Linuksa, OSX i Androida.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Final Burn Neo é um emulador de jogos arcade baseado no emulador Final Burn, que emula vários sistemas tais como MVS, CPS1 e CPS2, System 16, System 18, X e Y Board da Sega, bem como uma lista completa de jogos Cave Toaplan, Taito, Psikyo, Kaneko, ... Corre em Windows mas também é portado para Linux, OSX e Android.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>Final Burn Neo - это эмулятор аркадных игр, основанный на эмуляторе Final Burn, который эмулирует различные системы, такие как MVS, CPS1 и CPS2, System 16, System 18, X и Y Board от Sega, а также целый список игр Cave Toaplan, Taito, Psikyo, Kaneko, .... Она работает под Windows, но также портирована на Linux, OSX и Android.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;The Punisher (1993)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>The Punisher wears his iconic blue outfit in this sharp Capcom beat 'em up, where Frank Castle fights organized crime with punches, melee weapons and firearms picked up from enemies. On arcade, the game focuses on direct, violent and readable action, with the fast pace typical of Capcom productions from the early 90s.
Fun fact: the game features a co-op mode where Nick Fury can fight alongside the Punisher.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Le Punisher porte sa tenue bleue emblématique dans ce beat’em up nerveux signé Capcom, où Frank Castle affronte le crime organisé à coups de poings, d’armes blanches et d’armes à feu récupérées sur les ennemis. Sur arcade, le jeu mise sur une action directe, violente et très lisible, avec un rythme soutenu typique des productions Capcom du début des années 90.
Fun fact : le jeu propose un mode coopération permettant d’incarner Nick Fury aux côtés du Punisher.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>El Punisher lleva su icónico traje azul en este intenso beat 'em up de Capcom, donde Frank Castle se enfrenta al crimen organizado con puños, armas blancas y armas de fuego recogidas de los enemigos. En arcade, el juego apuesta por una acción directa, violenta y muy legible, con el ritmo rápido típico de las producciones de Capcom de principios de los 90.
Dato curioso: el juego incluye un modo cooperativo que permite encarnar a Nick Fury junto al Punisher.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Il Punisher indossa il suo iconico costume blu in questo frenetico beat 'em up Capcom, dove Frank Castle affronta il crimine organizzato con pugni, armi bianche e armi da fuoco raccolte dai nemici. In sala giochi, il gioco punta su un’azione diretta, violenta e molto leggibile, con il ritmo sostenuto tipico delle produzioni Capcom dei primi anni 90.
Curiosità: il gioco offre una modalità cooperativa che permette di usare Nick Fury al fianco del Punisher.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Der Punisher trägt sein ikonisches blaues Outfit in diesem rasanten Beat 'em up von Capcom, in dem Frank Castle das organisierte Verbrechen mit Fäusten, Nahkampfwaffen und von Gegnern erbeuteten Schusswaffen bekämpft. In der Arcade setzt das Spiel auf direkte, harte und gut lesbare Action, mit dem hohen Tempo typischer Capcom-Produktionen der frühen 90er.
Interessante Tatsache: Das Spiel bietet einen Koop-Modus, in dem Nick Fury an der Seite des Punisher spielbar ist.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>O Punisher usa o seu icônico traje azul neste intenso beat 'em up da Capcom, onde Frank Castle enfrenta o crime organizado com socos, armas brancas e armas de fogo recolhidas dos inimigos. No arcade, o jogo aposta numa ação direta, violenta e muito legível, com o ritmo acelerado típico das produções da Capcom do início dos anos 90.
Curiosidade: o jogo traz um modo cooperativo que permite controlar Nick Fury ao lado do Punisher.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
