<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>The Famicom Disk System or FDS is a peripheral for the Famicom video game console released on 21 February 1986 in Japan. It fits under the console and uses a proprietary floppy disk format to store games. The US version, planned for late 1986, was never released. </text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Le Famicom Disk System ou FDS est un périphérique de la console de jeux vidéo Famicom sorti le 21 février 1986 au Japon. Il se place sous la console et utilise un format propriétaire de disquette permettant de stocker des jeux. La version américaine, prévue pour fin 1986, n'a jamais été publiée. </text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Das Famicom Disk System oder FDS ist ein Peripheriegerät für die Videospielkonsole Famicom, das am 21. Februar 1986 in Japan veröffentlicht wurde. Es wird unter der Konsole angebracht und verwendet ein proprietäres Diskettenformat, auf dem Spiele gespeichert werden können. Die amerikanische Version, die für Ende 1986 geplant war, wurde nie veröffentlicht. </text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>El Famicom Disk System o FDS es un periférico para la videoconsola Famicom lanzado el 21 de febrero de 1986 en Japón. Se coloca debajo de la consola y utiliza un formato de disquete propietario para almacenar los juegos. La versión estadounidense, prevista para finales de 1986, nunca salió a la venta. </text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Il Famicom Disk System o FDS è una periferica per la console per videogiochi Famicom rilasciata il 21 febbraio 1986 in Giappone. Si inserisce sotto la console e utilizza un formato di floppy disk proprietario per memorizzare i giochi. La versione statunitense, prevista per la fine del 1986, non è mai stata rilasciata. </text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>ファミコンディスクシステム（FDS）は、1986年2月21日に日本で発売されたビデオゲーム機「ファミコン」用の周辺機器である。ゲーム機の下に装着し、独自のフロッピーディスク方式でゲームを保存する。1986年末に予定されていた米国版は、発売されなかった。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>Het Famicom Disk System of FDS is een randapparaat voor de Famicom videospelconsole dat op 21 februari 1986 in Japan werd uitgebracht. Het past onder de console en gebruikt een eigen floppydiskformaat om spellen op te slaan. De Amerikaanse versie, gepland voor eind 1986, werd nooit uitgebracht. </text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>Famicom Disk System lub FDS to urządzenie peryferyjne dla konsoli gier wideo Famicom wydanej 21 lutego 1986 roku w Japonii. Mieści się pod konsolą i wykorzystuje zastrzeżony format dyskietki do przechowywania gier. Wersja amerykańska, planowana na koniec 1986 roku, nigdy nie została wydana. </text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>O Famicom Disk System ou FDS é um periférico para a consola de videojogos Famicom lançado a 21 de Fevereiro de 1986 no Japão. Cabe debaixo da consola e utiliza um formato proprietário de disquete para armazenar jogos. A versão americana, planeada para finais de 1986, nunca foi lançada. </text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>Famicom Disk System или FDS - это периферийное устройство для игровой консоли Famicom, выпущенное 21 февраля 1986 года в Японии. Он помещается под консоль и использует собственный формат дискет для хранения игр. Версия для США, запланированная на конец 1986 года, так и не была выпущена. </text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Yume Kojou: Doki Doki Panic (1987)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>Imajin is one of the heroes of Yume Kojou: Doki Doki Panic, a platform game released on Famicom Disk System and designed to promote a Japanese media event (Yume Kojou ’87). The game features several playable characters with different abilities, offering varied approaches depending on the player’s choice and adding depth from the very first minutes.
Fun fact: The game later became the basis for Super Mario Bros. 2 outside Japan, with its mascots replaced by Mario, Luigi, Peach and Toad</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Imajin est l’un des héros de Yume Kojou: Doki Doki Panic, un jeu de plateforme sorti sur Famicom Disk System et conçu pour promouvoir un événement médiatique japonais (Yume Kojou ’87). Le jeu propose plusieurs personnages jouables aux capacités différentes, apportant des approches variées selon le choix du joueur et renforçant sa richesse dès ses premières minutes.
Fun fact : Le jeu a servi de base à Super Mario Bros. 2 hors Japon, avec les mascottes remplacées par Mario, Luigi, Peach et Toad</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Imajin es uno de los héroes de Yume Kojou: Doki Doki Panic, un juego de plataformas lanzado para Famicom Disk System y creado para promocionar un evento mediático japonés (Yume Kojou ’87). El juego ofrece varios personajes jugables con habilidades distintas, aportando enfoques variados según la elección del jugador y aumentando su riqueza desde los primeros minutos.
Dato curioso: El juego sirvió de base para Super Mario Bros. 2 fuera de Japón, con sus mascotas sustituidas por Mario, Luigi, Peach y Toad</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Imajin è uno degli eroi di Yume Kojou: Doki Doki Panic, un platform uscito su Famicom Disk System e creato per promuovere un evento mediatico giapponese (Yume Kojou ’87). Il gioco propone più personaggi giocabili con abilità diverse, offrendo approcci vari in base alla scelta del giocatore e aumentando la sua ricchezza fin dai primi minuti.
Curiosità: Il gioco servì da base per Super Mario Bros. 2 fuori dal Giappone, con le mascotte sostituite da Mario, Luigi, Peach e Toad</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Imajin ist einer der Helden von Yume Kojou: Doki Doki Panic, einem Jump-and-Run für das Famicom Disk System, das zur Werbung für ein japanisches Medienereignis (Yume Kojou ’87) entwickelt wurde. Das Spiel bietet mehrere spielbare Figuren mit unterschiedlichen Fähigkeiten und ermöglicht je nach Wahl des Spielers verschiedene Ansätze.
Interessante Tatsache: Das Spiel diente außerhalb Japans als Grundlage für Super Mario Bros. 2, wobei die Maskottchen durch Mario, Luigi, Peach und Toad ersetzt wurden</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Imajin é um dos heróis de Yume Kojou: Doki Doki Panic, um jogo de plataformas lançado para Famicom Disk System e criado para promover um evento mediático japonês (Yume Kojou ’87). O jogo oferece várias personagens jogáveis com capacidades diferentes, trazendo abordagens variadas conforme a escolha do jogador e enriquecendo a experiência desde o início.
Curiosidade: O jogo serviu de base para Super Mario Bros. 2 fora do Japão, com as mascotes substituídas por Mario, Luigi, Peach e Toad</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
