<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>Final Fight is a beat'em up series from Capcom that began in 1989, with Haggar, Cody and Guy battling the Mad Gear gang to save Metro City. The gameplay is based on dynamic street battles with varied attacks and pick-upable weapons. The series influenced the genre with its fluid action and urban atmosphere. Although less exploited today, it remains a retro-gaming classic.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Final Fight est une série de beat'em up de Capcom débutée en 1989, où Haggar, Cody et Guy affrontent le gang Mad Gear pour sauver Metro City. Le gameplay repose sur des combats de rue dynamiques avec des attaques variées et des armes ramassables. La série a influencé le genre avec son action fluide et son ambiance urbaine. Bien que moins exploitée aujourd’hui, elle reste un classique du rétro-gaming.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Final Fight es una serie de beat'em up de Capcom iniciada en 1989, donde Haggar, Cody y Guy se enfrentan a la banda Mad Gear para salvar Metro City. La jugabilidad se basa en combates callejeros dinámicos con ataques variados y armas que se pueden recoger. La serie influyó en el género con su acción fluida y su atmósfera urbana. Aunque hoy se explota menos, sigue siendo un clásico del retro-gaming.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Final Fight è una serie di beat'em up di Capcom iniziata nel 1989, in cui Haggar, Cody e Guy affrontano la gang Mad Gear per salvare Metro City. Il gameplay si basa su combattimenti di strada dinamici con attacchi vari e armi raccoglibili. La serie ha influenzato il genere con la sua azione fluida e la sua atmosfera urbana. Anche se oggi è meno sfruttata, resta un classico del retro-gaming.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Final Fight ist eine Beat'em-up-Reihe von Capcom, die 1989 begann und in der Haggar, Cody und Guy gegen die Mad-Gear-Bande kämpfen, um Metro City zu retten. Das Gameplay basiert auf dynamischen Straßenkämpfen mit vielfältigen Angriffen und aufnehmbaren Waffen. Die Reihe prägte das Genre mit flüssiger Action und urbaner Atmosphäre. Auch wenn sie heute weniger genutzt wird, bleibt sie ein Retro-Gaming-Klassiker.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Final Fight é uma série de beat'em up da Capcom iniciada em 1989, na qual Haggar, Cody e Guy enfrentam a gangue Mad Gear para salvar Metro City. A jogabilidade se baseia em combates de rua dinâmicos com ataques variados e armas que podem ser recolhidas. A série influenciou o gênero com sua ação fluida e sua atmosfera urbana. Embora hoje seja menos explorada, continua sendo um clássico do retro-gaming.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Final Fight (Arcade, 1989)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>Mike Haggar is the mayor of Metro City and a former wrestler turned vigilante, recognizable by his imposing build and brutal bare-handed fighting style, facing the gangs corrupting the city with direct, uncompromising strength and embodying an authority figure ready to take to the streets to restore order.
Fun fact: Haggar appears in several Capcom games outside Final Fight, such as Saturday Night Slam Masters and Marvel vs. Capcom 3, while being linked to Street Fighter through Metro City, where he is mayor.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Mike Haggar est le maire de Metro City et ancien catcheur devenu justicier, reconnaissable à sa carrure imposante et son style de combat brutal à mains nues, affrontant les gangs qui gangrènent la ville avec une force directe et sans compromis, incarnant une figure d’autorité prête à descendre dans la rue pour rétablir l’ordre.
Fun fact : Haggar apparaît dans plusieurs jeux Capcom hors Final Fight comme Saturday Night Slam Masters et Marvel vs. Capcom 3, tout en étant lié à Street Fighter via Metro City dont il est le maire.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Mike Haggar es el alcalde de Metro City y un antiguo luchador convertido en justiciero, reconocible por su corpulencia imponente y su estilo brutal de combate cuerpo a cuerpo, enfrentándose a los gangs que corrompen la ciudad con una fuerza directa y sin concesiones, encarnando una figura de autoridad dispuesta a bajar a la calle para restaurar el orden.
Dato curioso: Haggar aparece en varios juegos de Capcom fuera de Final Fight, como Saturday Night Slam Masters y Marvel vs. Capcom 3, además de estar ligado a Street Fighter a través de Metro City, donde es alcalde.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Mike Haggar è il sindaco di Metro City ed ex wrestler diventato giustiziere, riconoscibile dalla corporatura imponente e dal suo stile di combattimento brutale a mani nude, affrontando le gang che corrompono la città con forza diretta e senza compromessi, incarnando una figura d’autorità pronta a scendere in strada per ristabilire l’ordine.
Curiosità: Haggar appare in diversi giochi Capcom fuori da Final Fight, come Saturday Night Slam Masters e Marvel vs. Capcom 3, ed è legato a Street Fighter tramite Metro City, di cui è sindaco.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Mike Haggar ist der Bürgermeister von Metro City und ein ehemaliger Wrestler, der zum Selbstjustizler wurde. Er ist an seiner imposanten Statur und seinem brutalen waffenlosen Kampfstil erkennbar, stellt sich den Gangs, die die Stadt verderben, mit direkter und kompromissloser Kraft entgegen und verkörpert eine Autoritätsfigur, die selbst auf die Straße geht, um Ordnung wiederherzustellen.
Interessante Tatsache: Haggar erscheint in mehreren Capcom-Spielen außerhalb von Final Fight, etwa Saturday Night Slam Masters und Marvel vs. Capcom 3, und ist über Metro City, dessen Bürgermeister er ist, mit Street Fighter verbunden.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Mike Haggar é o prefeito de Metro City e um ex-lutador que se tornou justiceiro, reconhecível por sua estrutura imponente e seu estilo brutal de combate corpo a corpo, enfrentando as gangues que corroem a cidade com força direta e sem concessões, encarnando uma figura de autoridade pronta para ir às ruas a fim de restaurar a ordem.
Curiosidade: Haggar aparece em vários jogos da Capcom fora de Final Fight, como Saturday Night Slam Masters e Marvel vs. Capcom 3, além de estar ligado a Street Fighter por meio de Metro City, da qual é prefeito.</text>
</text>


</view>
</theme>
