<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>Adobe Flash, formerly Macromedia Flash, is a set of software technologies for manipulating vector graphics, raster images and ActionScript scripts to create or use multimedia content (animations, videos, games, applications, etc.). </text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Adobe Flash anciennement Macromedia Flash, désigne un ensemble de technologies logicielles permettant la manipulation de graphiques vectoriels, d'images matricielles et de scripts ActionScript en vue de créer ou utiliser des contenus multimédia (animations, vidéos, jeux, applications...). </text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Adobe Flash, früher Macromedia Flash, bezeichnet eine Reihe von Softwaretechnologien, die die Manipulation von Vektorgrafiken, Matrixbildern und ActionScript-Skripten ermöglichen, um Multimedia-Inhalte (Animationen, Videos, Spiele, Anwendungen...) zu erstellen oder zu verwenden. </text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Adobe Flash, antes Macromedia Flash, es un conjunto de tecnologías de software que permiten manipular gráficos vectoriales, imágenes de trama y secuencias de comandos ActionScript para crear o utilizar contenidos multimedia (animaciones, vídeos, juegos, aplicaciones, etc.).</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Adobe Flash, ex Macromedia Flash, è un insieme di tecnologie software che consentono la manipolazione di grafica vettoriale, immagini raster e script ActionScript per creare o utilizzare contenuti multimediali (animazioni, video, giochi, applicazioni, ecc.). </text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>Adobe Flash（旧Macromedia Flash）は、ベクターグラフィックス、ラスターイメージ、ActionScriptスクリプトを操作して、マルチメディアコンテンツ（アニメーション、ビデオ、ゲーム、アプリケーションなど）を作成または使用できるソフトウェア技術群です。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>Adobe Flash, voorheen Macromedia Flash, is een reeks softwaretechnologieën waarmee vectorafbeeldingen, rasterafbeeldingen en ActionScript-scripts kunnen worden gemanipuleerd om multimedia-inhoud (animaties, video's, spelletjes, toepassingen, enz.) te creëren of te gebruiken. </text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>Adobe Flash, dawniej Macromedia Flash, to zestaw technologii programowych, które umożliwiają manipulację grafiką wektorową, obrazami rastrowymi i skryptami ActionScript w celu stworzenia lub wykorzystania treści multimedialnych (animacji, filmów, gier, aplikacji itp.). </text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Adobe Flash, anteriormente Macromedia Flash, é um conjunto de tecnologias de software que permitem a manipulação de gráficos vectoriais, imagens raster e scripts ActionScript para criar ou utilizar conteúdos multimédia (animações, vídeos, jogos, aplicações, etc.). </text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>Adobe Flash, ранее Macromedia Flash, - это набор программных технологий, позволяющих манипулировать векторной графикой, растровыми изображениями и сценариями ActionScript для создания или использования мультимедийного контента (анимации, видео, игр, приложений и т.д.). </text>
</text>


<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>  Yeti Sports (2004)  </text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>The penguin from Yeti Sports captures the absurd, immediate spirit of Flash games, built around one simple idea: sending an animal as far as possible with precise timing. In a browser, the game relies on an instant, readable mechanic, effective animations and clear feedback. This direct approach makes it a striking example of the fast, accessible gameplay that defined a generation of web mini-games.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Le pingouin de Yeti Sports incarne l’esprit absurde et immédiat des jeux Flash, basé sur un principe simple : envoyer un animal le plus loin possible avec un timing précis. Sur navigateur, le jeu mise sur une mécanique instantanée et lisible, portée par des animations efficaces et un feedback clair. Cette approche directe en fait un exemple marquant du gameplay rapide et accessible qui a défini toute une génération de mini-jeux web.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="en">
<text>The penguin from Yeti Sports captures the absurd, immediate spirit of Flash games, built around one simple idea: sending an animal as far as possible with precise timing. In a browser, the game relies on an instant, readable mechanic, effective animations and clear feedback. This direct approach makes it a striking example of the fast, accessible gameplay that defined a generation of web mini-games.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>El pingüino de Yeti Sports encarna el espíritu absurdo e inmediato de los juegos Flash, basado en una idea sencilla: lanzar un animal lo más lejos posible con el momento justo. En navegador, el juego apuesta por una mecánica instantánea y clara, con animaciones eficaces y una respuesta visual precisa. Su enfoque directo lo convierte en un ejemplo destacado del juego rápido y accesible que definió una generación de minijuegos web.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Il pinguino di Yeti Sports incarna lo spirito assurdo e immediato dei giochi Flash, basato su un’idea semplice: lanciare un animale il più lontano possibile con il giusto tempismo. Su browser, il gioco punta su una meccanica immediata e leggibile, con animazioni efficaci e un feedback chiaro. Questo approccio diretto lo rende un esempio emblematico del gameplay rapido e accessibile che ha definito una generazione di mini-giochi web.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Der Pinguin aus Yeti Sports verkörpert den absurden und direkten Geist der Flash-Spiele, aufgebaut auf einer einfachen Idee: ein Tier mit präzisem Timing möglichst weit zu schleudern. Im Browser setzt das Spiel auf eine sofort verständliche Mechanik, klare Animationen und direktes Feedback. Dieser geradlinige Ansatz macht es zu einem prägnanten Beispiel für das schnelle, zugängliche Gameplay einer ganzen Webspiel-Generation.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>O pinguim de Yeti Sports representa o espírito absurdo e imediato dos jogos Flash, baseado numa ideia simples: lançar um animal o mais longe possível com o timing certo. No navegador, o jogo aposta numa mecânica instantânea e fácil de ler, com animações eficazes e resposta clara. Essa abordagem direta faz dele um exemplo marcante do gameplay rápido e acessível que definiu uma geração de minijogos web.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
