<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>The Gamate (超級小子) is a handheld game console manufactured by Bit Corporation in the early 1990s and marketed in Australia, parts of Europe, Asia (Taiwan and China), Argentina and the United States. Over 70 games, not all of which have been dumped, have been produced for the system.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>La Gamate (超級小子) est une console de jeu portable fabriquée par Bit Corporation au début des années 1990 et commercialisée en Australie, dans certaines régions d'Europe, en Asie (Taïwan et Chine), en Argentine et aux États-Unis. Plus de 70 jeux, qui n'ont pas tous fait l'objet d'un dumping, ont été produits pour le système.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Der Gamate (超級小子) ist eine tragbare Spielkonsole, die Anfang der 1990er Jahre von der Bit Corporation hergestellt und in Australien, Teilen Europas, Asien (Taiwan und China), Argentinien und den USA vermarktet wurde. Für das System wurden über 70 Spiele produziert, von denen nicht alle gedumpt wurden.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>La Gamate (超級小子) es una videoconsola portátil fabricada por Bit Corporation a principios de la década de 1990 y comercializada en Australia, parte de Europa, Asia (Taiwán y China), Argentina y Estados Unidos. Se produjeron para el sistema más de 70 juegos, de los cuales no todos fueron volcados.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Il Gamate (超級小子) è un sistema di gioco portatile prodotto da Bit Corporation all'inizio degli anni '90 e commercializzato in Australia, parte dell'Europa, Asia (Taiwan e Cina), Argentina e Stati Uniti. Per il sistema sono stati prodotti oltre 70 giochi, non tutti scaricati.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>ゲーマテ（超級小子）は、1990年代前半に株式会社ビットが製造し、オーストラリア、ヨーロッパの一部、アジア（台湾、中国）、アルゼンチン、アメリカで販売された携帯型ゲーム機である。このシステムのために、すべてが投棄されたわけではないが、70以上のゲームが生産された。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>De Gamate (超級小子) is een draagbare spelconsole die begin jaren negentig door Bit Corporation werd vervaardigd en in Australië, delen van Europa, Azië (Taiwan en China), Argentinië en de Verenigde Staten op de markt werd gebracht. Voor het systeem werden meer dan 70 spelletjes geproduceerd, die niet allemaal werden gedumpt.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>Gamate (超級小子) to ręczna konsola do gier wyprodukowana przez Bit Corporation na początku lat 90. i sprzedawana w Australii, części Europy, Azji (Tajwan i Chiny), Argentynie i Stanach Zjednoczonych. Dla systemu wyprodukowano ponad 70 gier, z których nie wszystkie zostały zrzucone.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>The Gamate (超級小子) é uma consola de jogos portátil fabricada pela Bit Corporation no início dos anos 90 e comercializada na Austrália, partes da Europa, Ásia (Taiwan e China), Argentina e Estados Unidos. Foram produzidos mais de 70 jogos, nem todos foram abandonados, para a consola.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>Gamate (超級小子) - портативная игровая консоль, выпущенная компанией Bit Corporation в начале 1990-х годов и продававшаяся в Австралии, некоторых странах Европы, Азии (Тайвань и Китай), Аргентине и США. Для системы было выпущено более 70 игр, не все из которых были выброшены на свалку.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
	<text>&#160;&#160;Snowman Legend (1992)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
	<text>Snowman Legend features a snowman navigating a winter-themed world filled with obstacles and enemies in a simple and direct platform game. The character’s minimal design reflects the limitations of the Gamate while offering clear and accessible gameplay focused on movement and jump timing.
Fun fact: The Gamate is one of the few 90s handheld consoles to use a very low-contrast LCD screen, making some games like Snowman Legend harder to read.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
	<text>Snowman Legend met en scène un bonhomme de neige évoluant dans un univers hivernal rempli d’obstacles et d’ennemis, dans un jeu de plateforme simple et direct. Le personnage, au design minimaliste, reflète les limitations de la Gamate tout en proposant une action lisible et accessible, centrée sur les déplacements et le timing des sauts.
Fun fact : La Gamate est l’une des rares consoles portables des années 90 à utiliser un écran LCD très peu contrasté, rendant certains jeux comme Snowman Legend difficiles à lire.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
	<text>Snowman Legend presenta a un muñeco de nieve evolucionando en un entorno invernal lleno de obstáculos y enemigos, en un juego de plataformas simple y directo. El diseño minimalista del personaje refleja las limitaciones de la Gamate, ofreciendo una jugabilidad clara y accesible basada en el movimiento y el tiempo de salto.
Dato curioso: La Gamate es una de las pocas consolas portátiles de los años 90 que utilizaba una pantalla LCD con muy bajo contraste, haciendo que algunos juegos como Snowman Legend sean difíciles de ver.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
	<text>Snowman Legend mette in scena un pupazzo di neve in un ambiente invernale pieno di ostacoli e nemici, in un gioco platform semplice e diretto. Il design minimalista del personaggio riflette le limitazioni della Gamate, offrendo un gameplay chiaro e accessibile basato sul movimento e sul tempismo dei salti.
Curiosità: La Gamate è una delle poche console portatili degli anni 90 a utilizzare uno schermo LCD con un contrasto molto basso, rendendo alcuni giochi come Snowman Legend difficili da vedere.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
	<text>Snowman Legend zeigt einen Schneemann in einer winterlichen Umgebung voller Hindernisse und Gegner in einem einfachen und direkten Plattformspiel. Das minimalistische Design der Figur spiegelt die technischen Einschränkungen der Gamate wider und bietet ein klares und zugängliches Gameplay, das auf Bewegung und Sprungtiming basiert.
Interessante Tatsache: Die Gamate gehört zu den wenigen tragbaren Konsolen der 90er Jahre mit einem sehr kontrastarmen LCD-Bildschirm, wodurch einige Spiele wie Snowman Legend schwer zu erkennen sind.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
	<text>Snowman Legend apresenta um boneco de neve em um ambiente de inverno cheio de obstáculos e inimigos, em um jogo de plataforma simples e direto. O design minimalista do personagem reflete as limitações da Gamate, oferecendo uma jogabilidade clara e acessível focada no movimento e no tempo dos saltos.
Curiosidade: A Gamate é uma das poucas consoles portáteis dos anos 90 a usar uma tela LCD com contraste muito baixo, tornando alguns jogos como Snowman Legend difíceis de visualizar.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
