<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>The Epoch Game Pocket Computer (ゲームポケコン) is a portable game console marketed only in Japan. Preceding the Game Boy by 5 years, the console was a commercial failure, only 5 games were designed for it. A puzzle game and a paint program were built into the system.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>L'Epoch Game Pocket Computer (ゲームポケコン) est une console de jeu portable commercialisée uniquement au Japon. Précédant de 5 ans la Game Boy, la console a été un échec commercial, seuls 5 jeux ont été conçus pour elle. Un jeu de puzzle et un programme de peinture étaient intégrés au système.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Der Epoch Game Pocket Computer (ゲームポケコン) ist eine tragbare Spielkonsole, die nur in Japan vertrieben wurde. Die Konsole, die 5 Jahre vor dem Game Boy auf den Markt kam, war ein kommerzieller Misserfolg, nur 5 Spiele wurden für sie entwickelt. Ein Puzzlespiel und ein Malprogramm waren in das System integriert.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>La Epoch Game Pocket Computer (ゲームポケコン) es una videoconsola portátil comercializada únicamente en Japón. Precediendo a la Game Boy en 5 años, la consola fue un fracaso comercial, sólo se diseñaron 5 juegos para ella. Un juego de puzles y un programa de pintura estaban integrados en el sistema.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>L'Epoch Game Pocket Computer (ゲームポケコン) è una console di gioco portatile commercializzata solo in Giappone. Preceduta di 5 anni dal Game Boy, la console è stata un fallimento commerciale: solo 5 giochi sono stati progettati per essa. Il sistema includeva un puzzle game e un programma di pittura.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>エポックゲームポケットコンピュータ（ゲームポコン）は、日本でのみ販売された携帯ゲーム機である。ゲームボーイに先立つこと5年、このゲーム機は商業的に失敗し、このゲーム用にデザインされたゲームはわずか5本だった。パズルゲームとペイントプログラムがシステムに組み込まれていた。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>De Epoch Game Pocket Computer (ゲームポケコン) is een draagbare spelconsole die alleen in Japan op de markt werd gebracht. De console, die 5 jaar vóór de Game Boy kwam, was een commerciële mislukking; er werden slechts 5 spellen voor ontworpen. Een puzzelspel en een verfprogramma werden in het systeem ingebouwd.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>Epoch Game Pocket Computer (ゲームポケコン) to przenośna konsola do gier sprzedawana tylko w Japonii. Poprzedzając Game Boya o 5 lat, konsola była komercyjną porażką, zaprojektowano na nią tylko 5 gier. W system wbudowana była gra logiczna oraz program do malowania.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>The Epoch Game Pocket Computer (ゲームポケコン) é uma consola de jogos portátil comercializada apenas no Japão. Precedendo o Game Boy por 5 anos, a consola foi um fracasso comercial, apenas 5 jogos foram concebidos para ela. Um jogo de puzzle e um programa de pintura foram incorporados no sistema.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>Epoch Game Pocket Computer (ゲームポケコン) - портативная игровая консоль, продававшаяся только в Японии. Предшествовавшая Game Boy на 5 лет, консоль была коммерчески неудачной, для нее было разработано всего 5 игр. В систему были встроены игра-головоломка и программа для рисования.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
