<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>The link cable is a proprietary type of cable to link two or more portable video game consoles to exchange content or play together on separate consoles. The term was popularised by Nintendo's Game Boy and the success of games such as Tetris, which were played on separate consoles.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Le câble link est un câble de type propriétaire permettant de lier deux ou plusieurs consoles de jeux vidéo portables pour échanger du contenu ou jouer ensemble, sur consoles séparées. Le terme a été popularisé par la Game Boy de Nintendo et le succès de jeux tels que Tetris, joués par consoles interposées.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Das Link-Kabel ist ein proprietäres Kabel, mit dem zwei oder mehr tragbare Videospielkonsolen miteinander verbunden werden können, um Inhalte auszutauschen oder gemeinsam auf getrennten Konsolen zu spielen. Der Begriff wurde durch Nintendos Game Boy und den Erfolg von Spielen wie Tetris populär, die über zwischengeschaltete Konsolen gespielt wurden.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>El cable de enlace es un cable propietario que permite enlazar dos o más videoconsolas portátiles para intercambiar contenidos o jugar a juegos en consolas separadas. El término se popularizó con la Game Boy de Nintendo y el éxito de juegos como el Tetris, que se jugaban en consolas separadas.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Il cavo di collegamento è un cavo proprietario che consente di collegare tra loro due o più console per videogiochi portatili per scambiare contenuti o giocare su console separate. Il termine è stato reso popolare dal Game Boy di Nintendo e dal successo di giochi come Tetris, che venivano giocati su console separate.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>リンクケーブルとは、2台以上の携帯型ゲーム機を連結して、別々のゲーム機でコンテンツを交換したり、ゲームをプレイしたりするための専用ケーブルのことです。この言葉は、任天堂のゲームボーイと、別々のゲーム機でプレイしていたテトリスなどのゲームの成功によって広まりました。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>De linkkabel is een eigen kabel waarmee twee of meer draagbare videospelconsoles aan elkaar kunnen worden gekoppeld om inhoud uit te wisselen of spellen op afzonderlijke consoles te spelen. De term werd populair door de Game Boy van Nintendo en het succes van spellen zoals Tetris, die op afzonderlijke consoles werden gespeeld.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>Kabel łączący to zastrzeżony kabel, który umożliwia połączenie dwóch lub więcej przenośnych konsol do gier wideo w celu wymiany treści lub grania w gry na oddzielnych konsolach. Termin ten został spopularyzowany przez Game Boy firmy Nintendo i sukces gier takich jak Tetris, które były odtwarzane na oddzielnych konsolach.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>O cabo de ligação é um cabo proprietário que permite que duas ou mais consolas de jogos de vídeo portáteis sejam ligadas entre si para trocar conteúdos ou jogar jogos em consolas separadas. O termo foi popularizado pelo Game Boy da Nintendo e o sucesso de jogos como o Tetris, que eram jogados em consolas separadas.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>Кабель связи - это проприетарный кабель, позволяющий соединить две или более портативных игровых консолей для обмена контентом или игр на отдельных консолях. Этот термин стал популярен благодаря Game Boy от Nintendo и успеху таких игр, как Tetris, в которые играли на отдельных консолях.</text>
</text>


<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Tetris (1989)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>The black-and-white Tetris block embodies the perfect simplicity of the Game Boy puzzle, where each piece must find its place before the screen fills up. The shapes fall without pause, demanding anticipation, reflexes and careful space management. This figurine highlights the game's monochrome look and its major role in the handheld's identity.
Fun fact: Two-player mode used the Link Cable, sending lines to the opponent after several rows were cleared.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Le bloc de Tetris noir et blanc incarne la simplicité parfaite du puzzle Game Boy, où chaque pièce doit trouver sa place avant que l’écran ne se remplisse. Les formes tombent sans pause, imposant anticipation, réflexes et gestion de l’espace. Cette figurine met en avant l’esthétique monochrome du jeu et son rôle majeur dans l’identité de la console portable.
Fun fact : Le mode deux joueurs utilisait le câble Link, avec des lignes envoyées à l’adversaire après plusieurs rangées effacées.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>El bloque en blanco y negro de Tetris encarna la simplicidad perfecta del puzle de Game Boy, donde cada pieza debe encontrar su lugar antes de que la pantalla se llene. Las formas caen sin pausa, exigiendo anticipación, reflejos y gestión del espacio. Esta figura destaca el aspecto monocromo del juego y su papel clave en la identidad de la portátil.
Dato curioso: El modo para dos jugadores usaba el Cable Link, enviando líneas al rival tras borrar varias filas.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Il blocco in bianco e nero di Tetris incarna la semplicità perfetta del puzzle per Game Boy, dove ogni pezzo deve trovare posto prima che lo schermo si riempia. Le forme cadono senza pausa, richiedendo anticipo, riflessi e gestione dello spazio. Questa figurina evidenzia l’estetica monocromatica del gioco e il suo ruolo nell’identità della portatile.
Curiosità: La modalità a due giocatori usava il cavo Link, inviando linee all’avversario dopo più righe eliminate.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Der schwarzweiße Tetris-Block verkörpert die perfekte Schlichtheit des Game-Boy-Puzzles, in dem jedes Teil seinen Platz finden muss, bevor der Bildschirm vollläuft. Die Formen fallen pausenlos und verlangen Voraussicht, Reflexe und Raumkontrolle. Diese Figur betont den monochromen Look des Spiels und seine große Rolle für die Identität des Handhelds.
Interessante Tatsache: Der Zweispielermodus nutzte das Link-Kabel und schickte nach mehreren gelöschten Reihen Linien zum Gegner.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>O bloco em preto e branco de Tetris encarna a simplicidade perfeita do puzzle no Game Boy, onde cada peça precisa encontrar seu lugar antes que a tela se encha. As formas caem sem pausa, exigindo antecipação, reflexos e controle do espaço. Esta figurine destaca o visual monocromático do jogo e seu papel central na identidade do portátil.
Curiosidade: O modo para dois jogadores usava o Cabo Link, enviando linhas ao adversário após várias filas eliminadas.</text>
</text>


</view>
</theme>
