<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>The Game Boy Advance is a portable video game console with a colour screen and a 32-bit processor, which made it the most powerful portable console when it was released. The GBA is not zoned, so it is possible to play American and Japanese games on a European console and vice versa. It is backwards compatible with GB and GBC games.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>La Game Boy Advance est une console de jeux vidéo portable avec un écran couleur et un processeur 32-bits, ce qui en faisait à sa sortie la console portable la plus performante. La GBA n'étant pas zonée, il est possible de jouer à des jeux américains et japonais sur une console européenne et vice versa. Elle est rétrocompatible avec les jeux GB et GBC.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Der Game Boy Advance ist eine tragbare Videospielkonsole mit einem Farbbildschirm und einem 32-Bit-Prozessor, was ihn bei seiner Veröffentlichung zur leistungsfähigsten tragbaren Konsole machte. Da der GBA nicht zonenabhängig ist, kann man auf einer europäischen Konsole amerikanische und japanische Spiele spielen und umgekehrt. Er ist abwärtskompatibel mit GB- und GBC-Spielen.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>La Game Boy Advance es una videoconsola portátil con pantalla en color y procesador de 32 bits, lo que la convirtió en la consola portátil más potente en el momento de su lanzamiento. La GBA no está dividida en zonas, por lo que es posible jugar a juegos americanos y japoneses en una consola europea y viceversa. Es retrocompatible con los juegos de GB y GBC.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Il Game Boy Advance è una console portatile per videogiochi con schermo a colori e processore a 32 bit, che al momento dell'uscita era la console portatile più potente. Il GBA non è suddiviso in zone, quindi è possibile giocare a giochi americani e giapponesi su una console europea e viceversa. È retrocompatibile con i giochi GB e GBC.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>ゲームボーイアドバンスは、カラー画面と32ビットプロセッサを搭載した携帯ゲーム機で、発売当時は最も高性能な携帯ゲーム機でした。GBAはゾーニングされていないため、ヨーロッパのゲーム機でアメリカや日本のゲームをプレイすることも、その逆も可能である。GBやGBCのゲームと後方互換性があります。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>De Game Boy Advance is een draagbare videogameconsole met een kleurenscherm en een 32-bits processor, waardoor het de krachtigste draagbare console was toen hij werd uitgebracht. De GBA is niet gezoneerd, zodat het mogelijk is Amerikaanse en Japanse spellen op een Europese console te spelen en omgekeerd. Het is achterwaarts compatibel met GB en GBC spellen.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>Game Boy Advance to przenośna konsola do gier wideo z kolorowym ekranem i 32-bitowym procesorem, co czyniło ją najpotężniejszą przenośną konsolą w momencie premiery. GBA nie jest podzielona na strefy, więc możliwe jest granie w amerykańskie i japońskie gry na europejskiej konsoli i odwrotnie. Jest ona wstecznie kompatybilna z grami na GB i GBC.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>A Game Boy Advance é uma consola portátil de videojogos com um ecrã a cores e um processador de 32 bits, o que a tornou na consola portátil mais poderosa quando foi lançada. A GBA não está zonada, pelo que é possível jogar jogos americanos e japoneses numa consola europeia e vice-versa. É retrocompatível com jogos GB e GBC.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>Game Boy Advance - это портативная игровая консоль с цветным экраном и 32-битным процессором, что сделало ее самой мощной портативной консолью на момент выпуска. Поскольку GBA не зонирована, на европейской консоли можно играть в американские и японские игры и наоборот. Она обратно совместима с играми для GB и GBC.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;WarioWare, Inc.: Mega Microgame$! (2003) &#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>Mona is an energetic high school student who juggles unlikely part-time jobs while taking part in Wario’s frantic microgames. As a pizza delivery rider, aspiring idol or waitress, she keeps moving even when the world around her turns chaotic. Her upbeat attitude, quick reactions and recurring animal friends make her one of the most recognizable faces in the WarioWare series.
Fun fact: Mona is often helped by her animals, including a monkey and a dog, who appear in several of her WarioWare microgame stages.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Mona est une lycéenne énergique qui enchaîne les petits boulots improbables tout en participant aux microgames déjantés de Wario. Livreuse de pizza, idole en devenir ou serveuse, elle garde toujours son sang-froid malgré le chaos ambiant. Sa personnalité spontanée, son rythme nerveux et ses amis animaux en font l’un des visages les plus reconnaissables de WarioWare.
Fun fact : Mona est souvent aidée par ses animaux, dont un singe et un chien, qui apparaissent dans plusieurs de ses séquences de microgames.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Mona es una estudiante enérgica que encadena trabajos a tiempo parcial muy improbables mientras participa en los frenéticos microjuegos de Wario. Como repartidora de pizza, aspirante a ídolo o camarera, sigue adelante incluso cuando todo a su alrededor se vuelve caótico. Su actitud alegre, sus reflejos rápidos y sus amigos animales la convierten en una de las caras más reconocibles de WarioWare.
Dato curioso: Mona suele recibir ayuda de sus animales, entre ellos un mono y un perro, que aparecen en varias de sus fases de microjuegos.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Mona è una studentessa energica che passa da un lavoro part-time improbabile all’altro mentre partecipa ai frenetici microgame di Wario. Come fattorina della pizza, aspirante idol o cameriera, continua a muoversi anche quando tutto intorno diventa caotico. Il suo carattere solare, i riflessi rapidi e gli amici animali la rendono uno dei volti più riconoscibili di WarioWare.
Curiosità: Mona viene spesso aiutata dai suoi animali, tra cui una scimmia e un cane, presenti in diverse sue sequenze di microgame.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Mona ist eine energiegeladene Schülerin, die ungewöhnliche Nebenjobs übernimmt und zugleich an Warios hektischen Mikrospielen teilnimmt. Als Pizzalieferantin, angehender Popstar oder Kellnerin bleibt sie selbst dann in Bewegung, wenn um sie herum alles chaotisch wird. Ihre fröhliche Art, schnellen Reaktionen und tierischen Begleiter machen sie zu einem der bekanntesten Gesichter von WarioWare.
Interessante Tatsache: Mona wird oft von ihren Tieren unterstützt, darunter ein Affe und ein Hund, die in mehreren ihrer Mikrospiel-Abschnitte auftreten.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Mona é uma estudante cheia de energia que acumula trabalhos temporários improváveis enquanto participa nos microjogos frenéticos de Wario. Como entregadora de pizza, aspirante a ídolo ou empregada de mesa, ela continua em movimento mesmo quando tudo à sua volta fica caótico. A sua atitude alegre, reflexos rápidos e amigos animais fazem dela uma das caras mais reconhecíveis de WarioWare.
Curiosidade: Mona é muitas vezes ajudada pelos seus animais, incluindo um macaco e um cão, que aparecem em várias das suas fases de microjogos.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
