<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>The Game Boy Color (ゲームボーイカラー), abbreviated GBC, is the successor portable video game console to the Game Boy. It incorporates a colour screen only slightly larger than that of the GB. However, its processor is twice as fast, and its memory twice as large. It is backwards compatible with all first generation GB games.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>La Game Boy Color (ゲームボーイカラー), abrégé GBC, est la console de jeux vidéo portable succédant à la Game Boy. Elle incorpore un écran couleur à peine plus grand que celui de la GB. En revanche, son processeur est deux fois plus rapide, et sa mémoire deux fois plus grande. Elle est rétrocompatible avec tous les jeux GB de première génération.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Der Game Boy Color (ゲームボーイカラー), kurz GBC, ist die tragbare Videospielkonsole als Nachfolger des Game Boy. Sie enthält einen Farbbildschirm, der nur wenig größer ist als der des GB. Dafür ist der Prozessor doppelt so schnell und der Speicher doppelt so groß. Er ist abwärtskompatibel mit allen GB-Spielen der ersten Generation.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>La Game Boy Color (ゲームボーイカラー), abreviada GBC, es la videoconsola portátil sucesora de la Game Boy. Incorpora una pantalla en color sólo ligeramente mayor que la de la GB. Sin embargo, su procesador es el doble de rápido y su memoria el doble de grande. Es retrocompatible con todos los juegos de la primera generación de GB.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Il Game Boy Color (ゲームボーイカラー), abbreviato GBC, è la console portatile per videogiochi successore del Game Boy. Incorpora uno schermo a colori solo leggermente più grande di quello del GB. Tuttavia, il processore è due volte più veloce e la memoria due volte più capiente. È retrocompatibile con tutti i giochi GB di prima generazione.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>ゲームボーイカラー（ゲームボーイカラー）、略称GBCは、ゲームボーイの後継の携帯ゲーム機である。GBよりわずかに大きいカラースクリーンを搭載しています。しかし、プロセッサーは2倍速く、メモリは2倍大きくなっています。GBの全ゲームソフトと後方互換性がある。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>De Game Boy Color (ゲームボーイカラー), afgekort GBC, is de opvolger van de Game Boy. Het heeft een kleurenscherm dat slechts iets groter is dan dat van de GB. De processor is echter twee keer zo snel en het geheugen twee keer zo groot. Hij is compatibel met alle GB-spellen van de eerste generatie.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>Game Boy Color (ゲームボーイカラー), w skrócie GBC, to następca przenośnej konsoli do gier wideo Game Boy. Posiada kolorowy ekran tylko nieznacznie większy od tego z GB. Jednak jego procesor jest dwa razy szybszy, a pamięć dwa razy większa. Jest wstecznie kompatybilny z wszystkimi grami GB pierwszej generacji.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>O Game Boy Color (ゲームボーイカラー), abreviado GBC, é a consola de videojogos portátil sucessora do Game Boy. Incorpora um ecrã a cores apenas ligeiramente maior do que o da GB. No entanto, o seu processador é duas vezes mais rápido, e a sua memória duas vezes maior. É retrocompatível com todos os jogos GB da primeira geração.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>Game Boy Color (ゲームボーイカラー), сокращенно GBC, является преемником портативной игровой консоли Game Boy. Она оснащена цветным экраном, который лишь немного больше, чем у GB. Однако его процессор в два раза быстрее, а память в два раза больше. Она обратно совместима со всеми играми первого поколения GB.</text>
</text>


<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Wario Land 3 (2000)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>Wario is Mario’s greedy and selfish rival, known for his brute strength and obsession with gold. In Wario Land 3, he explores a strange world trapped inside a music box, where transformations caused by enemies often become the key to progressing, opening new paths and recovering treasures in stages that must be revisited several times.
Fun fact: Unlike many platform games, Wario cannot die in Wario Land 3; he is only pushed back or transformed.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Wario est le rival cupide et égoïste de Mario, connu pour sa force brute et son obsession pour l’or. Dans Wario Land 3, il explore un monde étrange enfermé dans une boîte à musique, où ses transformations provoquées par les ennemis deviennent souvent la clé pour progresser, ouvrir de nouveaux passages et récupérer des trésors dans des niveaux à revisiter plusieurs fois.
Fun fact : Contrairement à beaucoup de jeux de plates-formes, Wario ne peut pas mourir dans Wario Land 3, il est seulement repoussé ou transformé.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Wario es el rival codicioso y egoísta de Mario, conocido por su fuerza bruta y su obsesión por el oro. En Wario Land 3, explora un mundo extraño encerrado dentro de una caja de música, donde las transformaciones provocadas por los enemigos suelen ser la clave para avanzar, abrir nuevos caminos y recuperar tesoros en niveles que se revisitan varias veces.
Dato curioso: A diferencia de muchos juegos de plataformas, Wario no puede morir en Wario Land 3; solo es empujado hacia atrás o transformado.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Wario è il rivale avido ed egoista di Mario, noto per la sua forza bruta e la sua ossessione per l’oro. In Wario Land 3 esplora uno strano mondo rinchiuso in un carillon, dove le trasformazioni causate dai nemici diventano spesso la chiave per avanzare, aprire nuovi passaggi e recuperare tesori in livelli da rivisitare più volte.
Curiosità: A differenza di molti giochi di piattaforme, Wario non può morire in Wario Land 3; viene solo respinto o trasformato.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Wario ist Marios gieriger und egoistischer Rivale, bekannt für rohe Kraft und seine Besessenheit von Gold. In Wario Land 3 erkundet er eine seltsame Welt in einer Spieluhr, in der Verwandlungen durch Gegner oft der Schlüssel sind, um voranzukommen, neue Wege zu öffnen und Schätze in mehrfach besuchten Leveln zu finden.
Interessante Tatsache: Anders als in vielen Jump-and-Run-Spielen kann Wario in Wario Land 3 nicht sterben; er wird nur zurückgeworfen oder verwandelt.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Wario é o rival ganancioso e egoísta de Mario, conhecido pela sua força bruta e obsessão por ouro. Em Wario Land 3, explora um mundo estranho preso dentro de uma caixa de música, onde as transformações causadas pelos inimigos muitas vezes são a chave para avançar, abrir novos caminhos e recuperar tesouros em níveis revisitados várias vezes.
Curiosidade: Ao contrário de muitos jogos de plataformas, Wario não pode morrer em Wario Land 3; ele apenas é empurrado para trás ou transformado.</text>
</text>
</view>
</theme>
