<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>Already present on the Game Boy, the link cable makes its return to allow the appearance of many features including multiplayer games and Pokémon exchange. This accessory is also compatible with the Game Boy Pocket.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Déjà présent sur la Game Boy, le câble link fait son retour pour permettre l'apparition de nombreuses fonctionnalités dont notamment les parties multijoueur et l'échange de Pokémon. Cet accessoire est également compatible avec la Game Boy Pocket.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Das Link-Kabel, das es schon auf dem Game Boy gab, ist nun wieder da und ermöglicht viele neue Funktionen, wie z. B. Mehrspielerpartien und den Austausch von Pokémon. Dieses Zubehör ist auch mit dem Game Boy Pocket kompatibel.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Ya presente en la Game Boy, el cable de enlace hace su regreso para permitir la aparición de numerosas funciones, como las partidas multijugador y el intercambio de Pokémon. Este accesorio también es compatible con la Game Boy Pocket.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Già presente sul Game Boy, il cavo di collegamento fa il suo ritorno per consentire la comparsa di molte funzioni, tra cui i giochi multiplayer e lo scambio di Pokémon. Questo accessorio è compatibile anche con il Game Boy Pocket.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>ゲームボーイに搭載されていたリンクケーブルが復活し、多人数プレイやポケモン交換など、様々な機能を搭載しています。ゲームボーイポケットにも対応しています。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>De linkkabel, die al aanwezig was op de Game Boy, maakt zijn terugkeer mogelijk, zodat vele functies, zoals multiplayer-spelletjes en Pokémon-uitwisseling, kunnen worden toegepast. Dit accessoire is ook compatibel met de Game Boy Pocket.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>Obecny już w Game Boyu, kabel łączący powraca, aby umożliwić pojawienie się wielu funkcji, w tym gier wieloosobowych i wymiany Pokémonów. To akcesorium jest również kompatybilne z Game Boy Pocket.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Já presente no Game Boy, o cabo de ligação faz o seu regresso para permitir o aparecimento de muitas características, incluindo jogos multijogadores e troca de Pokémon. Este acessório é também compatível com o Game Boy Pocket.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>Уже присутствовавший в Game Boy, соединительный кабель возвращается, чтобы обеспечить появление многих функций, включая многопользовательские игры и обмен покемонами. Этот аксессуар также совместим с Game Boy Pocket.</text>
</text>


<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Snoopy Tennis (2001)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>Snoopy steps onto the court with racket in hand in a colorful tennis game built for quick one- or two-player matches. Rallies stay easy to read, with several modes and characters from the Peanuts universe. This figurine highlights his sporty, light and expressive side, well suited to the friendly spirit of the Game Boy Color.
Fun fact: Two-player mode uses the Link Cable, letting two Game Boy Color systems compete with each player on their own screen.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Snoopy entre sur le court raquette en main dans un jeu de tennis coloré pensé pour des matchs rapides à un ou deux joueurs. Les échanges restent simples à lire, avec plusieurs modes et des personnages issus de l’univers Peanuts. Cette figurine met en avant son côté sportif, léger et expressif, parfaitement adapté à l’esprit convivial du Game Boy Color.
Fun fact : Le mode deux joueurs utilise le câble Link, permettant à deux Game Boy Color de s’affronter chacun sur son écran.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Snoopy entra en la pista con la raqueta en la mano en un juego de tenis colorido pensado para partidos rápidos de uno o dos jugadores. Los intercambios son fáciles de seguir, con varios modos y personajes del universo Peanuts. Esta figurina destaca su lado deportivo, ligero y expresivo, muy acorde con el espíritu amistoso de Game Boy Color.
Dato curioso: El modo para dos jugadores usa el Cable Link, permitiendo que dos Game Boy Color compitan cada uno en su propia pantalla.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Snoopy scende in campo con la racchetta in mano in un gioco di tennis colorato pensato per partite rapide a uno o due giocatori. Gli scambi restano facili da leggere, con varie modalità e personaggi dell’universo Peanuts. Questa figurina mette in risalto il suo lato sportivo, leggero ed espressivo, adatto allo spirito conviviale del Game Boy Color.
Curiosità: La modalità a due giocatori usa il cavo Link, permettendo a due Game Boy Color di sfidarsi ognuno sul proprio schermo.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Snoopy betritt mit dem Schläger in der Hand den Platz in einem farbenfrohen Tennisspiel für schnelle Matches allein oder zu zweit. Die Ballwechsel bleiben leicht lesbar, mit mehreren Modi und Figuren aus dem Peanuts-Universum. Diese Figur betont seine sportliche, lockere und ausdrucksstarke Seite, passend zum geselligen Geist des Game Boy Color.
Interessante Tatsache: Der Zweispielermodus nutzt das Link-Kabel, sodass zwei Game Boy Color jeweils auf eigenem Bildschirm gegeneinander antreten.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Snoopy entra no court com a raquete na mão em um jogo de tênis colorido feito para partidas rápidas de um ou dois jogadores. As trocas são fáceis de acompanhar, com vários modos e personagens do universo Peanuts. Esta figurine destaca seu lado esportivo, leve e expressivo, bem adequado ao espírito amigável do Game Boy Color.
Curiosidade: O modo para dois jogadores usa o Cabo Link, permitindo que dois Game Boy Color se enfrentem cada um em sua própria tela.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
