<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>The GameCube (ニンテンドーゲームキューブ), is a home video game console developed in association with IBM, NEC and ATI. It competed with the PS2, Xbox and Dreamcast. Despite its excellent games, the GameCube did not meet the success of its predecessors, with only 5 years in the game console market.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>La GameCube (ニンテンドーゲームキューブ), est une console de jeux vidéo de salon développée en association avec IBM, NEC et ATI. Elle fut en concurrence avec la PS2, la Xbox et la Dreamcast. Malgré ses excellents jeux, la GameCube ne rencontre pas le succès de ses devancières, avec seulement 5 ans d'existence sur le marché des consoles de jeux.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Der GameCube (ニンテンドーゲームキューブ), ist eine Videospielkonsole für den Heimgebrauch, die in Zusammenarbeit mit IBM, NEC und ATI entwickelt wurde. Sie konkurrierte mit der PS2, der Xbox und der Dreamcast. Trotz seiner hervorragenden Spiele war der GameCube nicht so erfolgreich wie seine Vorgänger und hatte nur 5 Jahre auf dem Markt für Spielkonsolen.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>La GameCube (ニンテンドーゲームキューブ), es una videoconsola doméstica desarrollada en asociación con IBM, NEC y ATI. Compitió con la PS2, la Xbox y la Dreamcast. A pesar de sus excelentes juegos, la GameCube no alcanzó el éxito de sus predecesoras, con sólo 5 años en el mercado de las videoconsolas.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Il GameCube (ニンテンドーゲームキューブ), è una console per videogiochi domestici sviluppata in associazione con IBM, NEC e ATI. Era in concorrenza con PS2, Xbox e Dreamcast. Nonostante i suoi eccellenti giochi, il GameCube non ha riscosso il successo dei suoi predecessori, rimanendo sul mercato delle console per videogiochi per soli 5 anni.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>ゲームキューブ（ニンテンドーゲームキューブ）は、IBM、NEC、ATIの3社が共同で開発した家庭用ゲーム機である。PS2、Xbox、Dreamcastと競合していた。ゲームキューブは、その優れたゲームにもかかわらず、ゲーム機市場でわずか5年で、先代の成功には至りませんでした。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>De GameCube (ニンテンドーゲームキューブ), is een spelcomputer voor thuisgebruik, ontwikkeld in samenwerking met IBM, NEC en ATI. Het concurreerde met de PS2, Xbox en Dreamcast. Ondanks de uitstekende spellen, haalde de GameCube niet het succes van zijn voorgangers, met slechts 5 jaar op de spelconsole markt.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>GameCube (ニンテンドーゲームキューブ), to domowa konsola do gier wideo opracowana we współpracy z IBM, NEC i ATI. Konkurowała z PS2, Xboxem i Dreamcastem. Pomimo doskonałych gier, GameCube nie odniósł sukcesu swoich poprzedników, będąc zaledwie 5 lat na rynku konsol do gier.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>A GameCube (ニンテンドーゲームキューブ), é uma consola de videojogos doméstica desenvolvida em associação com a IBM, NEC e ATI. Competiu com a PS2, Xbox e Dreamcast. Apesar dos seus excelentes jogos, a GameCube não alcançou o sucesso dos seus antecessores, com apenas 5 anos no mercado das consolas de jogos.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>GameCube (ニンテンドーゲームキューブ) - домашняя игровая приставка, разработанная совместно компаниями IBM, NEC и ATI. Она конкурировала с PS2, Xbox и Dreamcast. Несмотря на отличные игры, GameCube не достигла успеха своих предшественниц и продержалась на рынке игровых консолей всего 5 лет.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Resident Evil 4 (2005)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>
<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>Ada Wong appears here in her iconic red dress, which strongly contrasts with the hostile rural setting of the game. Cold, precise and withdrawn, she acts according to her own interests and manipulates events without ever revealing herself. Her relationship with Leon remains ambiguous, shifting between occasional help and personal goals tied to Las Plagas.
Fun fact: The Separate Ways mode, focused on Ada Wong, was not present in the original GameCube version and was added in later versions of the game.</text>
</text>
<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Ada Wong apparaît ici dans sa robe rouge emblématique qui contraste fortement avec l’environnement rural hostile du jeu. Froide, précise et en retrait, elle agit selon ses propres intérêts et manipule les événements sans jamais se dévoiler. Sa relation avec Leon reste ambiguë, oscillant entre aide ponctuelle et objectifs personnels liés aux enjeux autour de Las Plagas.
Fun fact : Le mode Separate Ways, centré sur Ada Wong, n’était pas présent dans la version GameCube d’origine et a été ajouté dans les versions suivantes du jeu.</text>
</text>
<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Ada Wong aparece aquí con su icónico vestido rojo, que contrasta con fuerza con el entorno rural hostil del juego. Fría, precisa y reservada, actúa según sus propios intereses y manipula los acontecimientos sin revelarse por completo. Su relación con Leon sigue siendo ambigua, entre ayudas puntuales y objetivos personales ligados a Las Plagas.
Dato curioso: El modo Separate Ways, centrado en Ada Wong, no estaba presente en la versión original de GameCube y se añadió en versiones posteriores del juego.</text>
</text>
<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Ada Wong appare qui con il suo iconico abito rosso, che contrasta nettamente con l’ambiente rurale ostile del gioco. Fredda, precisa e riservata, agisce secondo i propri interessi e manipola gli eventi senza rivelarsi mai del tutto. Il suo rapporto con Leon resta ambiguo, tra aiuti occasionali e obiettivi personali legati a Las Plagas.
Curiosità: La modalità Separate Ways, incentrata su Ada Wong, non era presente nella versione originale GameCube ed è stata aggiunta nelle versioni successive del gioco.</text>
</text>
<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Ada Wong erscheint hier in ihrem ikonischen roten Kleid, das stark mit der feindseligen ländlichen Umgebung des Spiels kontrastiert. Kühl, präzise und zurückhaltend verfolgt sie eigene Interessen und lenkt die Ereignisse, ohne sich vollständig zu offenbaren. Ihre Beziehung zu Leon bleibt zweideutig, zwischen gelegentlicher Hilfe und eigenen Zielen rund um Las Plagas.
Interessante Tatsache: Der auf Ada Wong ausgerichtete Modus Separate Ways war in der ursprünglichen GameCube-Version nicht enthalten und wurde in späteren Versionen des Spiels ergänzt.</text>
</text>
<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Ada Wong surge aqui com o seu icónico vestido vermelho, que contrasta fortemente com o ambiente rural hostil do jogo. Fria, precisa e reservada, age de acordo com os seus próprios interesses e manipula os acontecimentos sem se revelar por completo. A sua relação com Leon permanece ambígua, entre ajuda ocasional e objetivos pessoais ligados a Las Plagas.
Curiosidade: O modo Separate Ways, centrado em Ada Wong, não estava presente na versão original de GameCube e foi adicionado em versões posteriores do jogo.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
