<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>The GameCube (ニンテンドーゲームキューブ), is a home video game console developed in association with IBM, NEC and ATI. It competed with the PS2, Xbox and Dreamcast. Despite its excellent games, the GameCube did not meet the success of its predecessors, with only 5 years in the game console market.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>La GameCube (ニンテンドーゲームキューブ), est une console de jeux vidéo de salon développée en association avec IBM, NEC et ATI. Elle fut en concurrence avec la PS2, la Xbox et la Dreamcast. Malgré ses excellents jeux, la GameCube ne rencontre pas le succès de ses devancières, avec seulement 5 ans d'existence sur le marché des consoles de jeux.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Der GameCube (ニンテンドーゲームキューブ), ist eine Videospielkonsole für den Heimgebrauch, die in Zusammenarbeit mit IBM, NEC und ATI entwickelt wurde. Sie konkurrierte mit der PS2, der Xbox und der Dreamcast. Trotz seiner hervorragenden Spiele war der GameCube nicht so erfolgreich wie seine Vorgänger und hatte nur 5 Jahre auf dem Markt für Spielkonsolen.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>La GameCube (ニンテンドーゲームキューブ), es una videoconsola doméstica desarrollada en asociación con IBM, NEC y ATI. Compitió con la PS2, la Xbox y la Dreamcast. A pesar de sus excelentes juegos, la GameCube no alcanzó el éxito de sus predecesoras, con sólo 5 años en el mercado de las videoconsolas.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Il GameCube (ニンテンドーゲームキューブ), è una console per videogiochi domestici sviluppata in associazione con IBM, NEC e ATI. Era in concorrenza con PS2, Xbox e Dreamcast. Nonostante i suoi eccellenti giochi, il GameCube non ha riscosso il successo dei suoi predecessori, rimanendo sul mercato delle console per videogiochi per soli 5 anni.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>ゲームキューブ（ニンテンドーゲームキューブ）は、IBM、NEC、ATIの3社が共同で開発した家庭用ゲーム機である。PS2、Xbox、Dreamcastと競合していた。ゲームキューブは、その優れたゲームにもかかわらず、ゲーム機市場でわずか5年で、先代の成功には至りませんでした。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>De GameCube (ニンテンドーゲームキューブ), is een spelcomputer voor thuisgebruik, ontwikkeld in samenwerking met IBM, NEC en ATI. Het concurreerde met de PS2, Xbox en Dreamcast. Ondanks de uitstekende spellen, haalde de GameCube niet het succes van zijn voorgangers, met slechts 5 jaar op de spelconsole markt.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>GameCube (ニンテンドーゲームキューブ), to domowa konsola do gier wideo opracowana we współpracy z IBM, NEC i ATI. Konkurowała z PS2, Xboxem i Dreamcastem. Pomimo doskonałych gier, GameCube nie odniósł sukcesu swoich poprzedników, będąc zaledwie 5 lat na rynku konsol do gier.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>A GameCube (ニンテンドーゲームキューブ), é uma consola de videojogos doméstica desenvolvida em associação com a IBM, NEC e ATI. Competiu com a PS2, Xbox e Dreamcast. Apesar dos seus excelentes jogos, a GameCube não alcançou o sucesso dos seus antecessores, com apenas 5 anos no mercado das consolas de jogos.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>GameCube (ニンテンドーゲームキューブ) - домашняя игровая приставка, разработанная совместно компаниями IBM, NEC и ATI. Она конкурировала с PS2, Xbox и Dreamcast. Несмотря на отличные игры, GameCube не достигла успеха своих предшественниц и продержалась на рынке игровых консолей всего 5 лет.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
