<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>Ghouls 'n Ghosts is a series of action-platform games developed by Capcom, in which the knight Arthur battles demonic creatures to save a princess. Known for its extreme difficulty, it requires precision and memorization of levels. Arthur can collect various weapons and improve his armor, but loses it at the first blow. The series is a retro-gaming mainstay, making its mark on history with its demanding gameplay and gothic atmosphere.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Ghouls 'n Ghosts est une série de jeux d'action-plateforme développée par Capcom, où le chevalier Arthur combat des créatures démoniaques pour sauver une princesse. Connue pour sa difficulté extrême, elle exige précision et mémorisation des niveaux. La série est un pilier du rétro-gaming, marquant l’histoire avec son gameplay exigeant et son ambiance gothique.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Ghouls 'n Ghosts es una serie de juegos de acción y plataformas desarrollada por Capcom, en la que el caballero Arthur combate criaturas demoníacas para salvar a una princesa. Conocida por su dificultad extrema, exige precisión y memorización de los niveles. Arthur puede recoger distintas armas y mejorar su armadura, pero la pierde al primer golpe. La serie es un pilar del retro-gaming, marcada por su jugabilidad exigente y su atmósfera gótica.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Ghouls 'n Ghosts è una serie di giochi d'azione e piattaforme sviluppata da Capcom, in cui il cavaliere Arthur combatte creature demoniache per salvare una principessa. Nota per la sua difficoltà estrema, richiede precisione e memorizzazione dei livelli. Arthur può raccogliere varie armi e migliorare la propria armatura, ma la perde al primo colpo. La serie è un pilastro del retro-gaming, ricordata per il gameplay esigente e l'atmosfera gotica.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Ghouls 'n Ghosts ist eine Action-Plattformspielreihe von Capcom, in der der Ritter Arthur gegen dämonische Kreaturen kämpft, um eine Prinzessin zu retten. Bekannt für ihren extremen Schwierigkeitsgrad, verlangt sie Präzision und das Auswendiglernen der Level. Arthur kann verschiedene Waffen sammeln und seine Rüstung verbessern, verliert sie jedoch beim ersten Treffer. Die Reihe ist ein fester Bestandteil des Retro-Gaming, geprägt von anspruchsvollem Gameplay und gotischer Atmosphäre.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Ghouls 'n Ghosts é uma série de jogos de ação e plataforma desenvolvida pela Capcom, na qual o cavaleiro Arthur enfrenta criaturas demoníacas para salvar uma princesa. Conhecida por sua dificuldade extrema, exige precisão e memorização das fases. Arthur pode coletar várias armas e melhorar sua armadura, mas a perde no primeiro golpe. A série é um pilar do retro-gaming, marcada por sua jogabilidade exigente e sua atmosfera gótica.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Ghouls'n Ghosts (Arcade, 1988)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>Arthur is a knight facing hordes of demons to save the princess, recognizable by his emblematic armor that shatters at the slightest hit, leaving him vulnerable, a symbol of a demanding challenge where every mistake is punished and perseverance is essential to progress through a hostile and unforgiving world.
Fun fact: To see the true ending of Ghouls'n Ghosts, the player must finish the game twice, a famous series mechanic that reinforces its reputation for extreme difficulty.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Arthur est un chevalier affrontant des hordes de démons pour sauver la princesse, reconnaissable à son armure emblématique qui vole en éclats au moindre coup, le laissant vulnérable, symbole d’un défi exigeant où chaque erreur est punie et où la persévérance est essentielle pour progresser dans un monde hostile et impitoyable.
Fun fact : Pour voir la vraie fin de Ghouls'n Ghosts, le joueur doit terminer le jeu deux fois, une mécanique célèbre de la série qui renforce sa réputation de difficulté extrême.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Arthur es un caballero que enfrenta hordas de demonios para salvar a la princesa, reconocible por su armadura emblemática que se rompe al menor golpe y lo deja vulnerable, símbolo de un desafío exigente donde cada error se castiga y la perseverancia es esencial para avanzar en un mundo hostil e implacable.
Dato curioso: Para ver el verdadero final de Ghouls'n Ghosts, el jugador debe terminar el juego dos veces, una mecánica famosa de la serie que refuerza su reputación de dificultad extrema.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Arthur è un cavaliere che affronta orde di demoni per salvare la principessa, riconoscibile dalla sua armatura emblematica che va in pezzi al minimo colpo lasciandolo vulnerabile, simbolo di una sfida impegnativa in cui ogni errore viene punito e la perseveranza è essenziale per avanzare in un mondo ostile e spietato.
Curiosità: Per vedere il vero finale di Ghouls'n Ghosts, il giocatore deve completare il gioco due volte, una celebre meccanica della serie che rafforza la sua fama di difficoltà estrema.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Arthur ist ein Ritter, der Horden von Dämonen bekämpft, um die Prinzessin zu retten. Er ist an seiner ikonischen Rüstung erkennbar, die beim kleinsten Treffer zerbricht und ihn verwundbar zurücklässt, ein Symbol für eine harte Herausforderung, in der jeder Fehler bestraft wird und Ausdauer nötig ist, um in einer feindseligen Welt voranzukommen.
Interessante Tatsache: Um das wahre Ende von Ghouls'n Ghosts zu sehen, muss der Spieler das Spiel zweimal beenden, eine berühmte Mechanik der Reihe, die ihren Ruf extremer Schwierigkeit stärkt.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Arthur é um cavaleiro que enfrenta hordas de demônios para salvar a princesa, reconhecível por sua armadura emblemática que se despedaça ao menor golpe e o deixa vulnerável, símbolo de um desafio exigente em que cada erro é punido e a perseverança é essencial para avançar em um mundo hostil e implacável.
Curiosidade: Para ver o verdadeiro final de Ghouls'n Ghosts, o jogador precisa terminar o jogo duas vezes, uma mecânica famosa da série que reforça sua reputação de dificuldade extrema.</text>
</text>


</view>
</theme>
