<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>The Game Master is a portable game console manufactured by Hartung and designed to compete with the Nintendo Game Boy. It has a 64 x 64 monochrome LCD screen and uses a 40-pin cartridge port like the Supervision but is not compatible with it. Depending on the country there were quite a few different manufacturers.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Le Game Master est une console de jeu portable fabriquée par Hartung et conçue pour concurrencer le Nintendo Game Boy. Elle dispose d'un écran LCD monochrome de 64 x 64 et utilise un port de cartouche à 40 broches comme le Supervision mais n'est pas compatible avec celle-ci. Suivant le pays il y a eu pas mal de fabriquant différents.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Der Game Master ist eine tragbare Spielkonsole, die von Hartung hergestellt wurde und mit dem Nintendo Game Boy konkurrieren soll. Sie hat einen 64 x 64 monochromen LCD-Bildschirm und verwendet einen 40-poligen Cartridge-Anschluss wie die Supervision, ist aber nicht mit dieser kompatibel. Je nach Land gab es eine ganze Reihe verschiedener Hersteller.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>La Game Master es una videoconsola portátil fabricada por Hartung y diseñada para competir con la Nintendo Game Boy. Tiene una pantalla LCD monocroma de 64 x 64 y utiliza un puerto para cartuchos de 40 patillas, como la Supervision, pero no es compatible con ella. Dependiendo del país, hubo bastantes fabricantes diferentes.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Il Game Master è una console portatile prodotta da Hartung e progettata per competere con il Nintendo Game Boy. Ha uno schermo LCD monocromatico 64 x 64 e utilizza una porta per cartucce a 40 pin come il Supervision, ma non è compatibile con esso. A seconda del paese, esistevano diversi produttori.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>ゲームマスターは、任天堂のゲームボーイに対抗するために作られた、ハートン社製の携帯ゲーム機である。64×64のモノクロ液晶画面を持ち、スーパービジョンと同様に40ピンのカートリッジポートを使用するが、互換性はない。国によって、かなりの数のメーカーがありました。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>De Game Master is een draagbare spelconsole, vervaardigd door Hartung en ontworpen om te concurreren met de Nintendo Game Boy. Hij heeft een 64 x 64 monochroom LCD-scherm en gebruikt een 40-pins cartridge-poort zoals de Supervision, maar is er niet compatibel mee. Afhankelijk van het land waren er nogal wat verschillende fabrikanten.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>Game Master to przenośna konsola do gier wyprodukowana przez firmę Hartung i przeznaczona do konkurowania z Nintendo Game Boy. Posiada monochromatyczny ekran LCD o wymiarach 64 x 64 i korzysta z 40-pinowego portu kartridży jak Supervision, ale nie jest z nim kompatybilna. W zależności od kraju było sporo różnych producentów.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>O Game Master é uma consola de jogos portátil fabricada pela Hartung e concebida para competir com o Nintendo Game Boy. Tem um ecrã LCD monocromático de 64 x 64 e utiliza uma porta de cartucho de 40 pinos como a Supervisão, mas não é compatível com ela. Dependendo do país, existiam vários fabricantes diferentes.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>Game Master - это портативная игровая приставка, произведенная компанией Hartung и предназначенная для конкуренции с Nintendo Game Boy. Она имеет монохромный ЖК-экран размером 64 x 64 и использует 40-контактный порт для картриджей, как и Supervision, но не совместима с ней. В зависимости от страны существовало довольно много различных производителей.</text>
</text>


<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Go Bang! (1990)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>The Go Bang! stone represents the abstract duel at the heart of this Game Master board game, where every placement matters to form a line before the opponent. The figurine highlights a simple, round and readable piece, faithful to the console's monochrome style. It evokes a direct puzzle game based on anticipation, blocking and quick reading of the grid.
Fun fact: Go Bang! follows the gomoku principle, an alignment game where the goal is to form a row of five stones.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>La pierre de Go Bang! représente le duel abstrait au centre de ce jeu de plateau sur Game Master, où chaque placement compte pour former une ligne avant l’adversaire. La figurine met en valeur une pièce simple, ronde et lisible, fidèle à l’esprit monochrome de la console. Elle évoque un jeu de réflexion direct, basé sur l’anticipation, le blocage et la lecture rapide de la grille.
Fun fact : Go Bang! reprend le principe du gomoku, un jeu d’alignement où il faut former une rangée de cinq pierres.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>La piedra de Go Bang! representa el duelo abstracto en el centro de este juego de tablero para Game Master, donde cada colocación cuenta para formar una línea antes que el rival. La figura destaca una pieza simple, redonda y legible, fiel al estilo monocromo de la consola. Evoca un juego de lógica directo, basado en anticipación, bloqueo y lectura rápida de la cuadrícula.
Dato curioso: Go Bang! sigue el principio del gomoku, un juego de alineación donde hay que formar una fila de cinco piedras.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>La pietra di Go Bang! rappresenta il duello astratto al centro di questo gioco da tavolo per Game Master, dove ogni piazzamento conta per formare una linea prima dell’avversario. La statuetta valorizza un pezzo semplice, rotondo e leggibile, fedele allo stile monocromatico della console. Evoca un gioco logico diretto, basato su previsione, blocco e lettura rapida della griglia.
Curiosità: Go Bang! segue il principio del gomoku, un gioco di allineamento in cui bisogna formare una fila di cinque pietre.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Der Stein aus Go Bang! steht für das abstrakte Duell im Zentrum dieses Brettspiels auf Game Master, bei dem jede Platzierung zählt, um vor dem Gegner eine Linie zu bilden. Die Figur betont ein schlichtes, rundes und gut lesbares Spielstück, passend zum monochromen Stil der Konsole. Sie erinnert an ein direktes Denkspiel mit Vorausplanung, Blockieren und schnellem Erfassen des Gitters.
Interessante Tatsache: Go Bang! folgt dem Gomoku-Prinzip, bei dem eine Reihe aus fünf Steinen gebildet werden muss.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>A pedra de Go Bang! representa o duelo abstrato no centro deste jogo de tabuleiro para Game Master, onde cada colocação conta para formar uma linha antes do adversário. A figura destaca uma peça simples, redonda e legível, fiel ao estilo monocromático da consola. Evoca um jogo de lógica direto, baseado em antecipação, bloqueio e leitura rápida da grelha.
Curiosidade: Go Bang! segue o princípio do gomoku, um jogo de alinhamento em que é preciso formar uma fila de cinco pedras.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
