<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>The Game Master is a portable game console manufactured by Hartung and designed to compete with the Nintendo Game Boy. It has a 64 x 64 monochrome LCD screen and uses a 40-pin cartridge port like the Supervision but is not compatible with it. Depending on the country there were quite a few different manufacturers.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Le Game Master est une console de jeu portable fabriquée par Hartung et conçue pour concurrencer le Nintendo Game Boy. Elle dispose d'un écran LCD monochrome de 64 x 64 et utilise un port de cartouche à 40 broches comme le Supervision mais n'est pas compatible avec celle-ci. Suivant le pays il y a eu pas mal de fabriquant différents.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Der Game Master ist eine tragbare Spielkonsole, die von Hartung hergestellt wurde und mit dem Nintendo Game Boy konkurrieren soll. Sie hat einen 64 x 64 monochromen LCD-Bildschirm und verwendet einen 40-poligen Cartridge-Anschluss wie die Supervision, ist aber nicht mit dieser kompatibel. Je nach Land gab es eine ganze Reihe verschiedener Hersteller.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>La Game Master es una videoconsola portátil fabricada por Hartung y diseñada para competir con la Nintendo Game Boy. Tiene una pantalla LCD monocroma de 64 x 64 y utiliza un puerto para cartuchos de 40 patillas, como la Supervision, pero no es compatible con ella. Dependiendo del país, hubo bastantes fabricantes diferentes.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Il Game Master è una console portatile prodotta da Hartung e progettata per competere con il Nintendo Game Boy. Ha uno schermo LCD monocromatico 64 x 64 e utilizza una porta per cartucce a 40 pin come il Supervision, ma non è compatibile con esso. A seconda del paese, esistevano diversi produttori.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>ゲームマスターは、任天堂のゲームボーイに対抗するために作られた、ハートン社製の携帯ゲーム機である。64×64のモノクロ液晶画面を持ち、スーパービジョンと同様に40ピンのカートリッジポートを使用するが、互換性はない。国によって、かなりの数のメーカーがありました。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>De Game Master is een draagbare spelconsole, vervaardigd door Hartung en ontworpen om te concurreren met de Nintendo Game Boy. Hij heeft een 64 x 64 monochroom LCD-scherm en gebruikt een 40-pins cartridge-poort zoals de Supervision, maar is er niet compatibel mee. Afhankelijk van het land waren er nogal wat verschillende fabrikanten.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>Game Master to przenośna konsola do gier wyprodukowana przez firmę Hartung i przeznaczona do konkurowania z Nintendo Game Boy. Posiada monochromatyczny ekran LCD o wymiarach 64 x 64 i korzysta z 40-pinowego portu kartridży jak Supervision, ale nie jest z nim kompatybilna. W zależności od kraju było sporo różnych producentów.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>O Game Master é uma consola de jogos portátil fabricada pela Hartung e concebida para competir com o Nintendo Game Boy. Tem um ecrã LCD monocromático de 64 x 64 e utiliza uma porta de cartucho de 40 pinos como a Supervisão, mas não é compatível com ela. Dependendo do país, existiam vários fabricantes diferentes.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>Game Master - это портативная игровая приставка, произведенная компанией Hartung и предназначенная для конкуренции с Nintendo Game Boy. Она имеет монохромный ЖК-экран размером 64 x 64 и использует 40-контактный порт для картриджей, как и Supervision, но не совместима с ней. В зависимости от страны существовало довольно много различных производителей.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
