 <!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>GOG.com (Good Old Games) is a PC game distribution platform best known for offering DRM-free games, allowing players to download, install, and keep their games without online restrictions. It features both modern titles and classic games adapted to run on current systems, along with frequent sales and discounts.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>GOG.com (Good Old Games) est une plateforme de distribution de jeux vidéo sur PC, connue pour proposer des jeux sans DRM, ce qui signifie qu’ils peuvent être téléchargés, installés et conservés librement sans connexion obligatoire. Elle propose des jeux récents et classiques, souvent optimisés pour fonctionner sur les systèmes modernes, ainsi que des promotions régulières.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
	<text>GOG.com es una plataforma de distribución digital centrada en juegos de PC sin DRM.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
	<text>GOG.com è una piattaforma di distribuzione digitale focalizzata sui giochi PC senza DRM.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
	<text>GOG.com ist eine digitale Vertriebsplattform für DRM-freie PC-Spiele.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
	<text>GOG.com é uma plataforma de distribuição digital focada em jogos de PC sem DRM.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
	<text>&#160;&#160;The Elder Scrolls V: Skyrim (2011)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
	<text>Argonians are a reptilian race from the marshes of Black Marsh, recognizable by their lizard-like appearance and natural resistance to disease. In Skyrim, they can be played as a character with unique abilities such as underwater breathing and increased regeneration, setting them apart from other races in Tamriel.
Fun fact: Argonians can breathe underwater indefinitely, making them the only playable race with this ability from the start.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
	<text>Les Argoniens sont une race reptilienne originaire des marais de Black Marsh, reconnaissable à leur apparence de lézard humanoïde et à leur résistance naturelle aux maladies. Dans Skyrim, ils peuvent être incarnés comme personnage jouable, avec des capacités uniques comme la respiration sous l’eau et une régénération accrue. Leur culture et leur physiologie les distinguent fortement des autres peuples de Tamriel.
Fun fact : Les Argoniens peuvent respirer sous l’eau de manière illimitée, ce qui en fait la seule race jouable à posséder cette capacité dès le départ.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
	<text>Los argonianos son una raza reptiliana originaria de los pantanos de Black Marsh, reconocibles por su apariencia de lagarto humanoide y su resistencia natural a las enfermedades. En Skyrim, pueden ser jugados como personaje con habilidades únicas como respirar bajo el agua y una mayor regeneración.
Dato curioso: Los argonianos pueden respirar bajo el agua de forma ilimitada, siendo la única raza jugable con esta habilidad desde el inicio.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
	<text>Gli Argoniani sono una razza rettiliana originaria delle paludi di Black Marsh, riconoscibile per il loro aspetto da lucertola umanoide e la resistenza naturale alle malattie. In Skyrim possono essere giocati come personaggio con abilità uniche come respirare sott’acqua e una maggiore rigenerazione.
Curiosità: Gli Argoniani possono respirare sott’acqua senza limiti, rendendoli l’unica razza giocabile con questa capacità fin dall’inizio.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
	<text>Argonier sind eine reptilienartige Rasse aus den Sümpfen von Black Marsh, erkennbar an ihrem echsenartigen Aussehen und ihrer natürlichen Resistenz gegen Krankheiten. In Skyrim können sie als spielbarer Charakter gewählt werden und besitzen Fähigkeiten wie unbegrenztes Atmen unter Wasser und erhöhte Regeneration.
Interessante Tatsache: Argonier können unbegrenzt unter Wasser atmen und sind damit die einzige spielbare Rasse mit dieser Fähigkeit von Anfang an.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
	<text>Os argonianos são uma raça reptiliana originária dos pântanos de Black Marsh, reconhecidos por sua aparência de lagarto humanoide e resistência natural a doenças. Em Skyrim, podem ser jogados com habilidades únicas como respirar debaixo d’água e regeneração aumentada.
Curiosidade: Os argonianos podem respirar debaixo d’água indefinidamente, sendo a única raça jogável com essa habilidade desde o início.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
