<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>The GP32 (GamePark 32) is a South Korean portable game console. It has been distributed in some parts of Europe. Unlike other portable game consoles, which tend to be based on proprietary cartridges, the GP32 uses SmartMedia cards to store programs and data.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>La GP32 (GamePark 32) est une console de jeu portable sud-coréenne. Elle a été distribuée dans certaines régions d'Europe. Contrairement aux autres consoles de jeu portables, qui ont tendance à être basées sur des cartouches propriétaires, la GP32 utilise des cartes SmartMedia pour stocker les programmes et les données.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Die GP32 (GamePark 32) ist eine tragbare Spielkonsole aus Südkorea. Sie wurde in Teilen Europas vertrieben. Im Gegensatz zu anderen tragbaren Spielkonsolen, die tendenziell auf proprietären Cartridges basieren, verwendet die GP32 SmartMedia-Karten, um Programme und Daten zu speichern.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>La GP32 (GamePark 32) es una videoconsola portátil surcoreana. Se ha distribuido en partes de Europa. A diferencia de otras videoconsolas portátiles, que suelen basarse en cartuchos propietarios, la GP32 utiliza tarjetas SmartMedia para almacenar programas y datos.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Il GP32 (GamePark 32) è una console di gioco portatile sudcoreana. È stata distribuita in alcune parti d'Europa. A differenza di altre console portatili, che tendono a basarsi su cartucce proprietarie, il GP32 utilizza schede SmartMedia per memorizzare programmi e dati.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>GP32（GamePark 32）は、韓国の携帯ゲーム機である。欧州の一部で販売されている。他の携帯ゲーム機では、独自のカートリッジを使用することが多いのですが、GP32では、プログラムとデータの保存にスマートメディアカードを使用しています。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>De GP32 (GamePark 32) is een Zuid-Koreaanse draagbare spelconsole. Hij is in delen van Europa gedistribueerd. In tegenstelling tot andere draagbare spelconsoles, die meestal gebaseerd zijn op eigen cartridges, gebruikt de GP32 SmartMedia-kaarten om programma's en gegevens op te slaan.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>GP32 (GamePark 32) to południowokoreańska przenośna konsola do gier. Była ona dystrybuowana w niektórych częściach Europy. W przeciwieństwie do innych przenośnych konsol do gier, które zwykle opierają się na zastrzeżonych kartridżach, GP32 wykorzystuje karty SmartMedia do przechowywania programów i danych.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>O GP32 (GamePark 32) é uma consola de jogos portátil sul-coreana. Tem sido distribuída em partes da Europa. Ao contrário de outras consolas de jogos portáteis, que tendem a basear-se em cartuchos proprietários, a GP32 utiliza cartões SmartMedia para armazenar programas e dados.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>GP32 (GamePark 32) - это южнокорейская портативная игровая консоль. Она была распространена в некоторых странах Европы. В отличие от других портативных игровых консолей, которые обычно основаны на проприетарных картриджах, GP32 использует карты SmartMedia для хранения программ и данных.</text>
</text>


<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Her Knights (2002)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>Her Knights features one of the knights protecting Princess Lemian, forced to flee an arranged marriage. The character moves through a fast 2D beat'em up with quick attacks, heavy blows, guard moves and dodges. This figurine highlights the game's fantasy style, clear combat and arcade energy on GP32.
Fun fact: The game is also known as Her Knights: Forcing Break-Out and Her Knights: All for Princess.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Her Knights met en scène l’un des chevaliers venus protéger la princesse Lemian, forcée d’échapper à un mariage imposé. Le personnage avance dans un beat’em up 2D nerveux, avec attaques rapides, coups puissants, garde et esquives. Cette figurine souligne le style fantasy du jeu, ses combats lisibles et son énergie arcade sur GP32.
Fun fact : Le jeu est aussi connu sous les titres Her Knights: Forcing Break-Out et Her Knights: All for Princess.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Her Knights presenta a uno de los caballeros que protegen a la princesa Lemian, obligada a huir de un matrimonio impuesto. El personaje avanza en un beat'em up 2D ágil, con ataques rápidos, golpes fuertes, guardia y esquivas. Esta figura destaca el estilo fantasy del juego, sus combates claros y su energía arcade en GP32.
Dato curioso: El juego también se conoce como Her Knights: Forcing Break-Out y Her Knights: All for Princess.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Her Knights presenta uno dei cavalieri che proteggono la principessa Lemian, costretta a fuggire da un matrimonio imposto. Il personaggio avanza in un beat'em up 2D rapido, con attacchi veloci, colpi potenti, guardia e schivate. Questa statuetta evidenzia lo stile fantasy del gioco, i combattimenti chiari e l'energia arcade su GP32.
Curiosità: Il gioco è conosciuto anche come Her Knights: Forcing Break-Out e Her Knights: All for Princess.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Her Knights zeigt einen der Ritter, die Prinzessin Lemian beschützen, während sie vor einer aufgezwungenen Ehe flieht. Die Figur bewegt sich durch ein schnelles 2D-Beat'em-up mit raschen Angriffen, starken Schlägen, Abwehr und Ausweichmanövern. Diese Figur betont den Fantasy-Stil, klare Kämpfe und Arcade-Energie auf GP32.
Interessante Tatsache: Das Spiel ist auch als Her Knights: Forcing Break-Out und Her Knights: All for Princess bekannt.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Her Knights apresenta um dos cavaleiros que protegem a princesa Lemian, forçada a fugir de um casamento imposto. O personagem avança num beat'em up 2D rápido, com ataques velozes, golpes fortes, defesa e esquivas. Esta figura destaca o estilo fantasy do jogo, os combates claros e a energia arcade no GP32.
Curiosidade: O jogo também é conhecido como Her Knights: Forcing Break-Out e Her Knights: All for Princess.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
