<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>Grand Theft Auto (GTA) is a series of open-world action games created by Rockstar, in which players take on the role of criminals in fictional cities. Blending scripted missions with total freedom, the saga is known for its satirical humor, violence and varied gameplay. Each opus features a unique story inspired by gangster films and urban culture. GTA is one of the most influential and popular video game franchises.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Grand Theft Auto (GTA) est une série de jeux d’action en monde ouvert créée par Rockstar, où les joueurs incarnent des criminels évoluant dans des villes fictives. Mélangeant missions scénarisées et liberté totale, la saga est connue pour son humour satirique, sa violence et son gameplay varié. Chaque opus propose une histoire unique inspirée de films de gangsters et de la culture urbaine. GTA est l’une des franchises les plus influentes et populaires du jeu vidéo.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Grand Theft Auto (GTA) es una serie de juegos de acción en mundo abierto creada por Rockstar, en la que los jugadores encarnan a criminales en ciudades ficticias. Mezclando misiones guionizadas con libertad total, la saga es conocida por su humor satírico, violencia y jugabilidad variada. Cada entrega ofrece una historia propia inspirada en el cine de gánsteres y la cultura urbana. GTA es una de las franquicias más influyentes y populares del videojuego.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Grand Theft Auto (GTA) è una serie di giochi d’azione open world creata da Rockstar, in cui i giocatori interpretano criminali in città fittizie. Unendo missioni sceneggiate e libertà totale, la saga è nota per il suo umorismo satirico, la violenza e un gameplay vario. Ogni episodio propone una storia unica ispirata ai film di gangster e alla cultura urbana. GTA è una delle serie più influenti e popolari del videogioco.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Grand Theft Auto (GTA) ist eine von Rockstar entwickelte Open-World-Actionspielreihe, in der Spieler Kriminelle in fiktiven Städten verkörpern. Die Saga verbindet inszenierte Missionen mit großer Freiheit und ist für satirischen Humor, Gewalt und abwechslungsreiches Gameplay bekannt. Jeder Teil bietet eine eigene Geschichte, inspiriert von Gangsterfilmen und urbaner Kultur. GTA zählt zu den einflussreichsten und beliebtesten Videospielreihen.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Grand Theft Auto (GTA) é uma série de jogos de ação em mundo aberto criada pela Rockstar, na qual os jogadores assumem o papel de criminosos em cidades fictícias. Misturando missões roteirizadas com liberdade total, a saga é conhecida pelo humor satírico, violência e jogabilidade variada. Cada jogo traz uma história própria inspirada em filmes de gângster e cultura urbana. GTA é uma das franquias mais influentes e populares dos videogames.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Grand Theft Auto V (PS3, 2013)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>This anonymous woman embodies the provocative and glamorous aesthetic of Los Santos, leaning forward while blowing a kiss, a symbol of a world where seduction, excess and superficiality stand beside violence and crime, reflecting the series’ strong visual identity and its satirical view of modern culture.
Fun fact: This artwork became one of GTA V most iconic promotional images, often associated with the game more than its own main characters.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Cette femme anonyme incarne l’esthétique provocante et glamour de Los Santos, penchée en avant dans une pose suggestive tout en soufflant un baiser, symbole d’un univers où séduction, excès et superficialité côtoient violence et criminalité, reflétant l’identité visuelle forte de la série et son regard satirique sur la culture moderne.
Fun fact : Cette illustration est devenue l’une des images promotionnelles les plus emblématiques de GTA V, au point d’être souvent associée au jeu plus que ses propres personnages principaux.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Esta mujer anónima encarna la estética provocadora y glamurosa de Los Santos, inclinada hacia delante mientras lanza un beso, símbolo de un mundo donde seducción, exceso y superficialidad conviven con violencia y criminalidad, reflejando la fuerte identidad visual de la serie y su mirada satírica sobre la cultura moderna.
Dato curioso: Esta ilustración se convirtió en una de las imágenes promocionales más icónicas de GTA V, a menudo más asociada al juego que sus propios protagonistas.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Questa donna anonima incarna l’estetica provocante e glamour di Los Santos, piegata in avanti mentre manda un bacio, simbolo di un mondo in cui seduzione, eccesso e superficialità convivono con violenza e criminalità, riflettendo la forte identità visiva della serie e il suo sguardo satirico sulla cultura moderna.
Curiosità: Questa illustrazione è diventata una delle immagini promozionali più iconiche di GTA V, spesso associata al gioco più dei suoi protagonisti.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Diese anonyme Frau verkörpert die provokante und glamouröse Ästhetik von Los Santos, nach vorn gebeugt und einen Kuss zuwerfend, Sinnbild einer Welt, in der Verführung, Exzess und Oberflächlichkeit neben Gewalt und Kriminalität stehen, und spiegelt die starke visuelle Identität der Reihe sowie ihren satirischen Blick auf moderne Kultur.
Interessante Tatsache: Diese Illustration wurde zu einem der bekanntesten Werbemotive von GTA V und wird oft stärker mit dem Spiel verbunden als dessen Hauptfiguren.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Esta mulher anônima encarna a estética provocante e glamourosa de Los Santos, inclinada para a frente enquanto manda um beijo, símbolo de um universo onde sedução, excesso e superficialidade convivem com violência e criminalidade, refletindo a forte identidade visual da série e seu olhar satírico sobre a cultura moderna.
Curiosidade: Esta ilustração se tornou uma das imagens promocionais mais icônicas de GTA V, muitas vezes mais associada ao jogo do que seus protagonistas.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
