<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>Game hacks are modifications to existing video games, created by fans or amateur programmers. They can include changes to levels, graphics, gameplay or even story, transforming the original experience. Very popular for retro games like Super Mario, Sonic or Pokémon, they allow you to explore new, unofficial versions. Some hacks become cult favorites, rivaling the original titles in creativity.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Les jeux hacks sont des modifications de jeux vidéo existants, créées par des fans ou des programmeurs amateurs. Ils peuvent inclure des changements de niveaux, de graphismes, de gameplay ou même d’histoire, transformant l’expérience originale. Très populaires pour les jeux rétro comme Super Mario, Sonic ou Pokémon, ils permettent d’explorer de nouvelles versions non officielles. Certains hacks deviennent cultes et rivalisent avec les titres originaux en créativité.</text>
</text>
<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Los hacks de juegos son modificaciones de videojuegos existentes, creadas por fans o programadores aficionados. Pueden cambiar niveles, gráficos, jugabilidad o incluso la historia, transformando la experiencia original. Muy populares en juegos retro como Super Mario, Sonic o Pokémon, permiten explorar nuevas versiones no oficiales. Algunos hacks se vuelven de culto y rivalizan en creatividad con los títulos originales.</text>
</text>
<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Gli hack dei giochi sono modifiche a videogiochi esistenti, create da fan o programmatori amatoriali. Possono cambiare livelli, grafica, gameplay o persino la storia, trasformando l’esperienza originale. Molto popolari nei giochi retro come Super Mario, Sonic o Pokémon, permettono di esplorare nuove versioni non ufficiali. Alcuni hack diventano cult e competono in creatività con i titoli originali.</text>
</text>
<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Game-Hacks sind Modifikationen bestehender Videospiele, erstellt von Fans oder Hobbyprogrammierern. Sie können Levels, Grafik, Gameplay oder sogar die Geschichte verändern und so das ursprüngliche Erlebnis verwandeln. Besonders beliebt bei Retro-Spielen wie Super Mario, Sonic oder Pokémon, ermöglichen sie neue, inoffizielle Versionen. Manche Hacks werden Kult und konkurrieren kreativ mit den Originalen.</text>
</text>
<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Hacks de jogos são modificações de videogames existentes, criadas por fãs ou programadores amadores. Podem mudar fases, gráficos, jogabilidade ou até a história, transformando a experiência original. Muito populares em jogos retrô como Super Mario, Sonic ou Pokémon, permitem explorar novas versões não oficiais. Alguns hacks se tornam cultuados e rivalizam em criatividade com os títulos originais.</text>
</text>


<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Sonic the Hedgehog (MegaDrive / Genesis, 1991)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>
<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>This infernal version of Sonic twists the iconic hero into a dark and unsettling creature, symbolizing the world of hacks where games are modified, altered or completely reinvented, embodying both the creativity and the excesses of a scene where everything can be transformed, from gameplay to graphics.
Fun fact: Sonic hacks form one of the most active, with hundreds of modified versions ranging from small tweaks to complete transformations of the original game.</text>
</text>
<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Cette version infernale de Sonic détourne l’image du héros iconique en une créature sombre et inquiétante, symbolisant l’univers des hacks où les jeux sont modifiés, altérés ou complètement réinventés, incarnant la créativité comme les dérives d’une scène où tout peut être transformé, du gameplay aux graphismes.
Fun fact : La scène des hacks de Sonic est l’une des plus actives, avec des centaines de versions modifiées allant de simples ajustements à des transformations complètes du jeu original.</text>
</text>
<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Esta versión infernal de Sonic transforma al héroe icónico en una criatura oscura e inquietante, simbolizando el mundo de los hacks donde los juegos se modifican, alteran o reinventan por completo, encarnando tanto la creatividad como los excesos de una escena donde todo puede cambiar, desde la jugabilidad hasta los gráficos.
Dato curioso: La escena de hacks de Sonic es una de las más activas, con cientos de versiones modificadas que van desde pequeños ajustes hasta transformaciones completas.</text>
</text>
<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Questa versione infernale di Sonic trasforma l’eroe iconico in una creatura oscura e inquietante, simbolo dell’universo degli hack in cui i giochi vengono modificati, alterati o reinventati del tutto, incarnando sia la creatività sia gli eccessi di una scena dove tutto può cambiare, dal gameplay alla grafica.
Curiosità: La scena degli hack di Sonic è una delle più attive, con centinaia di versioni modificate, da piccoli ritocchi a trasformazioni complete.</text>
</text>
<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Diese infernalische Version von Sonic verwandelt den ikonischen Helden in eine dunkle, beunruhigende Kreatur und steht für die Welt der Hacks, in der Spiele verändert, verfälscht oder völlig neu erfunden werden, als Ausdruck von Kreativität und Übertreibung einer Szene, in der alles wandelbar ist.
Interessante Tatsache: Die Sonic-Hack-Szene gehört zu den aktivsten, mit hunderten modifizierten Versionen von kleinen Anpassungen bis zu kompletten Umbauten.</text>
</text>
<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Esta versão infernal de Sonic transforma o herói icônico em uma criatura sombria e inquietante, simbolizando o universo dos hacks onde jogos são modificados, alterados ou totalmente reinventados, representando tanto a criatividade quanto os excessos de uma cena em que tudo pode mudar, da jogabilidade aos gráficos.
Curiosidade: A cena de hacks de Sonic é uma das mais ativas, com centenas de versões modificadas, de pequenos ajustes a transformações completas.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
