<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>HBMAME (HomeBrew MAME) is an unofficial version of MAME (Arcade) allowing the addition of many home games and various hacks.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>HBMAME (HomeBrew MAME) est une version non officielle de MAME (Arcade) permettant l'ajout de nombreux jeux maison et hacks divers.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>HBMAME (HomeBrew MAME) ist eine inoffizielle Version von MAME (Arcade), die das Hinzufügen von vielen verschiedenen Heimspielen und Hacks ermöglicht.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>HBMAME (HomeBrew MAME) es una versión no oficial de MAME (Arcade) que permite añadir muchos juegos caseros y varios hacks.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>HBMAME (HomeBrew MAME) è una versione non ufficiale di MAME (Arcade) che permette di aggiungere molti giochi fatti in casa e vari hack.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>HBMAME (HomeBrew MAME) は、MAME(Arcade)の非公式バージョンで、多くの自作ゲームや様々なハックを追加することができます。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>HBMAME (HomeBrew MAME) is een onofficiële versie van MAME (Arcade) waarmee vele zelfgemaakte spellen en diverse hacks kunnen worden toegevoegd.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>HBMAME (HomeBrew MAME) to nieoficjalna wersja MAME (Arcade) pozwalająca na dodanie wielu gier domowej roboty i różnych hacków.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>HBMAME (HomeBrew MAME) é uma versão não oficial de MAME (Arcade) que permite a adição de muitos jogos feitos em casa e vários hacks.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>HBMAME (HomeBrew MAME) - это неофициальная версия MAME (Arcade), позволяющая добавлять множество самодельных игр и различных хаков.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Metal Slug 2 (1998)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>Fiolina “Fio” Germi is a special forces soldier, recognizable by her uniform and her efficiency in the field in this explosive run and gun. In Metal Slug 2, she faces entire armies with varied weapons and iconic vehicles, in nervous gameplay known for its high difficulty, numerous enemies and traps requiring careful memorization of the levels.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Fiolina “Fio” Germi est une soldate experte des forces spéciales, reconnaissable à son uniforme et à son efficacité sur le terrain dans ce run and gun explosif. Dans Metal Slug 2, elle affronte des armées entières à coups d’armes variées et de véhicules emblématiques, dans un gameplay nerveux connu pour sa difficulté élevée, ses ennemis nombreux et ses pièges demandant une bonne mémorisation des niveaux.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Fiolina “Fio” Germi es una soldado de fuerzas especiales, reconocible por su uniforme y su eficacia sobre el terreno en este explosivo run and gun. En Metal Slug 2, se enfrenta a ejércitos enteros con armas variadas y vehículos emblemáticos, en una jugabilidad nerviosa conocida por su alta dificultad, enemigos numerosos y trampas que exigen memorizar bien los niveles.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Fiolina “Fio” Germi è una soldatessa delle forze speciali, riconoscibile dal suo uniforme e dalla sua efficacia sul campo in questo esplosivo run and gun. In Metal Slug 2 affronta interi eserciti con armi varie e veicoli iconici, in un gameplay frenetico noto per l’elevata difficoltà, i molti nemici e le trappole che richiedono una buona memorizzazione dei livelli.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Fiolina “Fio” Germi ist eine Soldatin der Spezialeinheiten, erkennbar an ihrer Uniform und ihrer Effizienz im Einsatz in diesem explosiven Run and Gun. In Metal Slug 2 stellt sie sich ganzen Armeen mit verschiedenen Waffen und ikonischen Fahrzeugen, in einem schnellen Gameplay, das für hohe Schwierigkeit, viele Gegner und Fallen bekannt ist, die gutes Auswendiglernen der Levels verlangen.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Fiolina “Fio” Germi é uma soldado das forças especiais, reconhecível pelo seu uniforme e pela sua eficácia em campo neste run and gun explosivo. Em Metal Slug 2, ela enfrenta exércitos inteiros com armas variadas e veículos emblemáticos, numa jogabilidade intensa conhecida pela dificuldade elevada, muitos inimigos e armadilhas que exigem boa memorização dos níveis.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
