<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>J2ME (Java 2 Platform, Micro Edition) is a technology that allows programmers to use the Java programming language and associated tools to develop programs for wireless mobile information devices such as mobile phones and PDAs. </text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>J2ME (Java 2 Platform, Micro Edition) est une technologie qui permet aux programmeurs d'utiliser le langage de programmation Java et les outils associés pour développer des programmes pour les dispositifs d'information mobiles sans fil tels que les téléphones cellulaires et les assistants numériques personnels (PDA). </text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>J2ME (Java 2 Platform, Micro Edition) ist eine Technologie, die es Programmierern ermöglicht, die Programmiersprache Java und zugehörige Tools zu verwenden, um Programme für drahtlose mobile Informationsgeräte wie Mobiltelefone und Personal Digital Assistants (PDAs) zu entwickeln. </text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>J2ME (Java 2 Platform, Micro Edition) es una tecnología que permite a los programadores utilizar el lenguaje de programación Java y las herramientas asociadas para desarrollar programas para dispositivos inalámbricos de información móvil, como teléfonos móviles y PDA. </text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>J2ME (Java 2 Platform, Micro Edition) è una tecnologia che consente ai programmatori di utilizzare il linguaggio di programmazione Java e gli strumenti associati per sviluppare programmi per dispositivi informatici mobili senza fili come telefoni cellulari e PDA. </text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>J2ME（Java 2 Platform, Micro Edition）は、プログラマーがJavaプログラミング言語と関連ツールを使用して、携帯電話やPDAなどの無線携帯情報端末向けのプログラムを開発するための技術です。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>J2ME (Java 2 Platform, Micro Edition) is een technologie waarmee programmeurs de programmeertaal Java en de bijbehorende hulpmiddelen kunnen gebruiken om programma's te ontwikkelen voor draadloze mobiele informatieapparaten zoals mobiele telefoons en PDA's. </text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>J2ME (Java 2 Platform, Micro Edition) to technologia, która umożliwia programistom wykorzystanie języka programowania Java i powiązanych z nim narzędzi do tworzenia programów dla bezprzewodowych mobilnych urządzeń informacyjnych, takich jak telefony komórkowe i PDA. </text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>J2ME (Java 2 Platform, Micro Edition) é uma tecnologia que permite aos programadores utilizar a linguagem de programação Java e ferramentas associadas para desenvolver programas para dispositivos de informação móvel sem fios, tais como telemóveis e PDAs. </text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>J2ME (Java 2 Platform, Micro Edition) - это технология, которая позволяет программистам использовать язык программирования Java и связанные с ним инструменты для разработки программ для беспроводных мобильных информационных устройств, таких как мобильные телефоны и персональные цифровые помощники (PDA). </text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
