<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>Kaneko Seisakusho Co, Ltd (株式会社金子製作所?) was a Japanese company developing and selling video games and computer software established in 1980. It worked as a subcontractor for the Taito company from 1982.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Kaneko Seisakusho Co., Ltd. (株式会社金子製作所?) était une société japonaise de développement et de vente de jeux vidéo et de logiciels informatiques créée en 1980. Elle a travaillé en tant que sous-traitant pour la société Taito dès 1982.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Kaneko Seisakusho Co., Ltd. (株式会社金子製作所?) war ein 1980 gegründetes japanisches Unternehmen, das Videospiele und Computersoftware entwickelte und verkaufte. Sie arbeitete ab 1982 als Zulieferer für die Firma Taito.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Kaneko Seisakusho Co, Ltd (株式会社金子製作所?) fue una empresa japonesa de desarrollo y venta de videojuegos y software informático fundada en 1980. Trabajó como subcontratista de la empresa Taito a partir de 1982.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Kaneko Seisakusho Co, Ltd (株式会社金子製作所?) era una società giapponese che sviluppava e vendeva videogiochi e software per computer fondata nel 1980. Dal 1982 ha lavorato come subappaltatore per la società Taito.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>株式会社金子製作所（株式会社かねこせいさくしょ）は、1980年に設立された日本のゲームソフト・コンピュータソフトの開発・販売会社である。1982年からは、タイトーの下請け会社として活動していた。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>Kaneko Seisakusho Co, Ltd (株式会社金子製作所?) was een Japans bedrijf dat videospelletjes en computersoftware ontwikkelde en verkocht, opgericht in 1980. Vanaf 1982 werkte het als onderaannemer voor het bedrijf Taito.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>Kaneko Seisakusho Co, Ltd (株式会社金子製作所?) była japońską firmą zajmującą się tworzeniem i sprzedażą gier wideo i oprogramowania komputerowego, założoną w 1980 roku. Od 1982 roku pracowała jako podwykonawca dla firmy Taito.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Kaneko Seisakusho Co, Ltd (株式会社金子製作所?) era uma empresa japonesa que desenvolvia e vendia jogos de vídeo e software de computador, criada em 1980. Trabalhou como subcontratante para a empresa Taito a partir de 1982.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>Kaneko Seisakusho Co, Ltd (株式会社金子製作所?) была японской компанией по разработке и продаже видеоигр и компьютерного программного обеспечения, основанной в 1980 году. С 1982 года она работала в качестве субподрядчика компании Taito.</text>
</text>


<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Gals Panic (1990) &amp; Great 1000 Miles Rally (1994)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>Gals Panic and Great 1000 Miles Rally show two very different sides of Kaneko arcade games: a fast Qix-style puzzle game with bold presentation, and a clear, immediate rally game built for quick races, readable roads and pure coin-op rhythm. Together, they capture the studio’s colorful 1990s identity, between playful risk, simple controls and instantly recognizable arcade energy.
Fun fact: Great 1000 Miles Rally also received an improved arcade version, Great 1000 Miles Rally 2, with new routes and refined presentation.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Gals Panic et Great 1000 Miles Rally montrent deux visages très différents de Kaneko en arcade : un puzzle game nerveux façon Qix, à l’habillage provocateur, et un jeu de rallye clair, immédiat, pensé pour des courses rapides, des routes lisibles et un vrai rythme de salle. Ensemble, ils résument bien l’identité colorée et les prises de risque du studio dans les années 90.
Fun fact : Great 1000 Miles Rally a eu une version arcade améliorée, Great 1000 Miles Rally 2, avec de nouveaux tracés et une présentation affinée.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Gals Panic y Great 1000 Miles Rally muestran dos caras muy distintas de Kaneko en arcade: un puzzle rápido al estilo Qix, con una presentación atrevida, y un rally claro e inmediato, pensado para carreras cortas, rutas legibles y puro ritmo de salón. Juntos resumen la identidad colorida del estudio en los años 90, entre riesgo, controles simples y energía arcade reconocible.
Dato curioso: Great 1000 Miles Rally también tuvo una versión arcade mejorada, Great 1000 Miles Rally 2, con nuevas rutas y una presentación más pulida.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Gals Panic e Great 1000 Miles Rally mostrano due volti molto diversi di Kaneko in sala giochi: un puzzle game veloce in stile Qix, dalla presentazione audace, e un rally chiaro e immediato, pensato per gare brevi, strade leggibili e puro ritmo arcade. Insieme riassumono l’identità colorata dello studio negli anni 90, tra rischio, controlli semplici ed energia da coin-op.
Curiosità: Great 1000 Miles Rally ebbe anche una versione arcade migliorata, Great 1000 Miles Rally 2, con nuovi tracciati e una presentazione rifinita.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Gals Panic und Great 1000 Miles Rally zeigen zwei sehr unterschiedliche Seiten von Kaneko in der Arcade: ein schnelles Puzzle-Spiel im Qix-Stil mit gewagter Präsentation und ein klares, direktes Rallyespiel für kurze Rennen, gut lesbare Strecken und echten Spielhallenrhythmus. Zusammen fangen sie die bunte Identität des Studios in den 90ern ein, mit Risiko, einfachen Regeln und Arcade-Energie.
Interessante Tatsache: Great 1000 Miles Rally erhielt auch eine verbesserte Arcade-Version, Great 1000 Miles Rally 2, mit neuen Strecken und verfeinerter Präsentation.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Gals Panic e Great 1000 Miles Rally mostram dois lados muito diferentes da Kaneko nos arcades: um puzzle rápido ao estilo Qix, com apresentação ousada, e um rally claro e imediato, feito para corridas curtas, estradas legíveis e puro ritmo de salão. Juntos, resumem a identidade colorida do estúdio nos anos 90, entre risco, controlos simples e energia arcade reconhecível.
Curiosidade: Great 1000 Miles Rally também teve uma versão arcade melhorada, Great 1000 Miles Rally 2, com novas rotas e apresentação refinada.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
