<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Joseledos
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>The Pioneer LaserActive was a hybrid Laserdisc player and video game console released by Pioneer in 1993. It played Japanese/US video laserdiscs without requiring any additional modules. Optional modules (called PACs by Pioneer) expanded the hardware to include new features, including compatibility with the Sega Mega Drive/Genesis and the NEC PC Engine/TurboGrafx-16, and it was capable of running both cartridge/HuCard-based and CD-based games.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>La Pioneer LaserActive était un lecteur Laserdisc hybride faisant également office de console de jeux vidéo, commercialisée par Pioneer en 1993. Elle lisait les Laserdiscs vidéo japonais et américains sans nécessiter de modules supplémentaires. Des modules optionnels (appelés PAC par Pioneer) permettaient d'étendre ses fonctionnalités, notamment la compatibilité avec la Sega Mega Drive/Genesis et la NEC PC Engine/TurboGrafx-16. Elle pouvait ainsi faire tourner des jeux sur cartouche/HuCard et sur CD.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Der Pioneer LaserActive war ein Hybridgerät aus Laserdisc-Player und Videospielkonsole, das 1993 von Pioneer auf den Markt gebracht wurde. Er spielte japanische und US-amerikanische Videolaserdiscs ohne zusätzliche Module ab. Optionale Module (von Pioneer als PACs bezeichnet) erweiterten die Hardware um neue Funktionen, darunter die Kompatibilität mit dem Sega Mega Drive/Genesis und dem NEC PC Engine/TurboGrafx-16. Außerdem konnte er sowohl Cartridge-/HuCard-basierte als auch CD-basierte Spiele abspielen.</text>
</text>


<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>El Pioneer LaserActive fue un híbrido de reproductor Laserdisc y videoconsola lanzado por Pioneer en 1993. Reproducía laserdiscs de vídeo Japón/EE. UU. sin necesidad de ningún módulo. Mediante módulos opcionales (llamados PAC por Pioneer) se ampliaba el hardware para incluir nuevas funcionalidades, entre ellas compatibilidad con la Sega Mega Drive/Genesis y la NEC PC Engine/TurboGrafx-16, siendo capaz de ejecutar tanto los juegos basados en cartucho/HuCard como los basados en CD.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Il Pioneer LaserActive era un ibrido tra lettore Laserdisc e console per videogiochi, commercializzato da Pioneer nel 1993. Riproduceva Laserdisc video giapponesi e statunitensi senza moduli aggiuntivi. I moduli opzionali, chiamati PAC da Pioneer, ampliavano l’hardware con nuove funzioni, tra cui la compatibilità con Sega Mega Drive/Genesis e NEC PC Engine/TurboGrafx-16, permettendo di usare giochi su cartuccia, HuCard e CD.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>O Pioneer LaserActive era um híbrido de leitor Laserdisc e console de videogame lançado pela Pioneer em 1993. Reproduzia Laserdiscs de vídeo japoneses e americanos sem módulos adicionais. Módulos opcionais, chamados PAC pela Pioneer, ampliavam o hardware com novas funções, incluindo compatibilidade com Sega Mega Drive/Genesis e NEC PC Engine/TurboGrafx-16, rodando jogos em cartucho, HuCard e CD.</text>
</text>


<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Space Berserker (1993)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>Futuristic rail shooter for Pioneer LaserActive, Space Berserker uses the Mega LD format through the Sega PAC module to blend video sequences with space action. The player faces enemy waves, locks onto targets and crosses several zones before attacking motherships. The experience relies on rhythm, precision and the typical integration of LaserDisc games.
Fun fact: Mega LD games combined real video with interactive elements, an approach still rare in the early 1990s.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Rail shooter futuriste sur Pioneer LaserActive, Space Berserker exploite le format Mega LD via le module Sega PAC pour mêler séquences vidéo et action spatiale. Le joueur affronte des vagues d’ennemis, verrouille ses cibles et traverse plusieurs zones avant d’attaquer des vaisseaux mères. L’expérience repose sur le rythme, la précision et l’intégration typique des jeux LaserDisc.
Fun fact : Les jeux Mega LD combinaient vidéo réelle et éléments interactifs, une approche encore rare au début des années 90.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Rail shooter futurista para Pioneer LaserActive, Space Berserker usa el formato Mega LD mediante el módulo Sega PAC para combinar secuencias de vídeo y acción espacial. El jugador afronta oleadas de enemigos, fija objetivos y cruza varias zonas antes de atacar naves nodriza. La experiencia se apoya en ritmo, precisión e integración típica de los juegos LaserDisc.
Dato curioso: Los juegos Mega LD combinaban vídeo real con elementos interactivos, un enfoque aún raro a comienzos de los años 90.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Rail shooter futuristico per Pioneer LaserActive, Space Berserker usa il formato Mega LD tramite il modulo Sega PAC per unire sequenze video e azione spaziale. Il giocatore affronta ondate di nemici, aggancia bersagli e attraversa varie zone prima di attaccare navi madri. L’esperienza si basa su ritmo, precisione e integrazione tipica dei giochi LaserDisc.
Curiosità: I giochi Mega LD combinavano video reale ed elementi interattivi, un approccio ancora raro nei primi anni 90.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Futuristischer Rail-Shooter für Pioneer LaserActive: Space Berserker nutzt das Mega-LD-Format über das Sega-PAC-Modul, um Videosequenzen mit Weltraumaction zu verbinden. Der Spieler bekämpft Gegnerwellen, erfasst Ziele und durchquert mehrere Zonen, bevor Mutterschiffe angegriffen werden. Das Erlebnis lebt von Rhythmus, Präzision und typischer LaserDisc-Integration.
Interessante Tatsache: Mega-LD-Spiele kombinierten echtes Video mit interaktiven Elementen, ein Anfang der 90er noch seltener Ansatz.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Rail shooter futurista para Pioneer LaserActive, Space Berserker usa o formato Mega LD através do módulo Sega PAC para misturar sequências de vídeo e ação espacial. O jogador enfrenta vagas de inimigos, mira nos alvos e atravessa várias zonas antes de atacar naves-mãe. A experiência aposta em ritmo, precisão e integração típica dos jogos LaserDisc.
Curiosidade: Os jogos Mega LD combinavam vídeo real com elementos interativos, uma abordagem ainda rara no início dos anos 90.</text>
</text>
</view>
</theme>
