<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
"<text>Place your magazines and videos in the ""library"" directory.
Acceptable extensions: jpg, jpeg, png, bmp, psd, tga, gif, hdr, pic, ppm, pgm, mkv, pdf, mp4, avi, cbz.</text>"
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
"<text>Placez dans le répertoire ""library"" vos magazines et vidéos.
Extensions acceptables : jpg, jpeg, png, bmp, psd, tga, gif, hdr, pic, ppm, pgm, mkv, pdf, mp4, avi, cbz.</text>"
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
"<text>Legen Sie Ihre Zeitschriften und Videos in das Verzeichnis ""library"".
Akzeptable Erweiterungen: jpg, jpeg, png, bmp, psd, tga, gif, hdr, pic, ppm, pgm, mkv, pdf, mp4, avi, cbz.</text>"
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
"<text>Coloca tus revistas y vídeos en el directorio ""biblioteca"".
Extensiones aceptables: jpg, jpeg, png, bmp, psd, tga, gif, hdr, pic, ppm, pgm, mkv, pdf, mp4, avi, cbz.</text>"
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
"<text>Inserire le riviste e i video nella directory ""library"".
Estensioni accettabili: jpg, jpeg, png, bmp, psd, tga, gif, hdr, pic, ppm, pgm, mkv, pdf, mp4, avi, cbz.</text>"
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
"<text>雑誌やビデオは、""library ""ディレクトリに置いてください。
使用可能な拡張子：jpg、jpeg、png、bmp、psd、tga、gif、hdr、pic、ppm、pgm、mkv、pdf、MP4、AVI、CBZ。</text>"
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
"<text>Plaats uw tijdschriften en video's in de map ""bibliotheek"".
Aanvaardbare extensies: jpg, jpeg, png, bmp, psd, tga, gif, hdr, pic, ppm, pgm, mkv, pdf, mp4, avi, cbz.</text>"
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
"<text>Czasopisma i filmy umieszczaj w katalogu ""library"".
Akceptowane rozszerzenia: jpg, jpeg, png, bmp, psd, tga, gif, hdr, pic, ppm, pgm, mkv, pdf, mp4, avi, cbz.</text>"
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
"<text>Coloque as suas revistas e vídeos no directório ""biblioteca"".
Extensões aceitáveis: jpg, jpeg, png, bmp, psd, tga, gif, hdr, pic, ppm, pgm, mkv, pdf, mp4, avi, cbz.</text>"
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
"<text>Поместите ваши журналы и видео в каталог ""library"".
Приемлемые расширения: jpg, jpeg, png, bmp, psd, tga, gif, hdr, pic, ppm, pgm, mkv, pdf, mp4, avi, cbz.</text>"
</text>

</view>
</theme>
