<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
"<text>Place your magazines and videos in the "library" directory.
Acceptable extensions: jpg, jpeg, png, bmp, psd, tga, gif, hdr, pic, ppm, pgm, mkv, pdf, mp4, avi, cbz.</text>"
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
"<text>Placez dans le répertoire "library" vos magazines et vidéos afin de pouvoir les consulter ici. Voici les différentes extensions qui sont autorisées : 
jpg, jpeg, png, bmp, psd, tga, gif, hdr, pic, ppm, pgm, mkv, pdf, mp4, avi, cbz.</text>"
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
"<text>Legen Sie Ihre Zeitschriften und Videos in das Verzeichnis "library".
Akzeptable Erweiterungen: jpg, jpeg, png, bmp, psd, tga, gif, hdr, pic, ppm, pgm, mkv, pdf, mp4, avi, cbz.</text>"
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
"<text>Coloca tus revistas y vídeos en el directorio ""biblioteca"".
Extensiones aceptables: jpg, jpeg, png, bmp, psd, tga, gif, hdr, pic, ppm, pgm, mkv, pdf, mp4, avi, cbz.</text>"
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
"<text>Inserire le riviste e i video nella directory "library".
Estensioni accettabili: jpg, jpeg, png, bmp, psd, tga, gif, hdr, pic, ppm, pgm, mkv, pdf, mp4, avi, cbz.</text>"
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
"<text>雑誌やビデオは、""library ""ディレクトリに置いてください。
使用可能な拡張子：jpg、jpeg、png、bmp、psd、tga、gif、hdr、pic、ppm、pgm、mkv、pdf、MP4、AVI、CBZ。</text>"
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
"<text>Plaats uw tijdschriften en video's in de map ""bibliotheek"".
Aanvaardbare extensies: jpg, jpeg, png, bmp, psd, tga, gif, hdr, pic, ppm, pgm, mkv, pdf, mp4, avi, cbz.</text>"
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
"<text>Czasopisma i filmy umieszczaj w katalogu "library".
Akceptowane rozszerzenia: jpg, jpeg, png, bmp, psd, tga, gif, hdr, pic, ppm, pgm, mkv, pdf, mp4, avi, cbz.</text>"
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
"<text>Coloque as suas revistas e vídeos no directório ""biblioteca"".
Extensões aceitáveis: jpg, jpeg, png, bmp, psd, tga, gif, hdr, pic, ppm, pgm, mkv, pdf, mp4, avi, cbz.</text>"
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
"<text>Поместите ваши журналы и видео в каталог "library".
Приемлемые расширения: jpg, jpeg, png, bmp, psd, tga, gif, hdr, pic, ppm, pgm, mkv, pdf, mp4, avi, cbz.</text>"
</text>

<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Lisa Simpson&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>Lisa is the middle child of the Simpson family, known for her intelligence, curiosity and deep love of reading, which sets her apart in her everyday world. Passionate about culture, music and knowledge, she spends much of her time with books, newspapers or magazines, always searching for understanding, new ideas and a clearer view of the world.
Fun fact: Matt Groening named Lisa after his own younger sister, Lisa Groening, just as several Simpsons share names with his family.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Lisa est la cadette de la famille Simpson, reconnue pour son intelligence, sa curiosité et son amour profond pour la lecture. Passionnée de culture, de musique et de savoir, elle passe une grande partie de son temps plongée dans des livres, toujours en quête de compréhension et d’idées nouvelles.
Fun fact : Matt Groening a nommé Lisa d’après sa propre sœur cadette, Lisa Groening, comme plusieurs membres de la famille Simpson.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Lisa es la hija mediana de la familia Simpson, conocida por su inteligencia, su curiosidad y su profundo amor por la lectura, que la distingue claramente en su entorno cotidiano. Apasionada por la cultura, la música y el conocimiento, pasa mucho tiempo entre libros, periódicos o revistas, siempre buscando comprensión, ideas nuevas y una mirada más lúcida sobre el mundo.
Dato curioso: Matt Groening llamó Lisa al personaje por su propia hermana menor, Lisa Groening, igual que varios Simpson toman nombres de su familia.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Lisa è la figlia mediana della famiglia Simpson, nota per la sua intelligenza, la curiosità e il profondo amore per la lettura, che la distinguono nettamente nel suo ambiente quotidiano. Appassionata di cultura, musica e conoscenza, passa molto tempo tra libri, giornali o riviste, sempre in cerca di comprensione, nuove idee e uno sguardo più lucido sul mondo.
Curiosità: Matt Groening chiamò Lisa come la sua sorella minore, Lisa Groening, proprio come altri Simpson riprendono nomi della sua famiglia.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Lisa ist das mittlere Kind der Familie Simpson, bekannt für ihre Intelligenz, Neugier und tiefe Liebe zum Lesen, die sie in ihrem Alltag deutlich hervorheben. Begeistert von Kultur, Musik und Wissen verbringt sie viel Zeit mit Büchern, Zeitungen oder Magazinen und sucht stets nach Verständnis, neuen Ideen und einem klareren Blick auf die Welt.
Interessante Tatsache: Matt Groening benannte Lisa nach seiner jüngeren Schwester Lisa Groening, wie auch mehrere Simpsons Namen seiner Familie tragen.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Lisa é a filha do meio da família Simpson, conhecida pela sua inteligência, curiosidade e profundo amor pela leitura, que a distinguem claramente no seu ambiente quotidiano. Apaixonada por cultura, música e conhecimento, passa muito tempo entre livros, jornais ou revistas, sempre à procura de compreensão, novas ideias e uma visão mais lúcida do mundo.
Curiosidade: Matt Groening chamou Lisa à personagem em homenagem à sua irmã mais nova, Lisa Groening, como acontece com vários Simpsons.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
