<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>The Atari Lynx was developed by Epyx under the name "Handy". It was Atari's only handheld console and the very first handheld with a colour LCD screen. Although this console was technologically superior to the Game Boy, Atari's marketing mistakes and the small number of games available meant that the console was a commercial failure.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>L'Atari Lynx fut développée par Epyx sous le nom « Handy ». Ce fut la seule console portable d'Atari et la toute première portable avec un écran LCD couleur. Bien que cette console fût supérieure à la Game Boy d'un point de vue technologique, les erreurs marketing d'Atari et la faible quantité de jeux disponibles firent que la console fut un échec commercial.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Der Atari Lynx wurde von Epyx unter dem Namen "Handy" entwickelt. Es war Ataris einzige tragbare Konsole und die allererste tragbare Konsole mit einem Farb-LCD-Bildschirm. Obwohl die Konsole dem Game Boy technologisch überlegen war, führten Ataris Marketingfehler und die geringe Anzahl an verfügbaren Spielen dazu, dass die Konsole ein kommerzieller Misserfolg wurde.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>La Atari Lynx fue desarrollada por Epyx bajo el nombre de "Handy". Fue la única consola portátil de Atari y la primera con pantalla LCD en color. Aunque esta consola era tecnológicamente superior a la Game Boy, los errores de marketing de Atari y el reducido número de juegos disponibles hicieron que la consola fuera un fracaso comercial.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>L'Atari Lynx è stato sviluppato da Epyx con il nome di "Handy". Fu l'unica console portatile di Atari e la prima console portatile con schermo LCD a colori. Sebbene questa console fosse tecnologicamente superiore al Game Boy, gli errori di marketing di Atari e l'esiguo numero di giochi disponibili ne decretarono il fallimento commerciale.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>Atari LynxはEpyx社によって "Handy "という名前で開発されました。アタリ社の唯一の携帯ゲーム機であり、カラー液晶画面を搭載した最初の携帯ゲーム機でした。このゲーム機は技術的にはゲームボーイより優れていましたが、アタリのマーケティングの失敗と利用できるゲームの数が少なかったため、このゲーム機は商業的に失敗してしまいました。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>De Atari Lynx werd ontwikkeld door Epyx onder de naam "Handy". Het was Atari's enige handheld console en de allereerste handheld met een kleuren LCD scherm. Hoewel deze console technologisch superieur was aan de Game Boy, zorgden Atari's marketingfouten en het kleine aantal beschikbare spellen ervoor dat de console een commerciële mislukking werd.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>Atari Lynx został opracowany przez firmę Epyx pod nazwą "Handy". Była to jedyna ręczna konsola Atari i pierwszy handheld z kolorowym ekranem LCD. Mimo że konsola ta była technologicznie lepsza od Game Boya, błędy marketingowe Atari i mała liczba dostępnych gier sprawiły, że konsola okazała się komercyjną porażką.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>O Atari Lince foi desenvolvido pela Epyx sob o nome "Handy". Era a única consola portátil da Atari e a primeira consola portátil com um ecrã LCD a cores. Embora esta consola fosse tecnologicamente superior ao Game Boy, os erros de marketing da Atari e o pequeno número de jogos disponíveis significaram que a consola foi um fracasso comercial.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>Atari Lynx была разработана компанией Epyx под названием "Handy". Это была единственная портативная консоль Atari и самая первая портативная консоль с цветным ЖК-экраном. Хотя эта консоль технологически превосходила Game Boy, маркетинговые ошибки Atari и небольшое количество доступных игр привели к тому, что консоль потерпела коммерческий провал</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;California Games (1989)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>The surfer from California Games perfectly captures the game's Californian atmosphere, mixing beach, sunshine and sports culture. She refers to the surfing event, where the player must master balance on the wave, chain tricks together and control the trajectory precisely to avoid falling.
Fun fact: California Games was used as a launch game for the Atari Lynx, often included with the console depending on the region.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>La surfeuse de California Games incarne parfaitement l’ambiance californienne du jeu, entre plage, soleil et culture sportive. Elle renvoie à l’épreuve de surf, où le joueur doit maîtriser l’équilibre sur la vague, enchaîner les figures et gérer sa trajectoire avec précision pour éviter la chute.
Fun fact : California Games a été utilisé comme jeu de lancement de l’Atari Lynx, souvent inclus avec la console selon les régions.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>La surfista de California Games encarna perfectamente el ambiente californiano del juego, entre playa, sol y cultura deportiva. Remite a la prueba de surf, donde el jugador debe dominar el equilibrio sobre la ola, enlazar maniobras y controlar la trayectoria con precisión para evitar la caída.
Dato curioso: California Games se usó como juego de lanzamiento de Atari Lynx y a menudo se incluía con la consola según la región.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>La surfista di California Games incarna perfettamente l’atmosfera californiana del gioco, tra spiaggia, sole e cultura sportiva. Rimanda alla prova di surf, in cui il giocatore deve controllare l’equilibrio sull’onda, concatenare le acrobazie e gestire la traiettoria con precisione per evitare la caduta.
Curiosità: California Games fu usato come gioco di lancio dell’Atari Lynx, spesso incluso con la console a seconda della regione.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Die Surferin aus California Games verkörpert die kalifornische Atmosphäre des Spiels mit Strand, Sonne und Sportkultur. Sie verweist auf die Surfdisziplin, in der der Spieler das Gleichgewicht auf der Welle halten, Manöver aneinanderreihen und die Flugbahn präzise steuern muss, um nicht zu stürzen.
Interessante Tatsache: California Games wurde als Startspiel für den Atari Lynx genutzt und je nach Region oft mit der Konsole gebündelt.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>A surfista de California Games representa perfeitamente o ambiente californiano do jogo, entre praia, sol e cultura desportiva. Ela remete para a prova de surf, em que o jogador deve dominar o equilíbrio na onda, encadear manobras e controlar a trajetória com precisão para evitar a queda.
Curiosidade: California Games foi usado como jogo de lançamento do Atari Lynx, muitas vezes incluído com a consola conforme a região.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
