<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>Mega Man is a series of action-platform games from Capcom in which the robot Mega Man battles Dr. Wily and his evil robots. The gameplay is based on non-linear levels, with each boss defeated giving rise to a new weapon. Renowned for its difficulty and precision, the saga has evolved into several sub-series, such as X and Battle Network. It remains an icon of retro-gaming and action-platforming.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Mega Man est une série de jeux d’action-plateforme de Capcom où le robot Mega Man affronte le Dr. Wily et ses robots maléfiques. Le gameplay repose sur des niveaux non linéaires, où chaque boss vaincu donne une nouvelle arme. Connue pour sa difficulté et sa précision, la saga a évolué avec plusieurs sous-séries comme X et Battle Network. Elle reste une icône du rétro-gaming et de l’action-plateforme.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Mega Man es una serie de juegos de acción y plataformas de Capcom en la que el robot Mega Man se enfrenta al Dr. Wily y a sus robots malvados. Su jugabilidad se basa en niveles no lineales, donde cada jefe derrotado otorga una nueva arma. Conocida por su dificultad y precisión, la saga evolucionó con varias subsagas como X y Battle Network. Sigue siendo un icono del retro-gaming y de la acción-plataformas.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Mega Man è una serie di giochi action-platform di Capcom in cui il robot Mega Man affronta il Dr. Wily e i suoi robot malvagi. Il gameplay si basa su livelli non lineari, dove ogni boss sconfitto permette di ottenere una nuova arma. Nota per difficoltà e precisione, la saga si è evoluta in varie sottoserie come X e Battle Network. Resta un’icona del retrogaming e dell’action-platform.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Mega Man ist eine Action-Plattformspielreihe von Capcom, in der der Roboter Mega Man gegen Dr. Wily und seine bösen Roboter kämpft. Das Gameplay basiert auf nichtlinearen Levels, wobei jeder besiegte Boss eine neue Waffe freischaltet. Bekannt für Schwierigkeit und Präzision, entwickelte sich die Saga mit Unterreihen wie X und Battle Network weiter. Sie bleibt eine Ikone des Retro-Gamings.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Mega Man é uma série de jogos de ação e plataforma da Capcom em que o robô Mega Man enfrenta o Dr. Wily e seus robôs malignos. A jogabilidade se baseia em fases não lineares, nas quais cada chefe derrotado concede uma nova arma. Conhecida por sua dificuldade e precisão, a saga evoluiu com várias subséries como X e Battle Network. Continua sendo um ícone do retro-gaming e da ação-plataforma.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Mega Man (NES, 1987)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>Mega Man is a combat robot able to copy enemy weapons, recognizable by his arm cannon aimed at the target, symbolizing gameplay built around adaptation and strategic power choices in demanding levels where each new ability changes the player’s approach.
Fun fact: Mega Man is known in Japan as Rockman, a pun linked to Roll, his robot sister, forming the duo “Rock and Roll”.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Mega Man est un robot de combat capable de copier les armes de ses ennemis, reconnaissable à son bras modifié en canon qu’il dirige vers sa cible, symbole d’un gameplay basé sur l’adaptation et le choix stratégique des pouvoirs, incarnant un héros technologique confronté à des adversaires variés dans des niveaux exigeants où chaque capacité acquise change l’approche du joueur.
Fun fact : Mega Man est connu au Japon sous le nom Rockman, un jeu de mots lié à Roll, sa sœur robot, formant le duo “Rock and Roll”.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Mega Man es un robot de combate capaz de copiar las armas de sus enemigos, reconocible por su brazo transformado en cañón apuntando al objetivo, símbolo de una jugabilidad basada en la adaptación y la elección estratégica de poderes en niveles exigentes donde cada habilidad cambia el enfoque del jugador.
Dato curioso: Mega Man se conoce en Japón como Rockman, un juego de palabras relacionado con Roll, su hermana robot, formando el dúo “Rock and Roll”.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Mega Man è un robot da combattimento capace di copiare le armi dei nemici, riconoscibile dal braccio trasformato in cannone puntato sul bersaglio, simbolo di un gameplay basato sull’adattamento e sulla scelta strategica dei poteri in livelli impegnativi dove ogni abilità cambia l’approccio del giocatore.
Curiosità: Mega Man in Giappone è conosciuto come Rockman, un gioco di parole legato a Roll, sua sorella robot, formando il duo “Rock and Roll”.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Mega Man ist ein Kampfroboter, der die Waffen seiner Gegner kopieren kann, erkennbar an seinem zum Kanonarm umgebauten Arm, den er auf sein Ziel richtet, als Symbol für ein Gameplay, das auf Anpassung und strategischer Wahl von Kräften in anspruchsvollen Levels basiert.
Interessante Tatsache: Mega Man heißt in Japan Rockman, ein Wortspiel mit Roll, seiner Roboter-Schwester, zusammen bilden sie “Rock and Roll”.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Mega Man é um robô de combate capaz de copiar as armas dos inimigos, reconhecível pelo braço transformado em canhão apontado para o alvo, símbolo de uma jogabilidade baseada em adaptação e escolha estratégica de poderes em fases exigentes onde cada habilidade muda a abordagem do jogador.
Curiosidade: Mega Man é conhecido no Japão como Rockman, um trocadilho ligado a Roll, sua irmã robô, formando a dupla “Rock and Roll”.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
