<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>The Mega Drive (メガドライブ, Mega Doraibu), or Genesis in North America, is marketed by Japanese manufacturer Sega Enterprises, Ltd. It is Sega's third console, the successor to the Master System, and will compete fiercely against Nintendo's SNES. Whatever happens, never forget that Sega is stronger than you.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>La Mega Drive (メガドライブ, Mega Doraibu), ou Genesis en Amérique du Nord, est commercialisée par le constructeur japonais Sega Enterprises, Ltd. C'est la troisième console de Sega, elle succède à la Master System et rivalisera avec ferveur contre la SNES de Nintendo. Quoi qu'il arrive n'oublie jamais que Sega c'est plus fort que toi.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>La Mega Drive (メガドライブ, Mega Doraibu), o Genesis en Norteamérica, es comercializada por el fabricante japonés Sega Enterprises, Ltd. Es la tercera consola de Sega, sucesora de la Master System y competirá ferozmente con la SNES de Nintendo. Pase lo que pase, nunca olvides que Sega es más fuerte que tú.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Il Mega Drive (メガドライブ, Mega Doraibu), o Genesis in Nord America, è commercializzato dal produttore giapponese Sega Enterprises, Ltd. È la terza console di Sega, il successore del Master System e competerà ferocemente contro lo SNES di Nintendo. Qualunque cosa accada, non dimenticate mai che Sega è più forte di voi.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Das Mega Drive (メガドライブ, Mega Doraibu), in Nordamerika auch Genesis genannt, wird von dem japanischen Hersteller Sega Enterprises, Ltd. vertrieben. Es ist Segas dritte Konsole, die das Master System ablöst und mit dem SNES von Nintendo konkurrieren wird. Was auch immer geschieht, vergiss nie, dass Sega stärker ist als du.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>A Mega Drive (メガドライブ, Mega Doraibu), ou Génesis na América do Norte, é comercializada pelo fabricante japonês Sega Enterprises, Ltd. É a terceira consola da Sega, a sucessora do Master System e irá competir ferozmente contra a SNES da Nintendo. Aconteça o que acontecer, nunca se esqueça que a Sega é mais forte do que você.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Streets of Rage (1991)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>Blaze Fielding is a former police officer determined to take back a city ruled by a crime syndicate. Fast and technical, she relies on kicks and precise combos, giving her a more agile style than her partners. On Mega Drive, she forms with Axel and Adam an iconic trio in an urban beat ’em up driven by a nocturnal mood and a memorable soundtrack.
Fun fact: Blaze is one of the few playable female characters in early 90s beat ’em ups, with a central role from the first game.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Blaze Fielding est une ancienne policière déterminée à reprendre une ville dominée par un syndicat du crime. Rapide et technique, elle privilégie les coups de pied et les enchaînements précis, avec un style plus agile que ses partenaires. Sur Mega Drive, elle forme avec Axel et Adam un trio emblématique du beat’em up urbain porté par une ambiance nocturne et une bande-son culte.
Fun fact : Blaze fait partie des rares personnages féminins jouables dans les beat’em up du début des années 90, avec un rôle central dès le premier épisode.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Blaze Fielding es una antigua policía decidida a recuperar una ciudad dominada por un sindicato criminal. Rápida y técnica, apuesta por patadas y combinaciones precisas, con un estilo más ágil que el de sus compañeros. En Mega Drive, forma con Axel y Adam un trío emblemático en un beat ’em up urbano marcado por una atmósfera nocturna y una banda sonora destacada.
Dato curioso: Blaze es uno de los pocos personajes femeninos jugables en los beat ’em up de principios de los 90, con un papel central desde el primer juego.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Blaze Fielding è un’ex poliziotta decisa a riprendere una città dominata da un sindacato criminale. Rapida e tecnica, punta su calci e combo precise, con uno stile più agile rispetto ai suoi compagni. Su Mega Drive, forma con Axel e Adam un trio emblematico in un beat ’em up urbano segnato da un’atmosfera notturna e da una colonna sonora memorabile.
Curiosità: Blaze è uno dei pochi personaggi femminili giocabili nei beat ’em up dei primi anni 90, con un ruolo centrale fin dal primo gioco.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Blaze Fielding ist eine ehemalige Polizistin, die eine von einem Verbrechersyndikat beherrschte Stadt zurückerobern will. Schnell und technisch, setzt sie auf Tritte und präzise Kombinationen, wodurch ihr Stil beweglicher wirkt als der ihrer Partner. Auf dem Mega Drive bildet sie mit Axel und Adam ein prägendes Trio in einem urbanen Beat ’em up mit nächtlicher Stimmung und markantem Soundtrack.
Interessante Tatsache: Blaze gehört zu den wenigen spielbaren weiblichen Figuren in Beat ’em ups der frühen 90er und hat von Anfang an eine zentrale Rolle.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Blaze Fielding é uma ex-policial decidida a retomar uma cidade dominada por um sindicato do crime. Rápida e técnica, aposta em chutes e combinações precisas, com um estilo mais ágil que o de seus parceiros. No Mega Drive, forma com Axel e Adam um trio marcante em um beat ’em up urbano guiado por uma atmosfera noturna e uma trilha sonora memorável.
Curiosidade: Blaze é uma das poucas personagens femininas jogáveis nos beat ’em up do início dos anos 90, com um papel central desde o primeiro jogo.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>