<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>Metal Gear is a series of action games created by Hideo Kojima, centered on Solid Snake's missions of espionage and sabotage. The saga blends strategy, infiltration and combat with themes of geopolitics and nuclear war. It stands out for its innovative gameplay, complex storyline and deep characters. Metal Gear is a benchmark for the genre, profoundly influencing the video game industry.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Metal Gear est une série de jeux d'action créée par Hideo Kojima, centrée sur les missions d'espionnage et de sabotage menées par Solid Snake. La saga mêle stratégie, infiltration et combats tout en abordant des thèmes de géopolitique et de la guerre nucléaire. Elle se distingue par son gameplay innovant, son scénario complexe et ses personnages profonds. Metal Gear est une référence du genre, influençant profondément l'industrie du jeu vidéo.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Metal Gear es una serie de juegos de acción creada por Hideo Kojima, centrada en las misiones de espionaje y sabotaje de Solid Snake. La saga combina estrategia, infiltración y combate con temas de geopolítica y guerra nuclear. Destaca por su jugabilidad innovadora, su trama compleja y sus personajes profundos. Metal Gear es una referencia del género que influyó profundamente en la industria del videojuego.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Metal Gear è una serie di giochi d’azione creata da Hideo Kojima, incentrata sulle missioni di spionaggio e sabotaggio di Solid Snake. La saga unisce strategia, infiltrazione e combattimento affrontando temi di geopolitica e guerra nucleare. Si distingue per il gameplay innovativo, la trama complessa e i personaggi profondi. Metal Gear è un punto di riferimento del genere e ha influenzato profondamente l’industria videoludica.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Metal Gear ist eine Actionspielreihe von Hideo Kojima, die sich um Solid Snakes Spionage- und Sabotagemissionen dreht. Die Saga verbindet Strategie, Infiltration und Kampf mit Themen wie Geopolitik und Atomkrieg. Sie zeichnet sich durch innovatives Gameplay, eine komplexe Handlung und vielschichtige Figuren aus. Metal Gear gilt als Maßstab des Genres und hat die Videospielindustrie stark geprägt.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Metal Gear é uma série de jogos de ação criada por Hideo Kojima, centrada nas missões de espionagem e sabotagem de Solid Snake. A saga combina estratégia, infiltração e combate com temas de geopolítica e guerra nuclear. Destaca-se pela jogabilidade inovadora, pela história complexa e por personagens marcantes. Metal Gear é uma referência do gênero e influenciou profundamente a indústria dos videogames.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Metal Gear Solid (PlayStation, 1998)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>Solid Snake is a stealth operative specializing in infiltration missions, recognizable by his bandana and lightweight gear, combining discretion and efficiency with firearms and close combat in environments under heavy surveillance.
Fun fact: Snake’s bandana can grant special bonuses depending on the game, such as infinite ammo, becoming both a visual and gameplay icon.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Solid Snake est un agent d’infiltration spécialisé dans les missions furtives, reconnaissable à son bandana et son équipement léger, combinant discrétion et efficacité en utilisant armes à feu et combat rapproché, incarnant une approche stratégique où éviter les affrontements est souvent aussi crucial que savoir les mener dans des environnements sous haute surveillance.
Fun fact : Le bandana de Snake peut offrir des bonus spéciaux selon les jeux, comme des munitions infinies, devenant un élément emblématique autant visuel que gameplay.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Solid Snake es un agente especializado en infiltración, reconocible por su bandana y equipo ligero, combinando discreción y eficacia con armas de fuego y combate cercano en zonas bajo vigilancia extrema.
Dato curioso: La bandana de Snake puede otorgar ventajas especiales según el juego, como munición infinita, convirtiéndose en un icono visual y jugable.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Solid Snake è un agente esperto in infiltrazione, riconoscibile per la bandana e l’equipaggiamento leggero, capace di unire furtività ed efficacia tra armi da fuoco e combattimento ravvicinato.
Curiosità: La bandana di Snake può offrire bonus speciali a seconda del gioco, come munizioni infinite, diventando un’icona visiva e di gameplay.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Solid Snake ist ein Infiltrationsexperte, erkennbar an seinem Bandana und der leichten Ausrüstung, der Tarnung und Effizienz mit Schusswaffen und Nahkampf in stark bewachten Bereichen verbindet.
Interessante Tatsache: Snakes Bandana kann je nach Spiel besondere Vorteile wie unendliche Munition bieten und wurde so zum visuellen und spielerischen Symbol.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Solid Snake é um agente de infiltração reconhecido pela bandana e pelo equipamento leve, combinando furtividade e eficiência com armas de fogo e combate próximo em áreas muito vigiadas.
Curiosidade: A bandana de Snake pode conceder bônus especiais conforme o jogo, como munição infinita, tornando-se um ícone visual e de jogabilidade.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
