<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>Metal Slug is a 2D shooter series developed by SNK, known for its frenetic action and detailed pixel art graphics. Players control soldiers battling enemies through levels filled with impressive weapons, vehicles and bosses. The series stands out for its cooperative gameplay, humor and quirky atmosphere. Metal Slug is a classic of the “run and gun” genre and a mainstay of arcade games.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Metal Slug est une série de jeux de tir en 2D développée par SNK, connue pour son action frénétique et ses graphismes pixel art détaillés. Les joueurs contrôlent des soldats combattant des ennemis à travers des niveaux remplis d'armes, de véhicules et de boss impressionnants. La série se distingue par son gameplay coopératif, son humour et son atmosphère décalée. Metal Slug est un classique du genre "run and gun" et un pilier des jeux d'arcade.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Metal Slug es una serie de juegos de disparos en 2D desarrollada por SNK, conocida por su acción frenética y sus gráficos pixel art detallados. Los jugadores controlan soldados que combaten enemigos en niveles llenos de armas, vehículos y jefes impresionantes. La serie destaca por su juego cooperativo, humor y atmósfera peculiar. Metal Slug es un clásico del género run and gun y un pilar de los arcades.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Metal Slug è una serie di sparatutto 2D sviluppata da SNK, nota per l’azione frenetica e la grafica pixel art dettagliata. I giocatori controllano soldati che affrontano nemici in livelli pieni di armi, veicoli e boss spettacolari. La serie si distingue per il gameplay cooperativo, l’umorismo e l’atmosfera particolare. Metal Slug è un classico del genere run and gun e un punto fermo delle sale giochi.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Metal Slug ist eine 2D-Shooter-Reihe von SNK, bekannt für rasante Action und detaillierte Pixel-Art-Grafik. Die Spieler steuern Soldaten, die sich durch Level voller Waffen, Fahrzeuge und eindrucksvoller Bosse kämpfen. Die Reihe zeichnet sich durch kooperatives Gameplay, Humor und eine eigenwillige Atmosphäre aus. Metal Slug ist ein Klassiker des Run-and-Gun-Genres und ein fester Bestandteil der Arcade-Spiele.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Metal Slug é uma série de jogos de tiro em 2D desenvolvida pela SNK, conhecida pela ação frenética e pelos gráficos detalhados em pixel art. Os jogadores controlam soldados que enfrentam inimigos em fases cheias de armas, veículos e chefes impressionantes. A série se destaca pelo modo cooperativo, humor e atmosfera peculiar. Metal Slug é um clássico do gênero run and gun e um marco dos arcades.</text>
</text>


<!-- FIGURINE -->

<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Metal Slug (Arcade, 1996)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>The SV-001 Metal Slug is an iconic mini tank recognized for its compact, sturdy design, delivering considerable firepower in chaotic environments while retaining strong mobility, perfectly embodying the series’ balance between massive destruction and immediate accessibility. Fun fact: The Metal Slug series is famous for its extremely detailed pixel art animations, often considered among the finest of 2D arcade gaming.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Le SV-001 Metal Slug est un mini tank emblématique reconnaissable à son design compact et robuste, offrant une puissance de feu considérable dans des environnements chaotiques, permettant aux joueurs de résister aux vagues ennemies tout en conservant une grande mobilité, incarnant parfaitement l’équilibre entre destruction massive et accessibilité propre à la série.
Fun fact : La série Metal Slug est célèbre pour ses animations extrêmement détaillées en pixel art, souvent considérées comme parmi les plus abouties de l’arcade 2D.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>El SV-001 Metal Slug es un mini tanque emblemático reconocible por su diseño compacto y robusto, con una gran potencia de fuego en entornos caóticos mientras conserva una movilidad notable, encarnando el equilibrio entre destrucción masiva y accesibilidad propio de la serie.
Dato curioso: Metal Slug es famosa por sus animaciones de pixel art extremadamente detalladas, consideradas entre las mejores del arcade 2D.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Lo SV-001 Metal Slug è un mini carro armato emblematico, riconoscibile per il design compatto e robusto, capace di offrire grande potenza di fuoco in ambienti caotici mantenendo una notevole mobilità, incarnando l’equilibrio tra distruzione e accessibilità tipico della serie.
Curiosità: Metal Slug è celebre per le animazioni pixel art estremamente dettagliate, considerate tra le migliori dell’arcade 2D.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Der SV-001 Metal Slug ist ein ikonischer Mini-Panzer mit kompaktem und robustem Design, der in chaotischen Umgebungen enorme Feuerkraft bietet und zugleich beweglich bleibt, wodurch er das Gleichgewicht aus massiver Zerstörung und direkter Zugänglichkeit der Reihe verkörpert.
Interessante Tatsache: Metal Slug ist für extrem detailreiche Pixel-Art-Animationen bekannt, die zu den besten der 2D-Arcade-Ära zählen.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>O SV-001 Metal Slug é um mini tanque emblemático, reconhecido pelo design compacto e robusto, oferecendo grande poder de fogo em cenários caóticos enquanto mantém boa mobilidade, representando o equilíbrio entre destruição massiva e acessibilidade típico da série.
Curiosidade: Metal Slug é famosa por suas animações em pixel art extremamente detalhadas, consideradas entre as melhores do arcade 2D.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
