<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>Metroid is a series of action-adventure games developed by Nintendo, in which bounty hunter Samus Aran explores alien worlds while battling creatures and space pirates. The “Metroidvania” gameplay combines exploration, acquiring new powers and solving puzzles. The immersive atmosphere and sci-fi elements make this a striking series. Metroid is a benchmark for the genre, influencing many open-world adventure games.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Metroid est une série de jeux d’action-aventure développée par Nintendo, où la chasseuse de primes Samus Aran explore des mondes extraterrestres tout en combattant des créatures et des pirates de l'espace. Le gameplay "Metroidvania" combine exploration, acquisition de nouveaux pouvoirs et résolutions de puzzles. Metroid est une référence du genre, influençant de nombreux jeux d’aventure en monde ouvert.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Metroid es una serie de juegos de acción y aventura desarrollada por Nintendo, en la que la cazarrecompensas Samus Aran explora mundos alienígenas mientras combate criaturas y piratas espaciales. Su jugabilidad combina exploración, mejoras progresivas y resolución de puzles. Metroid es una referencia del género e influyó en muchos juegos de aventura basados en la exploración.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Metroid è una serie di giochi d’azione e avventura sviluppata da Nintendo, in cui la cacciatrice di taglie Samus Aran esplora mondi alieni combattendo creature e pirati spaziali. Il gameplay combina esplorazione, potenziamenti progressivi e risoluzione di enigmi. Metroid è un riferimento del genere e ha influenzato molti giochi d’avventura basati sull’esplorazione.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Metroid ist eine Action-Adventure-Reihe von Nintendo, in der die Kopfgeldjägerin Samus Aran fremde Welten erkundet und gegen Kreaturen sowie Weltraumpiraten kämpft. Das Gameplay verbindet Erkundung, neue Fähigkeiten und Rätsel. Metroid gilt als Referenz des Genres und beeinflusste viele erkundungsbasierte Abenteuerspiele.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Metroid é uma série de ação e aventura desenvolvida pela Nintendo, na qual a caçadora de recompensas Samus Aran explora mundos alienígenas enquanto enfrenta criaturas e piratas espaciais. A jogabilidade combina exploração, melhorias progressivas e resolução de puzzles. Metroid é uma referência do gênero e influenciou muitos jogos de aventura baseados em exploração.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Metroid (NES, 1986)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>Samus Aran is a bounty hunter in a high-tech suit, equipped with an arm cannon and exploring hostile environments where each upgrade opens new areas, embodying progression through discovery and survival in an oppressive alien world.
Fun fact: The original Metroid features multiple endings based on completion time, gradually revealing that Samus is a woman, with a suitless version only for the fastest players.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Samus Aran est une chasseuse de primes en armure high-tech, reconnaissable à son canon intégré, explorant des environnements hostiles où chaque amélioration ouvre de nouvelles zones, incarnant une progression basée sur la découverte et la survie dans un monde alien oppressant.
Fun fact : Le premier Metroid propose plusieurs fins selon le temps de complétion, révélant progressivement que Samus est une femme, avec une version sans armure uniquement pour les joueurs les plus rapides.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Samus Aran es una cazarrecompensas con armadura avanzada y cañón integrado, explorando entornos hostiles donde cada mejora abre nuevas zonas, encarnando una progresión basada en descubrimiento y supervivencia.
Dato curioso: El primer Metroid tiene varios finales según el tiempo, revelando progresivamente que Samus es una mujer.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Samus Aran è una cacciatrice di taglie con armatura tecnologica e cannone integrato, esplora ambienti ostili dove ogni potenziamento apre nuove aree, incarnando scoperta e sopravvivenza.
Curiosità: Il primo Metroid presenta finali multipli in base al tempo, rivelando progressivamente che Samus è una donna.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Samus Aran ist eine Kopfgeldjägerin mit Hightech-Rüstung und Armkanone, die feindliche Umgebungen erkundet, in denen jedes Upgrade neue Bereiche öffnet und Überleben verlangt.
Interessante Tatsache: Das erste Metroid bietet mehrere Enden je nach Spielzeit und enthüllt nach und nach, dass Samus eine Frau ist.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Samus Aran é uma caçadora de recompensas com armadura avançada e canhão integrado, explorando ambientes hostis onde cada melhoria abre novas áreas, unindo descoberta e sobrevivência.
Curiosidade: O primeiro Metroid possui múltiplos finais conforme o tempo, revelando progressivamente que Samus é uma mulher.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
