<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>Mitchell Corporation (株式会社ミッチェル) was a Japanese video game developer.  Some of the employees were former employees of Capcom and TAD Corporation. The company's business was suspended on 20 November 2012.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Mitchell Corporation (株式会社ミッチェル) était un développeur de jeux vidéo japonais.  Certains employés étaient d'anciens employés de Capcom et de TAD Corporation. L'activité de la société a été suspendue le 20 novembre 2012.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Mitchell Corporation (株式会社ミッチェル) war ein japanischer Entwickler von Videospielen.  Einige Mitarbeiter waren ehemalige Mitarbeiter von Capcom und der TAD Corporation. Die Geschäftstätigkeit des Unternehmens wurde am 20. November 2012 eingestellt.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Mitchell Corporation (株式会社ミッチェル) fue un desarrollador japonés de videojuegos.  Algunos empleados eran antiguos empleados de Capcom y TAD Corporation. La actividad de la empresa se suspendió el 20 de noviembre de 2012.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Mitchell Corporation (株式会社ミッチェル) era uno sviluppatore di videogiochi giapponese.  Alcuni dipendenti erano ex dipendenti di Capcom e TAD Corporation. L'attività della società è stata sospesa il 20 novembre 2012.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>株式会社ミッチェル（株式会社ミッチェル）は、日本のビデオゲーム開発会社である。 社員の中には、カプコンや株式会社TADの元社員もいた。2012年11月20日に営業停止となった。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>Mitchell Corporation (株式会社ミッチェル) was een Japanse ontwikkelaar van videospelletjes.  Sommige werknemers waren voormalige werknemers van Capcom en TAD Corporation. Het bedrijf werd op 20 november 2012 stilgelegd.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>Mitchell Corporation (株式会社ミッチェル) był japońskim producentem gier wideo.  Część pracowników to byli pracownicy Capcomu i TAD Corporation. Działalność firmy została zawieszona 20 listopada 2012 roku.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>A Mitchell Corporation (株式会社ミッチェル) era uma empresa japonesa de desenvolvimento de jogos de vídeo.  Alguns empregados eram antigos empregados da Capcom e da TAD Corporation. Os negócios da empresa foram suspensos a 20 de Novembro de 2012.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>Mitchell Corporation (株式会社ミッチェル) была японским разработчиком видеоигр.  Некоторые сотрудники компании были бывшими работниками Capcom и TAD Corporation. Деятельность компании была приостановлена 20 ноября 2012 года.</text>
</text>


<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Pang (1989)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>The brothers Buster and Nick travel the world destroying huge bouncing bubbles that split with each shot. Pang is built around fast, readable stages where players must anticipate trajectories, avoid rebounds and use bonuses to clear the screen before being overwhelmed.
Fun fact: Pang is known in Japan as Pomping World, while Buster Bros. was mainly used for the North American release.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Les frères Buster et Nick parcourent le monde pour détruire d’immenses bulles rebondissantes qui se divisent à chaque tir. Pang repose sur des parties rapides et lisibles où le joueur doit anticiper les trajectoires, éviter les ricochets et utiliser différents bonus pour nettoyer l’écran avant d’être submergé.
Fun fact : Pang est connu au Japon sous le nom Pomping World, tandis que le nom Buster Bros. a surtout été utilisé en Amérique du Nord.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Los hermanos Buster y Nick recorren el mundo para destruir enormes burbujas rebotantes que se dividen con cada disparo. Pang se basa en partidas rápidas y claras donde el jugador debe anticipar trayectorias, evitar rebotes y usar distintos bonus para limpiar la pantalla antes de verse superado.
Dato curioso: Pang se conoce en Japón como Pomping World, mientras que Buster Bros. se usó sobre todo en Norteamérica.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>I fratelli Buster e Nick viaggiano per il mondo per distruggere enormi bolle rimbalzanti che si dividono a ogni colpo. Pang propone partite rapide e leggibili in cui bisogna anticipare le traiettorie, evitare i rimbalzi e usare vari bonus per ripulire lo schermo prima di essere travolti.
Curiosità: Pang è conosciuto in Giappone come Pomping World, mentre Buster Bros. fu usato soprattutto in Nord America.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Die Brüder Buster und Nick reisen um die Welt, um riesige springende Blasen zu zerstören, die sich bei jedem Treffer teilen. Pang setzt auf schnelle, gut lesbare Runden, in denen man Flugbahnen vorausplanen, Abpraller meiden und Boni nutzen muss, bevor der Bildschirm überfüllt ist.
Interessante Tatsache: Pang ist in Japan als Pomping World bekannt, während Buster Bros. vor allem in Nordamerika verwendet wurde.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Os irmãos Buster e Nick viajam pelo mundo para destruir enormes bolhas saltitantes que se dividem a cada disparo. Pang aposta em partidas rápidas e claras, nas quais o jogador deve antecipar trajetórias, evitar ressaltos e usar bônus para limpar a tela antes de ser dominado.
Curiosidade: Pang é conhecido no Japão como Pomping World, enquanto Buster Bros. foi usado principalmente na América do Norte.</text>
</text>


</view>
</theme>
