<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>The MSX2+ standard offered graphics up to 512 × 212 pixels in 16 of 512 colours and an audio processor: 3-voice, 8-octave sound. Video memory was a minimum of 128 KB.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>La norme MSX2+ propose des graphismes jusqu’en 512 × 212 pixels en 16 couleurs parmi 512 et un processeur audio : son sur 3 voix et 8 octaves. La mémoire vidéo était au minimum de 128 Ko.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Der MSX2+-Standard bot Grafiken bis zu 512 × 212 Pixel in 16 von 512 Farben und einen Audioprozessor: dreistimmiger Ton und 8 Oktaven. Der Videospeicher war mindestens 128 KB groß.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>El estándar MSX2+ ofrecía gráficos de hasta 512 × 212 píxeles en 16 de 512 colores y un procesador de audio: sonido de 3 voces y 8 octavas. La memoria de vídeo era de un mínimo de 128 KB.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Lo standard MSX2+ offriva una grafica fino a 512 × 212 pixel in 16 di 512 colori e un processore audio: suono a 3 voci e 8 ottave. La memoria video era di almeno 128 KB.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>MSX2+規格では、グラフィックは最大512×212ピクセル、512色中16色、オーディオプロセッサ：3ボイス、8オクターブのサウンドを提供した。ビデオメモリは最低128KBでした。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>De MSX2+ standaard bood graphics tot 512 × 212 pixels in 16 van 512 kleuren en een audioprocessor: 3-stemmig, 8-octaafs geluid. Het videogeheugen was minimaal 128 KB.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>Standard MSX2+ oferował grafikę do 512 × 212 pikseli w 16 z 512 kolorów oraz procesor audio: 3-głosowy, 8-oktawowy dźwięk. Pamięć wideo wynosiła minimum 128 KB.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>O padrão MSX2+ oferecia gráficos até 512 × 212 pixels em 16 de 512 cores e um processador de áudio: 3-vozes, som de 8-octave. A memória de vídeo era de um mínimo de 128 KB.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>Стандарт MSX2+ предлагает графику до 512 × 212 пикселей в 16 из 512 цветов и аудиопроцессор: 3-голосный, 8-октавный звук. Видеопамять составляла минимум 128 КБ.</text>
</text>


<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Space Manbow (1989)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>The Manbow-J crosses space bases and organic zones in a smooth scrolling shoot ’em up built to use the MSX2’s strengths. Its steerable modules, evolving shots and large bosses give it a strong Konami identity. This figurine highlights an elegant, technical and instantly recognizable ship.
Fun fact: Space Manbow was born after Konami dropped an MSX adaptation of Thunder Cross, considered too limited to be worthwhile.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Le Manbow-J traverse des bases spatiales et des zones organiques dans un shoot’em up à scrolling fluide, pensé pour exploiter les capacités du MSX2. Ses modules orientables, ses tirs évolutifs et ses boss massifs donnent au jeu une identité Konami très marquée. Cette figurine met en avant un vaisseau élégant, technique et immédiatement reconnaissable.
Fun fact : Space Manbow est né après l’abandon d’une adaptation MSX de Thunder Cross, jugée trop peu intéressante par Konami.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>El Manbow-J cruza bases espaciales y zonas orgánicas en un shoot ’em up de desplazamiento fluido, pensado para aprovechar el MSX2. Sus módulos orientables, disparos evolutivos y grandes jefes le dan una identidad Konami muy marcada. Esta figura destaca una nave elegante, técnica y reconocible al instante.
Dato curioso: Space Manbow nació tras abandonar Konami una adaptación MSX de Thunder Cross, considerada poco interesante.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Il Manbow-J attraversa basi spaziali e zone organiche in uno shoot ’em up a scorrimento fluido, pensato per sfruttare il MSX2. Moduli orientabili, colpi evolutivi e grandi boss gli danno una forte identità Konami. Questa statuetta valorizza una nave elegante, tecnica e subito riconoscibile.
Curiosità: Space Manbow nacque dopo che Konami abbandonò un adattamento MSX di Thunder Cross, ritenuto poco interessante.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Die Manbow-J fliegt durch Raumstationen und organische Zonen in einem flüssig scrollenden Shoot ’em up, das die Stärken des MSX2 nutzt. Steuerbare Module, aufrüstbare Schüsse und große Bosse geben dem Spiel eine klare Konami-Identität. Diese Figur zeigt ein elegantes, technisches und sofort erkennbares Schiff.
Interessante Tatsache: Space Manbow entstand, nachdem Konami eine MSX-Umsetzung von Thunder Cross als zu wenig interessant aufgegeben hatte.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>A Manbow-J atravessa bases espaciais e zonas orgânicas num shoot ’em up de deslocamento fluido, pensado para explorar o MSX2. Módulos orientáveis, tiros evolutivos e grandes bosses dão ao jogo uma forte identidade Konami. Esta figura destaca uma nave elegante, técnica e imediatamente reconhecível.
Curiosidade: Space Manbow nasceu após a Konami abandonar uma adaptação MSX de Thunder Cross, considerada pouco interessante.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
