<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>For this standard, there was an 8-channel sound expansion cartridge and a sound library, this cartridge named FM-PAC was compatible with several MSX games from different publishers. Another example is the Philips Music Module, a cartridge with MIDI and RCA connectors, for which a piano was available as an option.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Il existait pour ce standard, une cartouche d’extension sonore à 8 canaux et une bibliothèque sonore, cette cartouche nommée FM-PAC était compatible avec plusieurs jeux MSX de différents éditeurs. On peut également citer le Music Module de Philips, cartouche avec prises MIDI et connecteurs RCA, pour laquelle un piano était disponible en option.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Für diesen Standard gab es eine Tonerweiterungskassette mit 8 Kanälen und einer Tonbibliothek, diese FM-PAC genannte Kassette war mit mehreren MSX-Spielen verschiedener Hersteller kompatibel. Ein weiteres Beispiel ist das Music Module von Philips, eine Kassette mit MIDI- und Cinch-Anschlüssen, für die ein Klavier als Option erhältlich war.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Para este estándar, existía un cartucho de expansión de sonido de 8 canales y una biblioteca de sonidos, este cartucho llamado FM-PAC era compatible con varios juegos MSX de diferentes editores. Otro ejemplo es el Philips Music Module, un cartucho con conectores MIDI y RCA, para el que había disponible un piano como opción.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Per questo standard, esisteva una cartuccia di espansione sonora a 8 canali e una libreria sonora; questa cartuccia, denominata FM-PAC, era compatibile con numerosi giochi MSX di diversi editori. Un altro esempio è il Philips Music Module, una cartuccia con connettori MIDI e RCA, per la quale era disponibile un pianoforte come opzione.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>この規格のために、8チャンネルのサウンド拡張カートリッジとサウンドライブラリがあり、FM-PACと名付けられたこのカートリッジは、異なるパブリッシャーのいくつかのMSXゲームと互換性がありました。もう一つの例はフィリップスのミュージックモジュールで、MIDIとRCAコネクタを備えたカートリッジで、オプションとしてピアノが用意されていた。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>Voor deze standaard was er een 8-kanaals geluidsuitbreidingscartridge en een geluidsbibliotheek, deze cartridge met de naam FM-PAC was compatibel met verschillende MSX-spellen van verschillende uitgevers. Een ander voorbeeld is de Philips Music Module, een cartridge met MIDI en RCA aansluitingen, waarvoor als optie een piano beschikbaar was.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>Dla tego standardu istniał 8-kanałowy kartridż rozszerzający dźwięk oraz biblioteka dźwięków, kartridż ten o nazwie FM-PAC był kompatybilny z kilkoma grami MSX od różnych wydawców. Innym przykładem jest Philips Music Module, kartridż ze złączami MIDI i RCA, dla którego opcjonalnie dostępny był fortepian.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Para este padrão, havia um cartucho de expansão sonora de 8 canais e uma biblioteca de sons, este cartucho denominado FM-PAC era compatível com vários jogos MSX de diferentes editoras. Outro exemplo é o módulo de música Philips, um cartucho com conectores MIDI e RCA, para o qual estava disponível um piano como opção.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>Для этого стандарта существовал картридж расширения 8-канального звука и звуковая библиотека, этот картридж под названием FM-PAC был совместим с несколькими играми для MSX от разных издателей. Другим примером является Philips Music Module, картридж с MIDI и RCA разъемами, для которого в качестве опции было доступно пианино.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
