<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>The Nintendo 64DD (Disk Drive) is a peripheral for the Nintendo 64 system released only in Japan. It is connected via the extension port located under the console. It can read magnetic disks. A modem was also used to connect to the network and offered various options such as online gaming and Internet browsing.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Le Nintendo 64DD (Disk Drive) est un périphérique de la console Nintendo 64 sorti uniquement au Japon. Il se connecte via le port extension situé sous la console. Il permet de lire des disques magnétiques. Un modem permettait également de se connecter au réseau et offrait différentes options comme le jeu en ligne, ou la navigation sur Internet.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Das Nintendo 64DD (Disk Drive) ist ein Peripheriegerät für die Nintendo 64-Konsole, das nur in Japan veröffentlicht wurde. Es wird über den Erweiterungsanschluss an der Unterseite der Konsole angeschlossen. Es ermöglicht das Abspielen von magnetischen Discs. Ein Modem ermöglichte außerdem den Anschluss an ein Netzwerk und bot verschiedene Optionen wie Online-Spiele oder das Surfen im Internet.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>El Nintendo 64DD (Disk Drive) es un periférico para la consola Nintendo 64 lanzado únicamente en Japón. Se conecta a través del puerto de extensión situado bajo la consola. Puede leer discos magnéticos. También se utilizaba un módem para conectarse a la red y ofrecía diversas opciones, como juegos en línea y navegación por Internet.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Il Nintendo 64DD (Disk Drive) è una periferica per la console Nintendo 64 rilasciata solo in Giappone. Si collega tramite la porta di estensione situata sotto la console. Può leggere dischi magnetici. Per connettersi alla rete si utilizzava anche un modem che offriva varie opzioni come il gioco online e la navigazione in Internet.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>Nintendo 64DD（Disk Drive）は、日本でのみ発売されたNintendo 64システムの周辺機器です。本体下部にある拡張ポートで接続します。磁気ディスクを読み込むことができる。また、ネットワークへの接続にはモデムが使用され、オンラインゲームやインターネットブラウジングなど様々なオプションが提供された。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>De Nintendo 64DD (Disk Drive) is een randapparaat voor het Nintendo 64-systeem dat alleen in Japan werd uitgebracht. Het wordt aangesloten via de uitbreidingspoort onder de console. Het kan magnetische schijven lezen. Een modem werd ook gebruikt om verbinding te maken met het netwerk en bood verschillende mogelijkheden zoals online gaming en surfen op het internet.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>Nintendo 64DD (Disk Drive) to urządzenie peryferyjne dla systemu Nintendo 64 wydane tylko w Japonii. Podłącza się go poprzez port rozszerzeń znajdujący się pod konsolą. Może on odczytywać dyski magnetyczne. Do połączenia z siecią służył również modem, który oferował różne opcje, takie jak gry online i przeglądanie Internetu.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>O Nintendo 64DD (Disk Drive) é um periférico para o sistema Nintendo 64 lançado apenas no Japão. É ligado através da porta de extensão localizada por baixo da consola. Pode ler discos magnéticos. Foi também utilizado um modem para se ligar à rede e ofereceu várias opções, tais como jogos online e navegação na Internet.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>Nintendo 64DD (Disk Drive) - это периферийное устройство для системы Nintendo 64, выпущенное только в Японии. Он подключается через порт расширения, расположенный под консолью. Он может считывать магнитные диски. Модем также использовался для подключения к сети и предлагал различные возможности, такие как онлайн-игры и просмотр интернет-страниц.</text>
</text>


<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;SimCity 64 (2000)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>The mayor of SimCity 64 oversees the growth of a Japanese city on 64DD, balancing residential zones, roads, power, disasters and advice from Dr. Wright. This version keeps the spirit of SimCity 2000 while adding a city visible in 3D, with residents and vehicles seen up close. The figurine evokes a careful builder, caught between planning and surprises.
Fun fact: SimCity 64 let players walk at street level inside their own city, a very rare idea for the series at that time.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Le maire de SimCity 64 supervise la croissance d’une ville japonaise sur 64DD, entre zones résidentielles, routes, énergie, catastrophes et avis du Dr Wright. Cette version reprend l’esprit de SimCity 2000 tout en ajoutant une ville visible en 3D, avec des habitants et véhicules observables de près. La figurine évoque le bâtisseur attentif, partagé entre planification et imprévus.
Fun fact : SimCity 64 permettait de se promener au niveau des rues dans sa propre ville, une idée très rare dans la série à cette époque.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>El alcalde de SimCity 64 supervisa el crecimiento de una ciudad japonesa en 64DD, entre zonas residenciales, carreteras, energía, desastres y consejos del Dr. Wright. Esta versión mantiene el espíritu de SimCity 2000 y añade una ciudad visible en 3D, con habitantes y vehículos observables de cerca. La figurina evoca a un constructor atento, entre planificación e imprevistos.
Dato curioso: SimCity 64 permitía caminar a nivel de calle dentro de tu propia ciudad, una idea muy rara en la serie en aquella época.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Il sindaco di SimCity 64 supervisiona la crescita di una città giapponese su 64DD, tra zone residenziali, strade, energia, disastri e consigli del Dr. Wright. Questa versione mantiene lo spirito di SimCity 2000 e aggiunge una città visibile in 3D, con abitanti e veicoli osservabili da vicino. La figurina evoca un costruttore attento, tra pianificazione e imprevisti.
Curiosità: SimCity 64 permetteva di camminare al livello delle strade nella propria città, un’idea molto rara nella serie all’epoca.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Der Bürgermeister von SimCity 64 überwacht das Wachstum einer japanischen Stadt auf dem 64DD, mit Wohngebieten, Straßen, Energie, Katastrophen und Rat von Dr. Wright. Diese Version bewahrt den Geist von SimCity 2000 und ergänzt eine in 3D sichtbare Stadt, mit Bewohnern und Fahrzeugen aus der Nähe. Die Figur zeigt einen aufmerksamen Baumeister zwischen Planung und Überraschungen.
Interessante Tatsache: SimCity 64 erlaubte Spaziergänge auf Straßenhöhe durch die eigene Stadt, eine damals sehr seltene Idee in der Reihe.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>O prefeito de SimCity 64 acompanha o crescimento de uma cidade japonesa no 64DD, entre zonas residenciais, estradas, energia, desastres e conselhos do Dr. Wright. Esta versão mantém o espírito de SimCity 2000 e acrescenta uma cidade visível em 3D, com moradores e veículos vistos de perto. A figurine evoca um construtor atento, entre planejamento e imprevistos.
Curiosidade: SimCity 64 permitia caminhar ao nível das ruas dentro da própria cidade, uma ideia muito rara na série naquela época.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
