<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>This arcade system is based on the architecture of a PC. The hardware is modified and adapted to suit requirements. The game medium is DVD, and it works with its own dongle using USB technology, which must be plugged into the original memory card port. The system is not zoned, so all games can be run on any machine. The nationality of the game differs according to the programme on the DVD.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Ce système destiné aux salles d'arcade est construit selon l'architecture d'un PC. Le hardware est modifié et adapté aux besoins. Le support de jeu est le DVD, il fonctionne avec un dongle qui lui est propre et qui utilise la technologie USB, il doit être branché sur le port carte mémoire d'origine. Le système n'est pas zoné, il est possible de faire fonctionner tous les jeux sur n'importe quelle machine. La nationalité du jeu se différencie en fonction du programme sur le DVD.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Este sistema arcade está construido sobre la arquitectura de un PC. El hardware está modificado y adaptado a sus necesidades. El soporte de juego es DVD y funciona con su propio dongle mediante tecnología USB, que debe conectarse al puerto original de la tarjeta de memoria. El sistema no tiene bloqueo regional, por lo que todos los juegos pueden funcionar en cualquier máquina. La nacionalidad del juego depende del programa incluido en el DVD.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Questo sistema arcade è costruito sull'architettura di un PC. L'hardware è modificato e adattato alle esigenze. Il supporto di gioco è il DVD e funziona con un proprio dongle che utilizza la tecnologia USB, da collegare alla porta originale della memory card. Il sistema non è zonato, quindi tutti i giochi possono funzionare su qualsiasi macchina. La nazionalità del gioco dipende dal programma presente sul DVD.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Dieses Arcade-System basiert auf der Architektur eines PCs. Die Hardware wurde verändert und an die jeweiligen Anforderungen angepasst. Das Spielmedium ist eine DVD, die mit einem eigenen Dongle über USB-Technologie funktioniert und an den ursprünglichen Speicherkartenanschluss angeschlossen werden muss. Das System hat keine Regionalsperre, sodass alle Spiele auf jeder Maschine laufen können. Die Nationalität des Spiels hängt vom Programm auf der DVD ab.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Este sistema arcade é construído com base na arquitetura de um PC. O hardware é modificado e adaptado às necessidades. O suporte de jogo é DVD e funciona com o seu próprio dongle usando tecnologia USB, que deve ser ligado à porta original do cartão de memória. O sistema não tem bloqueio regional, por isso todos os jogos podem funcionar em qualquer máquina. A nacionalidade do jogo depende do programa no DVD.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Tekken 3 (1997)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>Jin Kazama appears in Tekken 3 after Kazuya Mishima's death, taking his place as the new central character. Son of Kazuya and Jun, he is trained by Heihachi and uses a style mixing karate with Mishima techniques. This figurine highlights his pivotal role in the series, between family legacy and his own identity on Namco arcade hardware.
Fun fact: Jin was created to replace Kazuya after his disappearance, while keeping visual and technical similarities so players would not feel lost.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Jin Kazama apparaît dans Tekken 3 après la mort de Kazuya Mishima, prenant sa place comme nouveau personnage central. Fils de Kazuya et Jun, il est formé par Heihachi et adopte un style mêlant karaté et techniques Mishima. Cette figurine met en avant son rôle charnière dans la série, entre héritage familial et identité propre sur arcade Namco.
Fun fact : Jin a été conçu pour remplacer Kazuya après sa disparition, tout en conservant des similitudes visuelles et techniques pour ne pas déstabiliser les joueurs.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Jin Kazama aparece en Tekken 3 tras la muerte de Kazuya Mishima, ocupando su lugar como nuevo personaje central. Hijo de Kazuya y Jun, es entrenado por Heihachi y adopta un estilo que mezcla karate y técnicas Mishima. Esta figura destaca su papel clave en la serie, entre herencia familiar e identidad propia en arcade Namco.
Dato curioso: Jin fue creado para sustituir a Kazuya tras su desaparición, conservando parecidos visuales y técnicos para no desorientar a los jugadores.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Jin Kazama appare in Tekken 3 dopo la morte di Kazuya Mishima, prendendo il suo posto come nuovo personaggio centrale. Figlio di Kazuya e Jun, viene addestrato da Heihachi e adotta uno stile che unisce karate e tecniche Mishima. Questa statuetta evidenzia il suo ruolo chiave nella serie, tra eredità familiare e identità propria su arcade Namco.
Curiosità: Jin fu creato per sostituire Kazuya dopo la sua scomparsa, mantenendo somiglianze visive e tecniche per non spiazzare i giocatori.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Jin Kazama erscheint in Tekken 3 nach dem Tod von Kazuya Mishima und nimmt dessen Platz als neue zentrale Figur ein. Als Sohn von Kazuya und Jun wird er von Heihachi ausgebildet und verbindet Karate mit Mishima-Techniken. Diese Figur betont seine Schlüsselrolle in der Reihe, zwischen Familienerbe und eigener Identität auf Namco-Arcade-Hardware.
Interessante Tatsache: Jin wurde geschaffen, um Kazuya nach seinem Verschwinden zu ersetzen, behielt aber optische und technische Ähnlichkeiten, damit Spieler nicht den Anschluss verloren.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Jin Kazama surge em Tekken 3 depois da morte de Kazuya Mishima, assumindo o seu lugar como novo personagem central. Filho de Kazuya e Jun, é treinado por Heihachi e adota um estilo que mistura karaté e técnicas Mishima. Esta figura destaca o seu papel decisivo na série, entre herança familiar e identidade própria no arcade Namco.
Curiosidade: Jin foi criado para substituir Kazuya após o seu desaparecimento, mantendo semelhanças visuais e técnicas para não desorientar os jogadores.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
