<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>The GD-ROM kit was marketed as an upgrade to the Naomi, just like the Naomi 2, allowing the use of a different medium than the original cartridge. This system was named Naomi GD-ROM. Although the GD-ROM format is shared with the Dreamcast, the data structure in the high-density area of Naomi discs has absolutely nothing to do with that of the Dreamcast.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Le Kit GD-ROM a été commercialisé en tant que mise à niveau de la Naomi, tout comme le Naomi 2, permettant l'utilisation d'un autre média que la cartouche d'origine. Ce système portera l'appellation Naomi GD-ROM. Bien que le support GD-ROM soit commun avec la Dreamcast, la structure des données présente dans la zone de haute densité des disques Naomi n'a absolument rien à voir avec celle de la Dreamcast.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Das GD-ROM-Kit wurde als Upgrade für das Naomi-System vermarktet, ebenso wie das Naomi 2, und ermöglichte die Verwendung eines anderen Mediums als der ursprünglichen Cartridge. Dieses System wurde Naomi GD-ROM genannt. Obwohl das GD-ROM-Format mit der Dreamcast gemeinsam ist, unterscheidet sich die Datenstruktur im hochdichten Bereich der Naomi-Discs vollständig von der der Dreamcast.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>El Kit GD-ROM fue comercializado como una mejora de la Naomi, al igual que la Naomi 2, permitiendo el uso de otro medio distinto al cartucho original. Este sistema recibió el nombre de Naomi GD-ROM. Aunque el soporte GD-ROM es común con la Dreamcast, la estructura de los datos en la zona de alta densidad de los discos Naomi no tiene absolutamente nada que ver con la de la Dreamcast.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Il Kit GD-ROM è stato commercializzato come aggiornamento del Naomi, così come il Naomi 2, permettendo l'utilizzo di un altro supporto rispetto alla cartuccia originale. Questo sistema prese il nome di Naomi GD-ROM. Sebbene il supporto GD-ROM sia comune con il Dreamcast, la struttura dei dati presente nell'area ad alta densità dei dischi Naomi è completamente diversa da quella del Dreamcast.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>GD-ROMキットは、元のカートリッジとは異なるメディアを使用可能にするNaomiおよびNaomi 2のアップグレードとして販売されました。このシステムは「Naomi GD-ROM」と呼ばれました。GD-ROMメディアはDreamcastと共通ですが、Naomiディスクの高密度領域にあるデータ構造はDreamcastとはまったく異なります。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>De GD-ROM-kit werd op de markt gebracht als een upgrade van de Naomi, net als de Naomi 2, waarmee een ander medium dan de originele cartridge kon worden gebruikt. Dit systeem kreeg de naam Naomi GD-ROM. Hoewel het GD-ROM-formaat gedeeld wordt met de Dreamcast, is de datastructuur in het hogedichtheidsgebied van de Naomi-schijven volledig anders dan die van de Dreamcast.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>Zestaw GD-ROM został wprowadzony na rynek jako ulepszenie systemu Naomi, podobnie jak Naomi 2, umożliwiając korzystanie z innego nośnika niż oryginalny kartridż. System ten nazwano Naomi GD-ROM. Chociaż nośnik GD-ROM jest wspólny z konsolą Dreamcast, struktura danych w obszarze o dużej gęstości płyt Naomi jest całkowicie inna niż w przypadku Dreamcasta.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>O Kit GD-ROM foi comercializado como uma atualização do Naomi, tal como o Naomi 2, permitindo o uso de outro meio além do cartucho original. Este sistema foi denominado Naomi GD-ROM. Embora o suporte GD-ROM seja comum com a Dreamcast, a estrutura de dados presente na área de alta densidade dos discos Naomi não tem absolutamente nada a ver com a da Dreamcast.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>Комплект GD-ROM продавался как обновление для Naomi, так же как и Naomi 2, позволяя использовать другой носитель, кроме оригинального картриджа. Эта система получила название Naomi GD-ROM. Несмотря на то, что формат GD-ROM используется и в Dreamcast, структура данных в области высокой плотности дисков Naomi полностью отличается от структуры Dreamcast.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
