<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>Basketball video games offer rich and varied experiences, ranging from ultra-realistic simulations like "NBA 2K" or "NBA Live" to more arcade-style games like "NBA Jam". The "NBA Playgrounds" licence is another interesting variant. Constantly pushing the boundaries of realism, immersive game modes and official licensing, these games continue to captivate fans around the world. Boomshakalaka!</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Les jeux vidéo de basket-ball offrent des expériences riches et variées, allant des simulations ultra-réalistes comme "NBA 2K" ou "NBA Live"  aux jeux plutôt arcade comme "NBA Jam". La licence "NBA Playgrounds" est une variante aussi intéressante. Repoussant constamment les limites du réalisme, des modes de jeu immersifs et des licences officielles, ces jeux continuent de captiver les fans à travers le monde. Boomshakalaka !</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Los videojuegos de baloncesto ofrecen experiencias ricas y variadas, desde simulaciones ultrarrealistas como "NBA 2K" o "NBA Live" hasta juegos más arcade como "NBA Jam". La licencia "NBA Playgrounds" también es una variante interesante. Al ampliar constantemente los límites del realismo, los modos inmersivos y las licencias oficiales, estos juegos siguen cautivando a aficionados de todo el mundo. Boomshakalaka!</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>I videogiochi di basket offrono esperienze ricche e varie, dalle simulazioni ultra-realistiche come "NBA 2K" o "NBA Live" ai giochi più arcade come "NBA Jam". Anche la licenza "NBA Playgrounds" è una variante interessante. Spingendo costantemente i limiti del realismo, delle modalità immersive e delle licenze ufficiali, questi giochi continuano ad appassionare i fan di tutto il mondo. Boomshakalaka!</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Basketball-Videospiele bieten reichhaltige und abwechslungsreiche Erlebnisse, von ultrarealistischen Simulationen wie "NBA 2K" oder "NBA Live" bis zu arcade-orientierten Spielen wie "NBA Jam". Die Lizenz "NBA Playgrounds" ist ebenfalls eine interessante Variante. Mit immer realistischeren Darstellungen, immersiven Spielmodi und offiziellen Lizenzen begeistern diese Spiele weiterhin Fans auf der ganzen Welt. Boomshakalaka!</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Os videojogos de basquetebol oferecem experiências ricas e variadas, desde simulações ultrarrealistas como "NBA 2K" ou "NBA Live" até jogos mais arcade como "NBA Jam". A licença "NBA Playgrounds" também é uma variante interessante. Ao levar constantemente mais longe o realismo, os modos imersivos e as licenças oficiais, estes jogos continuam a cativar fãs em todo o mundo. Boomshakalaka!</text>
</text>


<!-- FIGURINE -->

<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;NBA 2K18 (PS4, 2017)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>Damian Lillard is an explosive point guard known for his deep shooting range and ability to make decisive shots, embodying a player capable of changing a game through composure and efficiency in key moments. 
Fun fact: Damian Lillard is nicknamed “Dame Time” for his ability to score in the final seconds, a reputation built on several iconic NBA game-winners.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Damian Lillard est un meneur explosif reconnu pour sa précision longue distance et sa capacité à prendre des tirs décisifs, incarnant un joueur capable de faire basculer un match à lui seul grâce à son sang-froid et son efficacité dans les moments clés, symbole d’un style moderne basé sur le tir extérieur et la prise de responsabilité.
Fun fact : Damian Lillard est surnommé “Dame Time” pour sa capacité à marquer dans les dernières secondes, une réputation construite sur plusieurs tirs décisifs devenus emblématiques.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Damian Lillard es un base explosivo conocido por su precisión desde larga distancia y su capacidad para anotar tiros decisivos, capaz de cambiar un partido con sangre fría en los momentos clave.
Dato curioso: Damian Lillard es apodado “Dame Time” por su habilidad para anotar en los últimos segundos.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Damian Lillard è un playmaker esplosivo, noto per il tiro da lunga distanza e la capacità di segnare canestri decisivi, cambiando le partite con freddezza nei momenti chiave.
Curiosità: Damian Lillard è soprannominato “Dame Time” per la sua abilità nel segnare negli ultimi secondi.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Damian Lillard ist ein explosiver Point Guard, bekannt für seine Distanzwürfe und entscheidenden Treffer, mit denen er Spiele in Schlüsselmomenten verändern kann.
Interessante Tatsache: Damian Lillard trägt den Spitznamen “Dame Time”, weil er in den letzten Sekunden oft entscheidend punktet.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Damian Lillard é um armador explosivo, conhecido pelos arremessos de longa distância e pela capacidade de decidir jogos com frieza nos momentos finais.
Curiosidade: Damian Lillard é apelidado de “Dame Time” pela habilidade de marcar nos últimos segundos.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
