<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>The Nintendo DS (ニンテンドーDS), DS for Dual or Double Screen, is the best-selling handheld console of all time. It is equipped with new features such as two screens, one of which is touch-sensitive, a microphone, two cartridge ports (one for DS games, another for GBA games and accessories), two surround sound speakers, and built-in Wi-Fi.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>La Nintendo DS (ニンテンドーDS), DS pour Dual ou Double Screen, est la console portable la plus vendue de tous les temps. Elle est équipée de fonctions inédites telles que deux écrans dont un tactile, un microphone, deux ports cartouche (un pour les jeux DS, un autre pour les jeux GBA et les accessoires), deux haut-parleurs surround, ou encore le Wi-Fi intégré.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Der Nintendo DS (ニンテンドーDS), DS für Dual oder Double Screen, ist die meistverkaufte tragbare Konsole aller Zeiten. Sie verfügt über neuartige Funktionen wie zwei Bildschirme, von denen einer ein Touchscreen ist, ein Mikrofon, zwei Cartridge-Anschlüsse (einen für DS-Spiele, einen anderen für GBA-Spiele und Zubehör), zwei Surround-Lautsprecher oder integriertes Wi-Fi.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>La Nintendo DS (ニンテンドーDS), DS por Dual o Doble Pantalla, es la consola portátil más vendida de todos los tiempos. Está equipada con nuevas funciones, como dos pantallas, una de ellas táctil, un micrófono, dos puertos para cartuchos (uno para juegos de DS y otro para juegos y accesorios de GBA), dos altavoces de sonido envolvente y Wi-Fi integrado.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Il Nintendo DS (ニンテンドーDS), DS per Dual o Double Screen, è la console portatile più venduta di tutti i tempi. È dotata di nuove funzionalità come due schermi, uno dei quali sensibile al tocco, un microfono, due porte per cartucce (una per i giochi DS, l'altra per i giochi e gli accessori GBA), due altoparlanti surround e Wi-Fi integrato.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>ニンテンドーDS（DSはDualまたはDouble Screenの略）は、史上最も売れた携帯型ゲーム機です。2画面（うち1画面はタッチセンサー）、マイク、2つのカートリッジポート（DSゲーム用、GBAゲームおよびアクセサリー用）、2つのサラウンドスピーカー、内蔵Wi-Fiなどの新機能を備えている。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>De Nintendo DS (ニンテンドーDS), DS voor Dual of Double Screen, is de best verkochte draagbare console aller tijden. Hij is uitgerust met nieuwe functies zoals twee schermen, waarvan één aanraakgevoelig, een microfoon, twee cartridge-poorten (één voor DS-spellen, één voor GBA-spellen en accessoires), twee surround sound speakers en ingebouwde Wi-Fi.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>Nintendo DS (ニンテンドーDS), DS dla Dual lub Double Screen, jest najlepiej sprzedającą się konsolą ręczną wszech czasów. Jest wyposażona w nowe funkcje, takie jak dwa ekrany, z których jeden jest wrażliwy na dotyk, mikrofon, dwa porty kartridży (jeden dla gier DS, drugi dla gier i akcesoriów GBA), dwa głośniki dźwięku przestrzennego i wbudowane Wi-Fi.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>A Nintendo DS (ニンテンドーDS), DS para ecrã duplo ou duplo, é a consola portátil mais vendida de todos os tempos. Está equipada com novas características tais como dois ecrãs, um dos quais sensível ao toque, um microfone, duas portas de cartucho (uma para jogos DS, outra para jogos GBA e acessórios), dois altifalantes de som surround, e Wi-Fi incorporado.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>Nintendo DS (ニンテンドーDS), DS означает "двойной или двухэкранный", является самой продаваемой портативной консолью всех времен. Она оснащена такими новыми функциями, как два экрана, один из которых сенсорный, микрофон, два порта для картриджей (один для игр DS, другой для игр и аксессуаров GBA), два динамика объемного звучания и встроенный Wi-Fi.</text>
</text>


<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Chrono Trigger (2008)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>Cult RPG adapted for Nintendo DS, Chrono Trigger blends time travel, dynamic battles and fluid storytelling in an adventure built around several connected eras. The game follows Crono and his companions against a threat beyond their own time, with choices that influence certain events and multiple endings to discover.
Fun fact: The DS version adds a revised translation, bonus dungeons and an interface adapted for the dual screen.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>RPG culte adapté sur Nintendo DS, Chrono Trigger mêle voyage temporel, combats dynamiques et narration fluide dans une aventure pensée autour de plusieurs époques liées entre elles. Le jeu suit Crono et ses compagnons face à une menace qui dépasse leur époque, avec des choix influençant certains événements et plusieurs fins à découvrir.
Fun fact : La version DS ajoute une traduction révisée, des donjons bonus et une interface adaptée au double écran.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>RPG de culto adaptado para Nintendo DS, Chrono Trigger combina viajes en el tiempo, combates dinámicos y una narración fluida en una aventura construida en torno a varias épocas conectadas. El juego sigue a Crono y sus compañeros frente a una amenaza que supera su tiempo, con decisiones que influyen en algunos eventos y varios finales por descubrir.
Dato curioso: La versión DS añade una traducción revisada, mazmorras extra y una interfaz adaptada a la doble pantalla.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>RPG cult adattato per Nintendo DS, Chrono Trigger unisce viaggi nel tempo, combattimenti dinamici e narrazione fluida in un’avventura costruita attorno a epoche collegate. Il gioco segue Crono e i suoi compagni contro una minaccia oltre il loro tempo, con scelte che influenzano alcuni eventi e finali multipli da scoprire.
Curiosità: La versione DS aggiunge una traduzione rivista, dungeon bonus e un’interfaccia adattata al doppio schermo.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Kult-RPG für Nintendo DS, Chrono Trigger verbindet Zeitreisen, dynamische Kämpfe und flüssiges Erzählen in einem Abenteuer über mehrere verknüpfte Epochen. Das Spiel folgt Crono und seinen Gefährten im Kampf gegen eine Bedrohung jenseits ihrer Zeit, mit Entscheidungen, die Ereignisse beeinflussen, und mehreren Enden zum Entdecken.
Interessante Tatsache: Die DS-Version bietet eine überarbeitete Übersetzung, Bonus-Dungeons und eine an den Doppelbildschirm angepasste Oberfläche.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>RPG cult adaptado para Nintendo DS, Chrono Trigger mistura viagem no tempo, combates dinâmicos e narrativa fluida numa aventura criada em torno de várias épocas ligadas. O jogo acompanha Crono e seus companheiros contra uma ameaça além de seu tempo, com escolhas que influenciam certos eventos e vários finais para descobrir.
Curiosidade: A versão DS adiciona tradução revista, masmorras bônus e uma interface adaptada à tela dupla.</text>
</text>
</view>
</theme>
