<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>A miniature-sized, semi-portable arcade terminal (vaguely resembling a Japanese Neo Geo MVS) that includes 40 built-in SNK titles and was launched on 24 July 2018 in Japan to celebrate SNK's 40th anniversary.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Une borne d'arcade semi-portable de taille miniature (ressemblant vaguement à une Neo Geo MVS japonaise) qui comprend 40 titres SNK intégrés et qui a été lancée le 24 juillet 2018 au Japon pour célébrer le 40ème anniversaire de SNK.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Ein halbwegs tragbarer Arcade-Automat in Miniaturgröße (der entfernt an ein japanisches Neo Geo MVS erinnert) mit 40 integrierten SNK-Titeln, der am 24. Juli 2018 in Japan zur Feier des 40-jährigen Jubiläums von SNK auf den Markt gebracht wurde.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Un terminal arcade semiportátil de tamaño miniatura (vagamente parecido a una Neo Geo MVS japonesa) que incluye 40 títulos de SNK incorporados y que se lanzó el 24 de julio de 2018 en Japón para celebrar el 40 aniversario de SNK.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Un terminale arcade semi-portatile di dimensioni miniaturizzate (vagamente somigliante a un Neo Geo MVS giapponese) che include 40 titoli SNK integrati ed è stato lanciato il 24 luglio 2018 in Giappone per celebrare il 40° anniversario di SNK.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>SNKの40タイトルを内蔵したミニチュアサイズの半携帯型アーケード端末（どことなく日本のネオジオMVSに似ている）で、SNKの40周年を記念して2018年7月24日に日本国内で発売された。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>Een miniatuurformaat, semi-draagbare arcade-terminal (die vaag lijkt op een Japanse Neo Geo MVS) die 40 ingebouwde SNK-titels bevat en op 24 juli 2018 in Japan werd gelanceerd om de 40e verjaardag van SNK te vieren.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>Miniaturowy rozmiar, półprzenośny terminal arcade (mgliście przypominający japoński Neo Geo MVS), który zawiera 40 wbudowanych tytułów SNK i został wprowadzony na rynek 24 lipca 2018 roku w Japonii, aby uczcić 40. rocznicę SNK.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Um terminal de arcada em miniatura, semi-portátil (vagamente parecido com um Neo Geo MVS japonês) que inclui 40 títulos SNK incorporados e foi lançado a 24 de Julho de 2018 no Japão para celebrar o 40º aniversário da SNK.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>Миниатюрный, полупортативный аркадный терминал (смутно напоминающий японскую Neo Geo MVS), включающий 40 встроенных игр SNK и запущенный 24 июля 2018 года в Японии в честь 40-летия SNK.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
