 <!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>The N-Gage is a portable video games console as well as a mobile phone. It incorporates an MP3 player, a radio and can be used as a web browser. This machine was not as successful as expected. It was one of the first multifunction mobiles, but didn't have enough games to interest consumers enough.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>La N-Gage est une console de jeux vidéo portable en plus d'un téléphone portable. Elle intègre un lecteur MP3, une radio et elle peut être utilisée comme navigateur web voir GPS avec certaines applications. Cette machine n'a pas eu le succès escompté. Elle fut l'un des premiers mobiles multifonctions, mais n'a pas eu assez de jeux pour intéresser suffisamment les consommateurs.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>La N-Gage es una videoconsola portátil además de un teléfono móvil. Incorpora un reproductor MP3, una radio y puede utilizarse como navegador web. Este aparato no tuvo el éxito esperado. Fue uno de los primeros móviles multifunción, pero no tenía suficientes juegos para interesar lo suficiente a los consumidores. </text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>N-Gage è una console portatile per videogiochi e anche un telefono cellulare. Integra un lettore MP3, una radio e può essere usata come browser web. Questa macchina non ebbe il successo sperato. Fu uno dei primi dispositivi mobili multifunzione, ma non disponeva di abbastanza giochi per interessare davvero i consumatori.</text>
</text>
<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Das N-Gage ist eine tragbare Videospielkonsole und zugleich ein Mobiltelefon. Es besitzt einen MP3-Player, ein Radio und kann als Webbrowser genutzt werden. Das Gerät hatte nicht den erwarteten Erfolg. Es gehörte zu den ersten multifunktionalen Mobilgeräten, bot aber nicht genug Spiele, um die Verbraucher ausreichend zu überzeugen.</text>
</text>
<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>O N-Gage é um console portátil de videogames e também um telefone celular. Ele inclui um leitor de MP3, rádio e pode ser usado como navegador web. O aparelho não teve o sucesso esperado. Foi um dos primeiros celulares multifuncionais, mas não teve jogos suficientes para atrair os consumidores.</text>
</text>
<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Tomb Raider (2003)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>
<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>Lara Croft appears here as an adventurous archaeologist, exploring tombs, ruins and isolated places in search of ancient artifacts. On N-Gage, Tomb Raider brings the cult 3D adventure to a very constrained portable format, with camera work, precise jumps and puzzles adapted to the machine’s vertical screen.
Fun fact: The N-Gage version of Tomb Raider uses a view and engine specially adapted for the console, different from the PlayStation and PC versions, to fit the hardware limits.</text>
</text>
<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Lara Croft apparaît ici dans son rôle d’archéologue aventurière, explorant tombeaux, ruines et lieux isolés à la recherche d’artefacts anciens. Sur N-Gage, Tomb Raider reprend l’aventure culte en 3D dans un format portable très contraint, avec une caméra, des sauts précis et des énigmes adaptées à l’écran vertical de la machine.
Fun fact : La version N-Gage de Tomb Raider utilise une vue et un moteur adaptés spécialement pour la console, différents des versions PlayStation et PC.</text>
</text>
<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Lara Croft aparece aquí en su papel de arqueóloga aventurera, explorando tumbas, ruinas y lugares aislados en busca de artefactos antiguos. En N-Gage, Tomb Raider lleva la aventura 3D de culto a un formato portátil muy limitado, con cámara, saltos precisos y puzles adaptados a la pantalla vertical de la máquina.
Dato curioso: La versión de Tomb Raider para N-Gage usa una vista y un motor adaptados especialmente para la consola, distintos de las versiones de PlayStation y PC, para ajustarse a sus límites técnicos.</text>
</text>
<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Lara Croft appare qui nel suo ruolo di archeologa avventuriera, esplorando tombe, rovine e luoghi isolati alla ricerca di antichi artefatti. Su N-Gage, Tomb Raider porta l’avventura 3D cult in un formato portatile molto limitato, con telecamera, salti precisi ed enigmi adattati allo schermo verticale della macchina.
Curiosità: La versione N-Gage di Tomb Raider usa una visuale e un motore adattati appositamente per la console, diversi dalle versioni PlayStation e PC, per rispettare i limiti tecnici del supporto.</text>
</text>
<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Lara Croft erscheint hier in ihrer Rolle als abenteuerlustige Archäologin, die Gräber, Ruinen und abgelegene Orte auf der Suche nach alten Artefakten erkundet. Auf dem N-Gage bringt Tomb Raider das bekannte 3D-Abenteuer in ein stark begrenztes tragbares Format, mit Kamera, präzisen Sprüngen und Rätseln für den vertikalen Bildschirm.
Interessante Tatsache: Die N-Gage-Version von Tomb Raider nutzt eine speziell an die Konsole angepasste Ansicht und Engine, anders als die PlayStation- und PC-Versionen, um den technischen Grenzen zu entsprechen.</text>
</text>
<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Lara Croft aparece aqui em seu papel de arqueóloga aventureira, explorando tumbas, ruínas e locais isolados em busca de artefatos antigos. No N-Gage, Tomb Raider leva a aventura 3D clássica para um formato portátil muito limitado, com câmera, saltos precisos e enigmas adaptados à tela vertical do aparelho.
Curiosidade: A versão de Tomb Raider para N-Gage usa uma visão e um motor adaptados especialmente para o console, diferentes das versões de PlayStation e PC, para respeitar os limites técnicos do suporte.</text>
</text>
</view>
</theme>
