<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>The Neo Geo Pocket Color is a 16-bit colour handheld game console. It is a fully backwards compatible successor to the monochrome Neo Geo Pocket console. Despite being a financial failure, the Neo Geo Pocket Color is considered an influential system and many games released on this system are very popular with the public.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>La Neo Geo Pocket Color est une console de jeu portable couleur 16 bits. Entièrement rétrocompatible elle succède à la console de poche monochrome Neo Geo Pocket. Malgré un échec financier, la Neo Geo Pocket Color est considérée comme un système influent et de nombreux jeux sortis sur ce système sont très appréciés du public.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Die Neo Geo Pocket Color ist eine tragbare 16-Bit-Farb-Spielkonsole. Sie ist vollständig rückwärtskompatibel und der Nachfolger der einfarbigen Handheld-Konsole Neo Geo Pocket. Trotz eines finanziellen Misserfolgs gilt die Neo Geo Pocket Color als einflussreiches System und viele der für dieses System veröffentlichten Spiele sind bei der Öffentlichkeit sehr beliebt.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>La Neo Geo Pocket Color es una videoconsola portátil en color de 16 bits. Es una sucesora totalmente retrocompatible de la consola monocroma Neo Geo Pocket. A pesar de ser un fracaso financiero, la Neo Geo Pocket Color se considera un sistema influyente y muchos juegos lanzados en este sistema son muy populares entre el público.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Il Neo Geo Pocket Color è una console di gioco portatile a colori a 16 bit. È il successore completamente retrocompatibile della console monocromatica Neo Geo Pocket. Nonostante il fallimento finanziario, il Neo Geo Pocket Color è considerato un sistema influente e molti giochi rilasciati su questo sistema sono molto popolari tra il pubblico.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>Neo Geo Pocket Colorは、16ビットカラーの携帯ゲーム機です。モノクロのNeo Geo Pocketコンソールの完全な後方互換性を持つ後継機である。経済的には失敗したものの、ネオジオポケットカラーは影響力のあるシステムだと考えられており、このシステムで発売された多くのゲームは一般に非常に人気がある。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>De Neo Geo Pocket Color is een 16-bit kleuren draagbare spelconsole. Het is een volledig achterwaarts compatibele opvolger van de monochrome Neo Geo Pocket console. Ondanks het feit dat de Neo Geo Pocket Color een financiële mislukking was, wordt het beschouwd als een invloedrijk systeem en veel spellen die op dit systeem zijn uitgebracht zijn zeer populair bij het publiek.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>Neo Geo Pocket Color to 16-bitowa kolorowa przenośna konsola do gier. Jest to w pełni kompatybilny wstecz następca monochromatycznej konsoli Neo Geo Pocket. Pomimo porażki finansowej, Neo Geo Pocket Color jest uważany za wpływowy system, a wiele gier wydanych na ten system jest bardzo popularnych wśród publiczności.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>O Neo Geo Pocket Color é uma consola de jogos portátil de 16 bits a cores. É um sucessor totalmente compatível com a consola monocromática Neo Geo Pocket. Apesar de ser um fracasso financeiro, o Neo Geo Pocket Color é considerado um sistema influente e muitos jogos lançados neste sistema são muito populares entre o público.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>Neo Geo Pocket Color - это 16-битная цветная портативная игровая консоль. Она является полностью обратно совместимым преемником монохромной консоли Neo Geo Pocket. Несмотря на финансовую неудачу, Neo Geo Pocket Color считается влиятельной системой, а многие игры, выпущенные на этой системе, пользуются большой популярностью у публики.</text>
</text>


<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Metal Slug: 2nd Mission (2000)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>Fiolina Germi, known as Fio, is a calm and precise soldier from the Metal Slug series. In Metal Slug: 2nd Mission, she joins the portable action with compact missions, varied routes, vehicles and frantic shooting, while keeping the military humour and energetic pace of the arcade games.
Fun fact: Fio became a playable character in Metal Slug 2, bringing a lighter but highly trained soldier profile to the Peregrine Falcons team.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Fiolina Germi, surnommée Fio, est une soldate calme et précise de la série Metal Slug. Dans Metal Slug: 2nd Mission, elle rejoint l’action portable avec missions compactes, chemins variés, véhicules et tirs nerveux, tout en gardant l’humour militaire et le rythme énergique des épisodes arcade.
Fun fact : Fio devient jouable dans Metal Slug 2, apportant au groupe des Peregrine Falcons un profil de soldate plus léger mais très entraîné.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Fiolina Germi, llamada Fio, es una soldado tranquila y precisa de la serie Metal Slug. En Metal Slug: 2nd Mission, participa en la acción portátil con misiones compactas, rutas variadas, vehículos y disparos intensos, manteniendo el humor militar y el ritmo de los juegos arcade.
Dato curioso: Fio se convirtió en personaje jugable en Metal Slug 2, aportando al equipo Peregrine Falcons un perfil de soldado más ligero pero muy entrenado.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Fiolina Germi, detta Fio, è una soldatessa calma e precisa della serie Metal Slug. In Metal Slug: 2nd Mission entra nell’azione portatile con missioni compatte, percorsi vari, veicoli e sparatorie frenetiche, mantenendo l’umorismo militare e il ritmo degli episodi arcade.
Curiosità: Fio divenne giocabile in Metal Slug 2, portando nei Peregrine Falcons un profilo di soldatessa più leggero ma molto addestrato.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Fiolina Germi, genannt Fio, ist eine ruhige und präzise Soldatin aus der Metal Slug-Reihe. In Metal Slug: 2nd Mission prägt sie die tragbare Action mit kompakten Missionen, verschiedenen Wegen, Fahrzeugen und hektischen Schusswechseln, samt militärischem Humor und Arcade-Tempo.
Interessante Tatsache: Fio wurde in Metal Slug 2 spielbar und brachte den Peregrine Falcons ein leichteres, aber sehr gut trainiertes Soldatenprofil.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Fiolina Germi, conhecida como Fio, é uma soldado calma e precisa da série Metal Slug. Em Metal Slug: 2nd Mission, participa na ação portátil com missões compactas, rotas variadas, veículos e tiroteios intensos, mantendo o humor militar e o ritmo dos jogos arcade.
Curiosidade: Fio tornou-se personagem jogável em Metal Slug 2, trazendo aos Peregrine Falcons um perfil de soldado mais leve mas muito treinado.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
