<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>

	<view name="system">
		<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
			<text>Oric foi o nome usado pela Tangerine Computer Systems para uma série de computadores domésticos, incluindo o original Oric-1, seu sucessor, o Oric Atmos e os modelos Oric Stratos / IQ164 e Oric Telestrat.</text>
		</text>
		
				<text name="system_description" extra="true">
			<text>Oric was the name used by Tangerine Computer Systems for a series of home computers, including the original Oric-1, its successor the Oric Atmos and the later Oric Stratos/IQ164 and Oric Telestrat models.</text>
		</text>
		
				<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
			<text>Oric fue el nombre utilizado por Tangerine Computer Systems para una serie de computadoras domésticas, incluidas la original Oric-1, su sucesora, Oric Atmos y la posterior Oric Stratos / IQ164 y Oric Telestrat.</text>
		</text>
		
				<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
			<text>Oric était le nom utilisé par Tangerine Computer Systems pour désigner une série d'ordinateurs personnels, notamment le premier Oric-1, son successeur, l'Oric Atmos, et les modèles plus récents Oric Stratos / IQ164 et Oric Telestrat.</text>
		</text>
		
				
		<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
			<text>Oric era il nome usato da Tangerine Computer Systems per una serie di home computer, tra cui l'Oric-1 originale, il suo successore Oric Atmos e i modelli successivi Oric Stratos / IQ164 e Oric Telestrat.</text>
		</text>
		
		<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
			<text>Oric war der Name, den Tangerine Computer Systems für eine Reihe von Heimcomputern verwendete, darunter der ursprüngliche Oric-1, sein Nachfolger Oric Atmos sowie die späteren Modelle Oric Stratos / IQ164 und Oric Telestrat.</text>
		</text>

		<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
			<text>&#160;&#160;Dracula (1983)&#160;&#160;</text>
		</text>
		
		<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
			<text>Dracula appears here as a classic adventure-game figure on home computers, inspired by Bram Stoker's gothic novel. On Oric Atmos, the game relies on exploration and puzzle solving through descriptive text, with the player progressing by typing commands on the keyboard. Its atmosphere depends mostly on imagination, supported by simple but evocative graphics for the period.
Fun fact: Dracula on Oric Atmos belongs to the many unofficial 1980s takes on the character, often produced without a direct license from the original novel.</text>
		</text>
		
		<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
			<text>Dracula apparaît ici comme une figure classique du jeu d’aventure sur micro-ordinateur, inspirée du roman gothique de Bram Stoker. Le jeu repose sur l’exploration et la résolution d’énigmes à partir de textes descriptifs, où le joueur progresse en entrant des commandes au clavier. L’ambiance repose sur l’imagination, avec des graphismes simples mais évocateurs pour l’époque.
Fun fact : Le jeu Dracula sur Oric Atmos fait partie des nombreuses adaptations informelles du personnage dans les années 80, souvent sans licence officielle du roman original.</text>
		</text>
		
		<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
			<text>Drácula aparece aquí como una figura clásica del juego de aventura en microordenador, inspirada en la novela gótica de Bram Stoker. El juego se basa en la exploración y la resolución de enigmas mediante textos descriptivos, con el jugador avanzando al escribir comandos con el teclado. La atmósfera depende sobre todo de la imaginación, con gráficos simples pero evocadores para la época.
Dato curioso: Dracula para Oric Atmos forma parte de muchas adaptaciones informales del personaje en los años 80, a menudo sin licencia oficial de la novela original.</text>
		</text>
		
		<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
			<text>Dracula appare qui come una figura classica dell’avventura su microcomputer, ispirata al romanzo gotico di Bram Stoker. Il gioco si basa sull’esplorazione e sulla risoluzione di enigmi attraverso testi descrittivi, con il giocatore che avanza digitando comandi sulla tastiera. L’atmosfera dipende soprattutto dall’immaginazione, con grafica semplice ma evocativa per l’epoca.
Curiosità: Dracula per Oric Atmos fa parte dei molti adattamenti informali del personaggio negli anni 80, spesso senza licenza ufficiale del romanzo originale.</text>
		</text>
		
		<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
			<text>Dracula erscheint hier als klassische Figur eines Adventure-Spiels auf dem Heimcomputer, inspiriert von Bram Stokers Gothic-Roman. Das Spiel auf Erkundung und Rätseln über beschreibende Texte, während der Spieler per Tastatur Befehle eingibt. Die Atmosphäre entsteht vor allem im Kopf, mit einfachen, aber für die Zeit stimmungsvollen Grafiken.
Interessante Tatsache: Dracula für Oric Atmos gehört zu den vielen informellen Umsetzungen der Figur in den 80er Jahren, oft ohne offizielle Lizenz des ursprünglichen Romans.</text>
		</text>
		
		<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
			<text>Drácula aparece aqui como uma figura clássica do jogo de aventura em microcomputador, inspirada no romance gótico de Bram Stoker. O jogo se baseia na exploração e na resolução de enigmas por meio de textos descritivos, com o jogador avançando ao digitar comandos no teclado. A atmosfera depende sobretudo da imaginação, com gráficos simples mas evocativos para a época.
Curiosidade: Dracula para Oric Atmos faz parte das muitas adaptações informais do personagem nos anos 80, frequentemente sem licença oficial do romance original.</text>
		</text>

	</view>
</theme>
