<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>PC-98 is an acronym for the NEC PC-9801 computer series, a personal computer model of Japanese origin. It was manufactured in 1982, the first in the PC-98 series of 16- and 32-bit personal computers. The graphics resolution was up to 640x400 pixels with an 8-colour palette display.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>PC-98 est un acronyme pour la série d'ordinateurs NEC PC-9801, un modèle d'ordinateur personnel d'origine japonaise. Il a été fabriqué en 1982, le premier de la série des ordinateurs personnels PC-98 de 16 et 32 bits. La résolution graphique pouvait monter jusqu'à 640x 400 pixels avec un affichage comportant une palette de 8 couleurs.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>PC-98 ist ein Akronym für die Computerserie NEC PC-9801, ein Personalcomputermodell japanischer Herkunft. Er wurde 1982 als erster der PC-98-Serie von 16- und 32-Bit-Personalcomputern hergestellt. Die Grafikauflösung betrug bis zu 640x400 Pixel bei einer Anzeige mit einer Palette von 8 Farben.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>PC-98 es el acrónimo de la serie de ordenadores NEC PC-9801, un modelo de ordenador personal de origen japonés. Se fabricó en 1982 y fue el primero de la serie PC-98 de ordenadores personales de 16 y 32 bits. La resolución gráfica era de hasta 640x400 píxeles con una pantalla de paleta de 8 colores.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>PC-98 è l'acronimo della serie di computer NEC PC-9801, un modello di personal computer di origine giapponese. Prodotto nel 1982, è stato il primo della serie PC-98 di personal computer a 16 e 32 bit. La risoluzione grafica era di 640x400 pixel con un display a 8 colori.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>PC-98は、日本発のパーソナルコンピュータ「NEC PC-9801」シリーズの頭文字をとったものである。16ビットおよび32ビットのパーソナルコンピュータであるPC-98シリーズの第1弾として、1982年に製造された。グラフィック解像度は最大640×400ピクセル、8色パレット表示であった。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>PC-98 is een acroniem voor de NEC PC-9801 computer serie, een personal computer model van Japanse oorsprong. Het werd vervaardigd in 1982, de eerste in de PC-98 serie van 16- en 32-bit personal computers. De grafische resolutie was tot 640x400 pixels met een 8-kleuren palet display.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>PC-98 to skrót od nazwy serii komputerów NEC PC-9801, modelu komputera osobistego pochodzenia japońskiego. Został wyprodukowany w 1982 roku, był pierwszym z serii PC-98 16- i 32-bitowych komputerów osobistych. Rozdzielczość grafiki wynosiła do 640x400 pikseli z wyświetlaniem palety 8 kolorów.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>PC-98 é um acrónimo da série NEC PC-9801 de computadores, um modelo de computador pessoal de origem japonesa. Foi fabricado em 1982, o primeiro da série PC-98 de computadores pessoais de 16 e 32 bits. A resolução gráfica era de até 640x400 pixels com uma paleta de 8 cores.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>PC-98 - это аббревиатура для серии компьютеров NEC PC-9801, модели персонального компьютера японского происхождения. Он был выпущен в 1982 году, первым в серии PC-98 16- и 32-разрядных персональных компьютеров. Графическое разрешение составляло до 640x400 пикселей с отображением 8-цветной палитры.</text>
</text>


<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Touhou Rei’iden (1997)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>Reimu Hakurei investigates after the Hakurei Shrine is destroyed and crosses a portal to other worlds to face those responsible. As the first Touhou game on PC-98, it does not yet use the series' vertical shooting style: it mixes fixed-screen action, projectiles and an Arkanoid-like mechanic. This figurine highlights the saga's more experimental origin.
Fun fact: Released in 1997, the game illustrates the PC-98's longevity, still used at the time especially for doujin productions.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Reimu Hakurei enquête après la destruction du sanctuaire Hakurei et traverse un portail vers d’autres mondes pour affronter les responsables. Premier épisode de Touhou sur PC-98, le jeu ne suit pas encore le tir vertical classique de la série : il mélange action fixe, projectiles et mécanique proche d’Arkanoid. Cette figurine met en avant l’origine plus expérimentale de la saga.
Fun fact : Sorti en 1997, le jeu illustre la longévité du PC-98, encore utilisé à cette époque surtout pour des productions doujin.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Reimu Hakurei investiga tras la destrucción del santuario Hakurei y cruza un portal hacia otros mundos para enfrentarse a los responsables. Primer episodio de Touhou en PC-98, el juego aún no usa el disparo vertical clásico de la serie: mezcla acción fija, proyectiles y una mecánica cercana a Arkanoid. Esta figurilla destaca el origen más experimental de la saga.
Dato curioso: Lanzado en 1997, el juego muestra la longevidad del PC-98, aún usado entonces sobre todo para producciones doujin.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Reimu Hakurei indaga dopo la distruzione del santuario Hakurei e attraversa un portale verso altri mondi per affrontare i responsabili. Primo episodio di Touhou su PC-98, il gioco non usa ancora lo sparatutto verticale classico della serie: mescola azione fissa, proiettili e una meccanica vicina ad Arkanoid. Questa statuetta evidenzia l'origine più sperimentale della saga.
Curiosità: Uscito nel 1997, il gioco mostra la longevità del PC-98, ancora usato allora soprattutto per produzioni doujin.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Reimu Hakurei ermittelt nach der Zerstörung des Hakurei-Schreins und durchquert ein Portal in andere Welten, um die Verantwortlichen zu stellen. Als erster Touhou-Teil auf PC-98 nutzt das Spiel noch nicht den klassischen vertikalen Shooter-Stil der Reihe: Es verbindet feste Action, Projektile und eine Arkanoid-nahe Mechanik. Diese Figur betont den experimentelleren Ursprung der Saga.
Interessante Tatsache: Das 1997 erschienene Spiel zeigt die Langlebigkeit des PC-98, der damals noch vor allem für Doujin-Produktionen genutzt wurde.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Reimu Hakurei investiga após a destruição do santuário Hakurei e atravessa um portal para outros mundos para enfrentar os responsáveis. Primeiro episódio de Touhou no PC-98, o jogo ainda não usa o tiro vertical clássico da série: mistura ação em tela fixa, projéteis e uma mecânica próxima de Arkanoid. Esta figura destaca a origem mais experimental da saga.
Curiosidade: Lançado em 1997, o jogo mostra a longevidade do PC-98, ainda usado na época sobretudo para produções doujin.</text>
</text>


</view>
</theme>
