<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>This extension that increases the technical capabilities of the PC-Engine includes a CD-ROM drive but also a new BIOS and 64 kB of memory (to load data and code from the CD). The American name of the device is TurboGrafx-CD. The game library is mostly known for its excellent shoot them up.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Cette extension qui accroît les capacités techniques de la PC-Engine inclus un lecteur CD-ROM mais aussi un nouveau BIOS et 64 ko de mémoire (pour charger les données et le code à partir du CD). L'appellation américaine du périphérique est TurboGrafx-CD. La ludothèque est surtout connue pour ses excellents shoot them up.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Diese Erweiterung, die die technischen Möglichkeiten der PC-Engine erweitert, enthält neben einem CD-ROM-Laufwerk auch ein neues BIOS und 64 KB Speicher (um Daten und Code von der CD zu laden). Die amerikanische Bezeichnung für das Gerät lautet TurboGrafx-CD. Die Spielothek ist vor allem für ihre hervorragenden Shoot them up's bekannt.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Esta ampliación de las capacidades técnicas del PC-Engine incluye una unidad de CD-ROM, pero también una nueva BIOS y 64k de memoria (para cargar datos y código del CD). El nombre americano del aparato es TurboGrafx-CD. La biblioteca de juegos es más conocida por sus excelentes juegos de disparos.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Questo ampliamento delle capacità tecniche del PC-Engine comprende un lettore CD-ROM, ma anche un nuovo BIOS e 64k di memoria (per caricare dati e codice dal CD). Il nome americano del dispositivo è TurboGrafx-CD. La libreria di giochi è nota soprattutto per i suoi eccellenti sparatutto.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>PC-Engineの技術力を拡張したもので、CD-ROMドライブはもちろん、新しいBIOSや64kのメモリ（CDからデータやコードを読み込むため）などが搭載されています。この装置のアメリカでの名称はTurboGrafx-CDです。ゲームライブラリは、優れたシューティングゲームでよく知られている。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>Deze uitbreiding van de technische mogelijkheden van de PC-Engine omvat een CD-ROM drive, maar ook een nieuw BIOS en 64k geheugen (om gegevens en code van de CD te laden). De Amerikaanse naam voor het apparaat is TurboGrafx-CD. De spelbibliotheek is vooral bekend om zijn uitstekende shoot them up spellen.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>Rozszerzenie to, zwiększające możliwości techniczne PC-Engine, zawiera napęd CD-ROM, nowy BIOS oraz 64 KB pamięci (do ładowania danych i kodu z płyty CD). Amerykańska nazwa urządzenia to TurboGrafx-CD. Biblioteka gier jest najbardziej znana z doskonałych gier typu shoot them up.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Esta extensão às capacidades técnicas do PC-Engine inclui uma unidade de CD-ROM, mas também uma nova BIOS e 64k de memória (para carregar dados e código do CD). O nome americano para o dispositivo é TurboGrafx-CD. A biblioteca de jogos é mais conhecida pelos seus excelentes jogos de tiro.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>Это расширение технических возможностей PC-Engine включает в себя привод CD-ROM, а также новый BIOS и 64k памяти (для загрузки данных и кода с CD). Американское название устройства - TurboGrafx-CD. Библиотека игр наиболее известна своими превосходными играми в жанре shoot them up.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>

