<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>The PC-FX is a 32-bit console released in Japan by NEC and Hudson Soft, designed as the successor to the PC Engine family. Focused on CD-ROM games, video sequences and anime-style presentation, it favored visual novels, interactive adventures and character-driven titles rather than polygonal 3D. Its library remains closely tied to the Japanese market.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>La PC-FX est une console 32 bits sortie au Japon par NEC et Hudson Soft, pensée comme la successeure de la famille PC Engine. Axée sur le CD-ROM, les séquences vidéo et une présentation proche de l’animation japonaise, elle privilégie visual novels, aventures interactives et jeux centrés sur les personnages plutôt que la 3D polygonale. Son catalogue reste très lié au marché japonais.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>La PC-FX es una consola de 32 bits lanzada en Japón por NEC y Hudson Soft, concebida como sucesora de la familia PC Engine. Centrada en el CD-ROM, las secuencias de vídeo y una presentación cercana al anime, favorece novelas visuales, aventuras interactivas y juegos centrados en personajes antes que la 3D poligonal. Su catálogo está muy ligado al mercado japonés.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>PC-FX è una console a 32 bit pubblicata in Giappone da NEC e Hudson Soft, pensata come erede della famiglia PC Engine. Basata su CD-ROM, sequenze video e una presentazione vicina all’animazione giapponese, privilegia visual novel, avventure interattive e giochi incentrati sui personaggi più che la grafica 3D poligonale. Il suo catalogo resta legato al mercato giapponese.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Die PC-FX ist eine 32-Bit-Konsole, die in Japan von NEC und Hudson Soft veröffentlicht wurde und als Nachfolger der PC-Engine-Familie gedacht war. Mit Fokus auf CD-ROM-Spiele, Videosequenzen und animeartige Präsentation setzte sie eher auf Visual Novels, interaktive Abenteuer und charakterbetonte Titel als auf polygonale 3D-Grafik. Ihre Bibliothek blieb eng mit Japan verbunden.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>O PC-FX é um console de 32 bits lançado no Japão pela NEC e Hudson Soft, criado como sucessor da família PC Engine. Focado em CD-ROM, sequências de vídeo e apresentação próxima da animação japonesa, privilegia visual novels, aventuras interativas e jogos centrados em personagens em vez de 3D poligonal. Seu catálogo permanece muito ligado ao mercado japonês.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Sakura Wars FX (1995)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>Ichiro Ogami is sent to Tokyo to join a theater troupe that secretly hides a combat unit tasked with protecting the city. The experience relies on timed dialogue choices that affect relationships and story progression. It highlights dense storytelling, theatrical staging and strong character presence, adapted to the PC-FX. Fun fact: Sakura Wars FX focuses on the narrative concept, while the later Sega Saturn version introduced strategic battle phases absent here.</text>
<text lang="fr">Ichiro Ogami est envoyé à Tokyo pour rejoindre une troupe théâtrale qui cache en réalité une unité de combat chargée de protéger la ville. L’expérience repose sur des choix de dialogue en temps limité influençant les relations et le déroulement de l’histoire. L’ensemble met en avant une narration dense avec une mise en scène théâtrale, adaptée aux capacités du PC-FX. Fun fact : Sakura Wars FX propose une interprétation centrée sur la narration du concept original, alors que la version Sega Saturn introduira ensuite les phases de combat stratégiques absentes ici.</text>
<text lang="es">Ichiro Ogami es enviado a Tokio para unirse a una compañía teatral que en realidad oculta una unidad de combate encargada de proteger la ciudad. La experiencia se basa en elecciones de diálogo con tiempo limitado que influyen en las relaciones y la historia. Destaca una narración densa, puesta en escena teatral y fuerte presencia de personajes, adaptada al PC-FX. Dato curioso: Sakura Wars FX se centra en la narración, mientras que la versión posterior de Sega Saturn añadió combates estratégicos ausentes aquí.</text>
<text lang="it">Ichiro Ogami viene inviato a Tokyo per unirsi a una compagnia teatrale che nasconde in realtà un’unità di combattimento incaricata di proteggere la città. L’esperienza si basa su scelte di dialogo a tempo che influenzano rapporti e storia. Mette in risalto una narrazione densa, una regia teatrale e personaggi molto presenti, adattati al PC-FX. Curiosità: Sakura Wars FX privilegia la narrazione, mentre la successiva versione Sega Saturn introdusse battaglie strategiche assenti qui.</text>
<text lang="de">Ichiro Ogami wird nach Tokio geschickt, um sich einer Theatertruppe anzuschließen, hinter der sich eine Kampfeinheit zum Schutz der Stadt verbirgt. Das Erlebnis basiert auf zeitbegrenzten Dialogentscheidungen, die Beziehungen und Handlung beeinflussen. Es betont dichte Erzählung, theatralische Inszenierung und starke Figurenpräsenz, angepasst an die PC-FX. Interessante Tatsache: Sakura Wars FX konzentriert sich auf die Erzählung, während die spätere Sega-Saturn-Version strategische Kämpfe einführte, die hier fehlen.</text>
<text lang="pt">Ichiro Ogami é enviado a Tóquio para integrar uma trupe teatral que esconde uma unidade de combate encarregada de proteger a cidade. A experiência usa escolhas de diálogo com tempo limitado que influenciam relações e história. O jogo destaca narrativa densa, encenação teatral e forte presença dos personagens, adaptadas ao PC-FX. Curiosidade: Sakura Wars FX foca a narrativa, enquanto a versão posterior de Sega Saturn introduziu batalhas estratégicas ausentes aqui.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
