<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>The PDP-1 (Programmed Data Processor-1) is the first computer in the PDP series from Digital Equipment Corporation and was first produced in 1959. The PDP-1 is the original hardware for playing the first game in history on a minicomputer, Steve Russell's Spacewar.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Le PDP-1 (Programmed Data Processor-1) est le premier ordinateur de la série PDP de Digital Equipment Corporation et a été produit pour la première fois en 1959. Le PDP-1 est le matériel original pour jouer au premier jeu de l'histoire sur un mini-ordinateur, Spacewar de Steve Russell.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Der PDP-1 (Programmed Data Processor-1) ist der erste Computer der PDP-Serie der Digital Equipment Corporation und wurde 1959 zum ersten Mal hergestellt. Die PDP-1 ist die Originalhardware, mit der man das erste Spiel der Geschichte auf einem Minicomputer spielen kann, Spacewar von Steve Russell.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>El PDP-1 (Programmed Data Processor-1) es el primer ordenador de la serie PDP de Digital Equipment Corporation y se fabricó por primera vez en 1959. El PDP-1 es el hardware original para jugar al primer juego de la historia en un miniordenador, el Spacewar de Steve Russell.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Il PDP-1 (Programmed Data Processor-1) è il primo computer della serie PDP di Digital Equipment Corporation, prodotto per la prima volta nel 1959. Il PDP-1 è l'hardware originale per giocare al primo gioco della storia su minicomputer, Spacewar di Steve Russell.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>PDP-1（Programmed Data Processor-1）は、Digital Equipment CorporationのPDPシリーズの最初のコンピュータで、1959年に初めて生産されました。PDP-1は、ミニコンピュータで史上初のゲーム、スティーブ・ラッセルの「スペースウォー」をプレイするためのオリジナルハードウェアである。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>De PDP-1 (Programmed Data Processor-1) is de eerste computer in de PDP-serie van Digital Equipment Corporation en werd voor het eerst geproduceerd in 1959. De PDP-1 is de oorspronkelijke hardware voor het spelen van het eerste spel in de geschiedenis op een minicomputer, Spacewar van Steve Russell.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>PDP-1 (Programmed Data Processor-1) to pierwszy komputer z serii PDP firmy Digital Equipment Corporation, który został wyprodukowany w 1959 roku. PDP-1 to oryginalny sprzęt do zagrania w pierwszą w historii grę na minikomputerze, Spacewar Steve'a Russella.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>O PDP-1 (Programmed Data Processor-1) é o primeiro computador da série PDP da Digital Equipment Corporation e foi produzido pela primeira vez em 1959. O PDP-1 é o hardware original para jogar o primeiro jogo da história com um minicomputador, o Spacewar de Steve Russell.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>PDP-1 (Programmed Data Processor-1) - первый компьютер серии PDP компании Digital Equipment Corporation, впервые выпущенный в 1959 году. PDP-1 - это оригинальное оборудование для первой в истории игры на мини-компьютере, Spacewar Стива Рассела.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
