<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>The Aamber Pegasus is a home computer first produced in New Zealand. Introduction of the Apple II computer into the New Zealand market, and its subsequent heavy educational discounting was the final nail in the coffin for Technosys and the Aamber Pegasus computer. Total production numbers are unknown, but it is thought "around one hundred" were sold.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>L'Aamber Pegasus est un ordinateur domestique produit pour la première fois en Nouvelle-Zélande. L'introduction de l'ordinateur Apple II sur le marché néo-zélandais, et la forte remise éducative qui s'en est suivie, a été le dernier clou dans le cercueil de Technosys et de l'ordinateur Aamber Pegasus. Le nombre total d'ordinateurs produits n'est pas connu, mais on pense qu'une centaine d'entre eux ont été vendus.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="en">
<text>The Aamber Pegasus is a home computer first produced in New Zealand. Introduction of the Apple II computer into the New Zealand market, and its subsequent heavy educational discounting was the final nail in the coffin for Technosys and the Aamber Pegasus computer. Total production numbers are unknown, but it is thought "around one hundred" were sold.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>El Aamber Pegasus es un ordenador doméstico producido por primera vez en Nueva Zelanda. La llegada del Apple II al mercado neozelandés y sus fuertes descuentos para educación acabaron siendo decisivos para Technosys y para el propio Aamber Pegasus. Se desconoce la producción total, pero se cree que se vendieron alrededor de cien unidades.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>L'Aamber Pegasus è un home computer prodotto per la prima volta in Nuova Zelanda. L'arrivo dell'Apple II sul mercato neozelandese e i forti sconti destinati al settore educativo furono decisivi per Technosys e per l'Aamber Pegasus. Il numero totale di esemplari prodotti non è noto, ma si pensa che ne siano stati venduti circa cento.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Der Aamber Pegasus ist ein Heimcomputer, der erstmals in Neuseeland produziert wurde. Die Einführung des Apple II auf dem neuseeländischen Markt und die starken Bildungsrabatte wurden für Technosys und den Aamber Pegasus zum entscheidenden Rückschlag. Die Gesamtproduktion ist unbekannt, vermutlich wurden etwa einhundert Geräte verkauft.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>O Aamber Pegasus é um computador doméstico produzido originalmente na Nova Zelândia. A chegada do Apple II ao mercado neozelandês, seguida por fortes descontos para o setor educativo, acabou sendo decisiva para a Technosys e para o Aamber Pegasus. A produção total é desconhecida, mas acredita-se que cerca de cem unidades tenham sido vendidas.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>  Balloon Fight (1984)  </text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>Balloon Fight offers a faithful take on the arcade classic, despite the machine's limits, which require a simplified presentation. The player controls a character lifted by balloons, protecting them while bursting those of rival flyers in tense aerial duels. The gameplay remains effective and instantly accessible, true to the spirit of the original.
Fun fact : Balloon Fight was directly inspired by Williams' Joust, released in 1982, reworking its airborne combat idea with a more accessible style.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Balloon Fight propose une adaptation fidèle du classique d’arcade, malgré les limitations de la machine qui imposent une réalisation simplifiée. Le joueur dirige un personnage équipé de ballons qu’il doit protéger tout en crevant ceux des adversaires dans des affrontements aériens nerveux. Le gameplay reste efficace et immédiatement accessible, fidèle à l’esprit du jeu original.
Fun fact : Balloon Fight s’inspire directement du jeu Joust de Williams sorti en 1982, dont il reprend le principe de combats aériens avec une approche plus accessible.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="en">
<text>Balloon Fight offers a faithful take on the arcade classic, despite the machine's limits, which require a simplified presentation. The player controls a character lifted by balloons, protecting them while bursting those of rival flyers in tense aerial duels. The gameplay remains effective and instantly accessible, true to the spirit of the original.
Fun fact : Balloon Fight was directly inspired by Williams' Joust, released in 1982, reworking its airborne combat idea with a more accessible style.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Balloon Fight propone una adaptación fiel del clásico arcade, pese a las limitaciones de la máquina, que obligan a una presentación simplificada. El jugador controla a un personaje sostenido por globos, que debe proteger mientras revienta los de sus rivales en combates aéreos tensos. La jugabilidad sigue siendo eficaz e inmediata, fiel al espíritu del original.
Fun fact : Balloon Fight se inspiró directamente en Joust de Williams, lanzado en 1982, retomando sus combates aéreos con un enfoque más accesible.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Balloon Fight propone un adattamento fedele del classico arcade, nonostante i limiti della macchina impongano una realizzazione semplificata. Il giocatore controlla un personaggio sollevato da palloncini, da proteggere mentre fa scoppiare quelli degli avversari in duelli aerei nervosi. Il gameplay resta efficace e immediato, fedele allo spirito originale.
Fun fact : Balloon Fight si ispira direttamente a Joust di Williams, uscito nel 1982, riprendendone i combattimenti aerei con uno stile più accessibile.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Balloon Fight bietet eine originalgetreue Umsetzung des Arcade-Klassikers, auch wenn die Grenzen der Maschine eine vereinfachte Darstellung erzwingen. Gesteuert wird eine von Ballons getragene Figur, die sie schützen muss, während sie die Ballons der Gegner in hektischen Luftduellen platzen lässt. Das Gameplay bleibt effektiv, direkt zugänglich und nah am Geist des Originals.
Fun fact : Balloon Fight wurde direkt von Williams' Joust aus dem Jahr 1982 inspiriert und überträgt dessen Luftkämpfe in eine zugänglichere Form.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Balloon Fight oferece uma adaptação fiel do clássico arcade, apesar das limitações da máquina, que impõem uma apresentação simplificada. O jogador controla um personagem erguido por balões, que precisa protegê-los enquanto estoura os dos adversários em duelos aéreos tensos. A jogabilidade continua eficiente e imediata, fiel ao espírito original.
Fun fact : Balloon Fight foi diretamente inspirado em Joust, da Williams, lançado em 1982, reinterpretando seus combates aéreos de forma mais acessível.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
