<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>The Commodore PET is a range of personal computers produced from 1977 by Commodore International. A single all-in-one box combines a MOS Technology 6502 microprocessor, Commodore BASIC in read-only memory, a keyboard, a computer monitor and, in the early models, a cassette deck.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Le Commodore PET est une gamme d'ordinateurs personnels produits à partir de 1977 par Commodore International. Un seul boîtier tout-en-un combine un microprocesseur MOS Technology 6502, Commodore BASIC en mémoire morte, un clavier, un écran d'ordinateur et, dans les premiers modèles, une platine à cassettes.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Der Commodore PET ist eine Reihe von Personalcomputern, die ab 1977 von Commodore International hergestellt wurden. Ein einziges All-in-One-Gehäuse vereint einen Mikroprozessor MOS Technology 6502, Commodore BASIC im Festspeicher, eine Tastatur, einen Computerbildschirm und in den ersten Modellen auch ein Kassettendeck.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>El Commodore PET es una gama de ordenadores personales fabricados a partir de 1977 por Commodore International. Una única caja todo en uno combina un microprocesador MOS Technology 6502, Commodore BASIC en memoria de sólo lectura, un teclado, un monitor de ordenador y, en los primeros modelos, una pletina de casete.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Il Commodore PET è una gamma di personal computer prodotti dal 1977 da Commodore International. Un'unica scatola all-in-one combina un microprocessore MOS Technology 6502, il Commodore BASIC in memoria di sola lettura, una tastiera, un monitor e, nei primi modelli, una piastra a cassette.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>コモドールPETは、コモドールインターナショナルが1977年から製造したパーソナルコンピュータのシリーズである。MOSテクノロジー社製6502マイクロプロセッサ、コモドールBASIC（リードオンリーメモリ）、キーボード、コンピュータモニタ、初期モデルにはカセットデッキが1台のオールインワンボックスに収められている。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>De Commodore PET is een reeks personal computers die vanaf 1977 door Commodore International werd geproduceerd. Een enkel alles-in-één doosje combineert een MOS Technology 6502 microprocessor, Commodore BASIC in read-only geheugen, een toetsenbord, een computermonitor en, in de eerste modellen, een cassettedeck.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>Commodore PET to seria komputerów osobistych produkowanych od 1977 roku przez Commodore International. Pojedyncze pudełko typu "wszystko w jednym" łączy w sobie mikroprocesor MOS Technology 6502, Commodore BASIC w pamięci tylko do odczytu, klawiaturę, monitor komputerowy oraz, we wczesnych modelach, deck kasetowy.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>O Commodore PET é uma gama de computadores pessoais produzidos a partir de 1977 pela Commodore International. Uma única caixa tudo-em-um combina um microprocessador MOS Technology 6502, Commodore BASIC em memória só de leitura, um teclado, um monitor de computador e, nos primeiros modelos, um leitor de cassetes.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>Commodore PET - это серия персональных компьютеров, выпускавшихся с 1977 года компанией Commodore International. В одной универсальной коробке объединены микропроцессор MOS Technology 6502, Commodore BASIC в памяти только для чтения, клавиатура, компьютерный монитор и, в ранних моделях, кассетная дека.</text>
</text>


<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Adventureland (1978)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>The dragon from Adventureland represents one of the memorable threats in this text adventure, where each place is discovered through typed commands and minimal descriptions. On PET 2001 Series, imagination does most of the work: the monster exists mainly through words, puzzles and the tension created by the machine's limits.
Fun fact: Adventureland is often considered the first commercial adventure game released for microcomputers.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Le dragon d’Adventureland représente l’une des menaces marquantes de cette aventure textuelle, où chaque lieu se découvre par commandes tapées et descriptions minimalistes. Sur PET 2001 Series, l’imagination fait tout le travail : le monstre existe surtout à travers les mots, les énigmes et la tension créée par les limites de la machine.
Fun fact : Adventureland est souvent considéré comme le premier jeu d’aventure commercialisé sur micro-ordinateur.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>El dragón de Adventureland representa una de las amenazas más recordadas de esta aventura de texto, donde cada lugar se descubre mediante comandos escritos y descripciones mínimas. En PET 2001 Series, la imaginación hace casi todo el trabajo: el monstruo existe sobre todo a través de palabras, enigmas y la tensión creada por los límites de la máquina.
Dato curioso: Adventureland suele considerarse el primer juego de aventura comercial lanzado para microordenadores.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Il drago di Adventureland rappresenta una delle minacce più memorabili di questa avventura testuale, in cui ogni luogo si scopre tramite comandi digitati e descrizioni minime. Su PET 2001 Series, l’immaginazione fa quasi tutto il lavoro: il mostro esiste soprattutto attraverso parole, enigmi e la tensione creata dai limiti della macchina.
Curiosità: Adventureland è spesso considerato il primo gioco di avventura commerciale pubblicato per microcomputer.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Der Drache aus Adventureland steht für eine der einprägsamen Gefahren dieses Textadventures, in dem jeder Ort über getippte Befehle und knappe Beschreibungen entdeckt wird. Auf PET 2001 Series übernimmt die Vorstellungskraft fast alles: Das Monster entsteht vor allem durch Worte, Rätsel und die Spannung, die aus den Grenzen der Maschine wächst.
Interessante Tatsache: Adventureland gilt oft als erstes kommerzielles Adventure-Spiel für Mikrocomputer.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>O dragão de Adventureland representa uma das ameaças mais marcantes desta aventura em texto, onde cada local é descoberto por comandos digitados e descrições mínimas. No PET 2001 Series, a imaginação faz quase todo o trabalho: o monstro existe sobretudo pelas palavras, enigmas e tensão criada pelos limites da máquina.
Curiosidade: Adventureland é frequentemente considerado o primeiro jogo de aventura comercial lançado para microcomputadores.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
