<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>Pinball FX2 is a pinball game developed by Zen Studios. It features original and licensed tables (Marvel, Star Wars, etc.), with HD graphics and fluid gameplay. The game emphasizes online multiplayer, leaderboards and challenges. Its realistic physics engine enhances the experience over its predecessor.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Pinball FX2 est un jeu de flipper développé par Zen Studios. Il propose des tables originales et sous licence (Marvel, Star Wars, etc.), avec des graphismes HD et un gameplay fluide. Le jeu met l’accent sur le multijoueur en ligne, les classements et les défis. Son moteur physique réaliste améliore l’expérience par rapport à son prédécesseur.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Pinball FX2 es un juego de pinball desarrollado por Zen Studios. Ofrece mesas originales y con licencia (Marvel, Star Wars, etc.), con gráficos HD y una jugabilidad fluida. El juego pone el acento en el multijugador en línea, las clasificaciones y los desafíos. Su motor físico realista mejora la experiencia frente a su predecesor.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Pinball FX2 è un gioco di flipper sviluppato da Zen Studios. Offre tavoli originali e con licenza (Marvel, Star Wars, ecc.), con grafica HD e gameplay fluido. Il gioco punta su multiplayer online, classifiche e sfide. Il suo motore fisico realistico migliora l’esperienza rispetto al predecessore.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Pinball FX2 ist ein Flipperspiel von Zen Studios. Es bietet originale und lizenzierte Tische (Marvel, Star Wars usw.) mit HD-Grafik und flüssigem Spielgefühl. Der Fokus liegt auf Online-Mehrspieler, Ranglisten und Herausforderungen. Die realistische Physik-Engine verbessert das Erlebnis gegenüber dem Vorgänger.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Pinball FX2 é um jogo de pinball desenvolvido pela Zen Studios. Inclui mesas originais e licenciadas (Marvel, Star Wars, etc.), com gráficos HD e jogabilidade fluida. O jogo destaca multijogador online, rankings e desafios. O seu motor de física realista melhora a experiência em relação ao antecessor.</text>
</text>


<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Attack from Mars (1995)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>Cult Bally pinball table adapted for Pinball FX2, Attack from Mars builds a parody sci-fi atmosphere with flying saucers, invading Martians and precise shots toward the central ship. The table relies on clear objectives, fast modes and a spectacular climb toward the final battle.
Fun fact: The Martians’ voices and comic style helped make the table a lasting reference in modern pinball.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Flipper culte de Bally adapté dans Pinball FX2, Attack from Mars mise sur une ambiance de science-fiction parodique, avec soucoupes volantes, Martiens envahisseurs et tirs précis vers le vaisseau central. La table repose sur des objectifs clairs, des modes rapides et une montée spectaculaire vers l’affrontement final.
Fun fact : La voix des Martiens et leur style humoristique ont largement contribué à la popularité de la table, devenue une référence du flipper moderne.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Mesa de Bally de culto adaptada en Pinball FX2, Attack from Mars apuesta por una ciencia ficción paródica, con platillos volantes, marcianos invasores y tiros precisos hacia la nave central. La mesa se basa en objetivos claros, modos rápidos y una subida espectacular hacia el combate final.
Dato curioso: Las voces de los marcianos y su estilo humorístico ayudaron a convertir la mesa en una referencia del pinball moderno.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Tavolo cult di Bally adattato in Pinball FX2, Attack from Mars punta su un’atmosfera fantascientifica parodica, con dischi volanti, marziani invasori e tiri precisi verso l’astronave centrale. Il tavolo si basa su obiettivi chiari, modalità rapide e una scalata spettacolare verso lo scontro finale.
Curiosità: Le voci dei marziani e il loro stile comico hanno aiutato il tavolo a diventare un riferimento del flipper moderno.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Kult-Flipper von Bally, für Pinball FX2 adaptiert: Attack from Mars setzt auf parodistische Science-Fiction mit fliegenden Untertassen, angreifenden Marsmenschen und präzisen Schüssen auf das zentrale Raumschiff. Der Tisch lebt von klaren Zielen, schnellen Modi und dem spektakulären Weg zum Finale.
Interessante Tatsache: Die Stimmen der Marsmenschen und ihr Humor machten den Tisch zu einer festen Referenz des modernen Flippers.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Mesa clássica da Bally adaptada no Pinball FX2, Attack from Mars aposta numa ficção científica paródica, com discos voadores, marcianos invasores e disparos precisos contra a nave central. A mesa baseia-se em objetivos claros, modos rápidos e uma subida espetacular até ao confronto final.
Curiosidade: As vozes dos marcianos e o seu estilo humorístico ajudaram a tornar a mesa uma referência do pinball moderno.</text>
</text>
</view>
</theme>
