<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
    <formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
    <view name="system">

        <text name="system_description" extra="true">
            <text>TV Games are plug-and-play systems with built-in games, designed for immediate use by connecting directly to a television. They focus on simplicity, accessibility and quick gameplay sessions.</text>
        </text>
        <text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
            <text>Les TV Games sont des systèmes plug-and-play avec jeux intégrés, conçus pour être utilisés immédiatement en étant branchés directement à une télévision. Ils privilégient la simplicité, l’accessibilité et des sessions de jeu rapides.</text>
        </text>
        <text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
            <text>Las TV Games son sistemas plug-and-play con juegos integrados, diseñados para usarse de inmediato conectándose directamente a un televisor. Se centran en la simplicidad, la accesibilidad y partidas rápidas.</text>
        </text>
        <text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
            <text>Le TV Games sono sistemi plug-and-play con giochi integrati, progettati per un utilizzo immediato collegandosi direttamente a un televisore. Puntano su semplicità, accessibilità e sessioni rapide.</text>
        </text>
        <text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
            <text>TV Games sind Plug-and-Play-Systeme mit integrierten Spielen, die direkt an den Fernseher angeschlossen werden. Sie setzen auf Einfachheit, Zugänglichkeit und kurze Spielrunden.</text>
        </text>
        <text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
            <text>Os TV Games são sistemas plug-and-play com jogos integrados, concebidos para uso imediato ao serem ligados diretamente à televisão. Focam-se na simplicidade, acessibilidade e sessões rápidas.</text>
        </text>

        <text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
            <text>&#160;&#160;Spider-Man (2002)&#160;&#160;</text>
        </text>

        <text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
            <text>Spider-Man offers an accessible adaptation of the Marvel hero where the player chains movement, combat and action phases in city-inspired environments. Designed for simple platforms like TV games, it focuses on immediate controls and direct mechanics centered on movement and enemy encounters.
Fun fact: Many Spider-Man TV games were built directly into controllers or consoles, requiring no physical media and connecting straight to the television.</text>
        </text>

        <text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
            <text>Spider-Man propose une adaptation accessible du héros Marvel où le joueur enchaîne déplacements, combats et phases d’action dans des environnements inspirés de la ville. Pensé pour des supports simples comme les TV games, le jeu mise sur une prise en main immédiate et des mécaniques directes centrées sur les déplacements et l’affrontement d’ennemis.
Fun fact : De nombreux TV games Spider-Man étaient des jeux intégrés directement dans la manette ou la console, sans support physique, destinés à être branchés directement sur la télévision.</text>
        </text>

        <text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
            <text>Spider-Man ofrece una adaptación accesible del héroe de Marvel donde el jugador encadena movimientos, combates y fases de acción en entornos inspirados en la ciudad. Pensado para plataformas simples como TV games, apuesta por controles inmediatos y mecánicas directas centradas en el movimiento y el combate.
Dato curioso: Muchos TV games de Spider-Man estaban integrados directamente en el mando o la consola, sin soporte físico y listos para conectarse al televisor.</text>
        </text>

        <text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
            <text>Spider-Man propone un adattamento accessibile dell’eroe Marvel dove il giocatore alterna movimento, combattimento e azione in ambienti ispirati alla città. Pensato per piattaforme semplici come i TV games, punta su controlli immediati e meccaniche dirette.
Curiosità: Molti TV games di Spider-Man erano integrati direttamente nel controller o nella console, senza supporti fisici e pronti all’uso su TV.</text>
        </text>

        <text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
            <text>Spider-Man bietet eine zugängliche Umsetzung des Marvel-Helden mit Bewegung, Kämpfen und Action in städtischen Umgebungen. Für einfache Plattformen wie TV Games konzipiert, setzt es auf direkte Steuerung und klare Mechaniken.
Interessante Tatsache: Viele Spider-Man TV Games waren direkt in Controller oder Konsole integriert und benötigten kein physisches Medium.</text>
        </text>

        <text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
            <text>Spider-Man apresenta uma adaptação acessível do herói da Marvel com movimento, combate e ação em ambientes urbanos. Pensado para plataformas simples como TV games, aposta em controlos imediatos e mecânicas diretas.
Curiosidade: Muitos TV games de Spider-Man eram integrados diretamente no comando ou consola, sem suporte físico e ligados diretamente à televisão.</text>
        </text>

    </view>
</theme>