<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>The PlayStation 2 (officially abbreviated to PS2) competed with Sega's Dreamcast, Nintendo's GameCube and Microsoft's Xbox. It was an immediate success, selling a million units in a few days in Japan. It is the best-selling home console in the history of video games.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>La PlayStation 2 (abrégé officiellement PS2) était en concurrence avec la Dreamcast de Sega, la GameCube de Nintendo et la Xbox de Microsoft. Elle a connu un succès immédiat avec un million d'exemplaires vendus en quelques jours au Japon. Elle est la console de salon la plus vendue de l'histoire des jeux vidéo.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Die PlayStation 2 (offiziell abgekürzt PS2) konkurrierte mit der Dreamcast von Sega, dem GameCube von Nintendo und der Xbox von Microsoft. Sie war ein sofortiger Erfolg und verkaufte in Japan innerhalb weniger Tage eine Million Exemplare. Sie ist die meistverkaufte Heimkonsole in der Geschichte der Videospiele.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>La PlayStation 2 (abreviada oficialmente como PS2) compitió con la Dreamcast de Sega, la GameCube de Nintendo y la Xbox de Microsoft. Fue un éxito inmediato, vendiendo un millón de unidades en pocos días en Japón. Es la consola doméstica más vendida de la historia de los videojuegos.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>La PlayStation 2 (ufficialmente abbreviata in PS2) è entrata in competizione con il Dreamcast di Sega, il GameCube di Nintendo e la Xbox di Microsoft. Il successo è stato immediato, con un milione di unità vendute in pochi giorni in Giappone. È la console domestica più venduta nella storia dei videogiochi.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>プレイステーション2（正式にはPS2と略される）は、セガのドリームキャスト、任天堂のゲームキューブ、マイクロソフトのXboxと競合していた。すぐに成功を収め、日本では数日で100万台を売り上げた。ビデオゲーム史上、最も売れた家庭用ゲーム機である。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>De PlayStation 2 (officieel afgekort tot PS2) concurreerde met Sega's Dreamcast, Nintendo's GameCube en Microsoft's Xbox. Het was onmiddellijk een succes en verkocht in een paar dagen tijd een miljoen exemplaren in Japan. Het is de best verkopende thuisconsole in de geschiedenis van de videospelletjes.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>PlayStation 2 (oficjalnie skracane do PS2) konkurowało z Dreamcastem firmy Sega, GameCube'em firmy Nintendo i Xboxem firmy Microsoft. Odniósł on natychmiastowy sukces, sprzedając milion sztuk w ciągu kilku dni w Japonii. Jest to najlepiej sprzedająca się konsola domowa w historii gier wideo.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>A PlayStation 2 (oficialmente abreviada para PS2) competiu com a Sega's Dreamcast, a GameCube da Nintendo e a Xbox da Microsoft. Foi um sucesso imediato, vendendo um milhão de unidades em poucos dias no Japão. É a consola doméstica mais vendida na história dos videojogos.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>PlayStation 2 (официальное сокращение PS2) конкурировала с Dreamcast от Sega, GameCube от Nintendo и Xbox от Microsoft. Она имела немедленный успех, продав миллион копий за несколько дней в Японии. Это самая продаваемая домашняя консоль в истории видеоигр.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Grand Theft Auto: Vice City (2002)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>The woman in a swimsuit from the iconic game cover embodies the bold and colorful aesthetic of Grand Theft Auto: Vice City, inspired by 1980s Miami. With her confident gaze and relaxed posture, she reflects the hedonistic atmosphere and distinctive visual style that made the game instantly recognizable.
Fun fact: The Vice City cover draws inspiration from Scarface and Miami Vice, using a mosaic composition already seen in cinema but popularized in video games by the GTA series.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>La femme en maillot issue de la célèbre jaquette du jeu incarne l’esthétique provocante et colorée de Grand Theft Auto: Vice City, inspirée de Miami dans les années 80. Avec son regard assuré et sa posture détendue, elle symbolise l’ambiance hédoniste et le style visuel iconique du titre, devenu immédiatement reconnaissable parmi les visuels les plus marquants du jeu vidéo.
Fun fact : La jaquette de Vice City s’inspire de Scarface et de Miami Vice, avec une composition en mosaïque déjà utilisée au cinéma mais popularisée dans le jeu vidéo par la série GTA.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>La mujer en bañador de la icónica portada del juego encarna la estética provocadora y colorida de Grand Theft Auto: Vice City, inspirada en el Miami de los años 80. Con su mirada segura y postura relajada, refleja la atmósfera hedonista y el estilo visual distintivo que hizo al juego inmediatamente reconocible.
Dato curioso: La portada de Vice City se inspira en Scarface y Miami Vice, usando una composición en mosaico ya vista en el cine pero popularizada en los videojuegos por la serie GTA.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>La donna in costume dalla celebre copertina del gioco incarna l’estetica provocatoria e colorata di Grand Theft Auto: Vice City, ispirata alla Miami degli anni 80. Con il suo sguardo sicuro e la postura rilassata, riflette l’atmosfera edonistica e lo stile visivo distintivo che ha reso il gioco immediatamente riconoscibile.
Curiosità: La copertina di Vice City si ispira a Scarface e Miami Vice, utilizzando una composizione a mosaico già vista nel cinema ma resa popolare nei videogiochi dalla serie GTA.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Die Frau im Badeanzug vom ikonischen Spielcover verkörpert die provokante und farbenfrohe Ästhetik von Grand Theft Auto: Vice City, inspiriert vom Miami der 80er Jahre. Mit ihrem selbstbewussten Blick und ihrer entspannten Haltung spiegelt sie die hedonistische Atmosphäre und den markanten visuellen Stil wider, der das Spiel sofort erkennbar machte.
Interessante Tatsache: Das Vice City Cover ist von Scarface und Miami Vice inspiriert und nutzt eine Mosaikkomposition, die bereits im Kino verwendet wurde, aber durch die GTA-Reihe im Videospielbereich populär wurde.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>A mulher de maiô da icônica capa do jogo representa a estética provocante e colorida de Grand Theft Auto: Vice City, inspirada na Miami dos anos 80. Com seu olhar confiante e postura relaxada, ela reflete a atmosfera hedonista e o estilo visual marcante que tornou o jogo imediatamente reconhecível.
Curiosidade: A capa de Vice City se inspira em Scarface e Miami Vice, usando uma composição em mosaico já vista no cinema, mas popularizada nos videogames pela série GTA.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>