<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>The PlayStation 4 is an eighth-generation home video game console developed by Sony Computer Entertainment. Introduced on February 20, 2013, it succeeds the PlayStation 3 and competes with Microsoft's Xbox One and Nintendo's Wii U and Switch. Always equipped with a Blu-ray player, it can achieve Full HD (1080p) definition for video games and Ultra HD for photos and videos.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>La PlayStation 4 est une console de jeux vidéo de salon de huitième génération développée par Sony Computer Entertainment. Présentée le 20 février 2013, elle succède à la PlayStation 3 et se place en concurrence avec la Xbox One de Microsoft et la Wii U puis la Switch de Nintendo. Toujours équipée d’un lecteur Blu-ray, elle peut atteindre une définition Full HD (1080p) pour les jeux vidéo et Ultra HD pour les photos et vidéos.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>La PlayStation 4 es una consola doméstica de octava generación desarrollada por Sony Computer Entertainment. Presentada el 20 de febrero de 2013, sucede a la PlayStation 3 y compite con la Xbox One de Microsoft y con la Wii U y Switch de Nintendo. Equipada con lector Blu-ray, puede alcanzar resolución Full HD en juegos y Ultra HD para fotos y vídeos.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>La PlayStation 4 è una console domestica di ottava generazione sviluppata da Sony Computer Entertainment. Presentata il 20 febbraio 2013, succede alla PlayStation 3 e compete con Xbox One di Microsoft, Wii U e Switch di Nintendo. Dotata di lettore Blu-ray, può raggiungere il Full HD nei giochi e l'Ultra HD per foto e video.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Die PlayStation 4 ist eine Heimkonsole der achten Generation, entwickelt von Sony Computer Entertainment. Sie wurde am 20. Februar 2013 vorgestellt, folgt auf die PlayStation 3 und konkurriert mit Microsofts Xbox One sowie Nintendos Wii U und Switch. Mit Blu-ray-Laufwerk erreicht sie Full HD in Spielen und Ultra HD für Fotos und Videos.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>A PlayStation 4 é uma consola doméstica de oitava geração desenvolvida pela Sony Computer Entertainment. Apresentada em 20 de fevereiro de 2013, sucede à PlayStation 3 e compete com a Xbox One da Microsoft e com a Wii U e Switch da Nintendo. Equipada com leitor Blu-ray, pode atingir Full HD nos jogos e Ultra HD em fotos e vídeos.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Red Dead Redemption 2 (2018)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>Red Dead Redemption 2 places the player in a realistic western where outlaws and civilians move through a richly detailed open world. Gunfights, exploration, saloon life and everyday encounters build the atmosphere of late 19th century America.
Fun fact: The game uses thousands of contextual dialogue lines and detailed NPC routines to make towns, camps and roads feel alive.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Red Dead Redemption 2 plonge le joueur dans un western réaliste où hors-la-loi et civils évoluent dans un monde ouvert riche en détails. Fusillades, exploration, vie de saloon et rencontres du quotidien construisent l’ambiance de l’Amérique de la fin du XIXe siècle.
Fun fact : Le jeu utilise des milliers de lignes de dialogues contextuels et des routines de PNJ détaillées pour rendre villes, camps et routes crédibles.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Red Dead Redemption 2 sitúa al jugador en un western realista donde forajidos y civiles viven en un mundo abierto lleno de detalles. Tiroteos, exploración, salones y encuentros cotidianos construyen la atmósfera de la América de finales del siglo XIX.
Dato curioso: El juego usa miles de líneas de diálogo contextual y rutinas detalladas de PNJ para dar vida a pueblos, campamentos y caminos.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Red Dead Redemption 2 porta il giocatore in un western realistico dove fuorilegge e civili vivono in un mondo aperto ricco di dettagli. Sparatorie, esplorazione, vita da saloon e incontri quotidiani costruiscono l’atmosfera dell’America di fine Ottocento.
Curiosità: Il gioco usa migliaia di dialoghi contestuali e routine dettagliate dei PNG per rendere vivi città, accampamenti e strade.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Red Dead Redemption 2 versetzt den Spieler in einen realistischen Western, in dem Gesetzlose und Zivilisten durch eine detailreiche offene Welt ziehen. Schießereien, Erkundung, Saloonleben und Begegnungen prägen das Amerika des späten 19. Jahrhunderts.
Interessante Tatsache: Das Spiel nutzt tausende kontextbezogene Dialogzeilen und genaue NPC-Routinen, um Städte, Lager und Wege lebendig wirken zu lassen.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Red Dead Redemption 2 coloca o jogador num western realista onde fora da lei e civis vivem num mundo aberto cheio de detalhes. Tiroteios, exploração, saloons e encontros do dia a dia constroem a atmosfera da América do fim do século XIX.
Curiosidade: O jogo usa milhares de falas contextuais e rotinas detalhadas de NPCs para tornar cidades, acampamentos e estradas mais vivos.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
