<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>The PlayStation Vita (プレイステーション・ヴィータ) is a portable video games console. Its codename was Next Generation Portable (NGP). It is the successor to the PlayStation Portable and its various derivatives. Its main competitors are the Nintendo 3DS and the smartphone market.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>La PlayStation Vita (プレイステーション・ヴィータ) est une console de jeux vidéo portable. Son nom de code était Next Generation Portable (NGP). Elle succède à la PlayStation Portable et aux différentes déclinaisons qui en découlent. Ses concurrents principaux sont la Nintendo 3DS et le marché du smartphone.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Die PlayStation Vita (プレイステーション・ヴィータ) ist eine tragbare Videospielkonsole. Ihr Codename war Next Generation Portable (NGP). Sie ist der Nachfolger der PlayStation Portable und ihrer verschiedenen Ableger. Ihre Hauptkonkurrenten sind der Nintendo 3DS und der Smartphone-Markt.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>La PlayStation Vita (プレイステーション・ヴィータ) es una videoconsola portátil. Su nombre en clave era Next Generation Portable (NGP). Es la sucesora de la PlayStation Portable y sus diversos derivados. Sus principales competidores son la Nintendo 3DS y el mercado de los smartphones.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>La PlayStation Vita (プレイステーション・ヴィータ) è una console per videogiochi portatile. Il suo nome in codice era Next Generation Portable (NGP). È il successore della PlayStation Portable e dei suoi vari derivati. I suoi principali concorrenti sono il Nintendo 3DS e il mercato degli smartphone.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>プレイステーション ヴィータ（PlayStation Vita）は、携帯型ゲーム機である。コードネームは次世代ポータブル（NGP）。プレイステーション・ポータブルとその派生機種の後継機である。主な競争相手はニンテンドー3DSとスマートフォン市場である。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>De PlayStation Vita (プレイテーション・ヴィータ) is een draagbare videogameconsole. De codenaam was Next Generation Portable (NGP). Het is de opvolger van de PlayStation Portable en zijn verschillende afgeleiden. De belangrijkste concurrenten zijn de Nintendo 3DS en de smartphonemarkt.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>PlayStation Vita (プレイステーション・ヴィータ) to przenośna konsola do gier wideo. Jej nazwa kodowa to Next Generation Portable (NGP). Jest to następca PlayStation Portable i jego różnych pochodnych. Jej głównymi konkurentami są Nintendo 3DS i rynek smartfonów.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>A PlayStation Vita (プレイステーション・ヴィータ) é uma consola de videojogos portátil. O seu nome de código era Next Generation Portable (NGP). É a sucessora da PlayStation Portable e dos seus vários derivados. Os seus principais concorrentes são a Nintendo 3DS e o mercado dos smartphones.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>PlayStation Vita (プレイステーション・ヴィータ) - портативная консоль для видеоигр. Ее кодовое название - Next Generation Portable (NGP). Консоль является преемницей PlayStation Portable и ее различных производных. Ее основными конкурентами являются Nintendo 3DS и рынок смартфонов.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>


