<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>Resident Evil, known in Japan as Biohazard, is a series of survival horror action-adventure video games. The franchise is owned by the Japanese company Capcom. It made its PlayStation debut in 1996. Thanks to its success, numerous sequels have been produced for most consoles. Resident Evil is a major series comprising more than 30 games, including remakes and remasterings.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Resident Evil, connue au Japon sous le nom Biohazard, est une série de jeux vidéo d'aventure, action et réflexion de type survival horror. La franchise appartient à la société japonaise Capcom. Elle fait ses débuts sur PlayStation en 1996. Grâce à son succès, de nombreuses suites sont réalisées, sur la plupart des consoles. Resident Evil est une série importante comprenant plus de 30 jeux en comptant les remakes et les remastérisations.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Resident Evil, conocida en Japón como Biohazard, es una serie de videojuegos de aventura y acción de terror de supervivencia. La franquicia pertenece a la compañía japonesa Capcom. Debutó en PlayStation en 1996. Gracias a su éxito, se han producido numerosas secuelas para la mayoría de consolas. Resident Evil es una saga importante con más de 30 juegos, incluidos remakes y remasterizaciones.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Resident Evil, nota in Giappone come Biohazard, è una serie di videogiochi d'azione e avventura survival horror. Il franchise appartiene alla società giapponese Capcom. Ha debuttato su PlayStation nel 1996. Grazie al suo successo, sono stati prodotti numerosi seguiti per la maggior parte delle console. Resident Evil è una saga importante con oltre 30 giochi, inclusi remake e remaster.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Resident Evil, in Japan als Biohazard bekannt, ist eine Survival-Horror-Reihe mit Action-Adventure-Spielen. Die Marke gehört dem japanischen Unternehmen Capcom. Ihr PlayStation-Debüt gab sie 1996. Durch den Erfolg entstanden zahlreiche Fortsetzungen für die meisten Konsolen. Resident Evil ist eine bedeutende Reihe mit mehr als 30 Spielen, darunter Remakes und Remaster.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Resident Evil, conhecida no Japão como Biohazard, é uma série de jogos de ação e aventura de survival horror. A franquia pertence à empresa japonesa Capcom. Estreou no PlayStation em 1996. Graças ao seu sucesso, muitas sequências foram produzidas para a maioria dos consoles. Resident Evil é uma saga importante com mais de 30 jogos, incluindo remakes e remasterizações.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Resident Evil 2 (PlayStation, 1998)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>Claire Redfield is a determined civilian trapped in Raccoon City during the outbreak. Searching for her brother Chris, she faces zombies and bio-organic creatures with remarkable composure. Less experienced than a soldier, she relies on courage, clear judgment and survival instinct in a hostile city where every mistake can be fatal.
Fun fact: Her red “Made in Heaven” jacket became iconic, almost as much as the Umbrella logo, a major symbol of the saga.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Claire Redfield est une civile déterminée qui se retrouve piégée dans Raccoon City en pleine épidémie. À la recherche de son frère Chris, elle affronte zombies et créatures bio-organiques avec un sang-froid remarquable. Moins expérimentée qu’un soldat, elle compense par son courage, sa lucidité et sa capacité à survivre dans un environnement hostile où chaque erreur peut être fatale.
Fun fact : Sa veste rouge “Made in Heaven” est devenue iconique, presque autant que le logo d’Umbrella, symbole majeur de la saga.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Claire Redfield es una civil decidida que queda atrapada en Raccoon City durante el brote. Mientras busca a su hermano Chris, se enfrenta a zombis y criaturas bioorgánicas con una notable sangre fría. Menos experta que un soldado, compensa con valor, lucidez e instinto de supervivencia en una ciudad hostil donde cada error puede ser fatal.
Dato curioso: Su chaqueta roja “Made in Heaven” se volvió icónica, casi tanto como el logo de Umbrella, símbolo mayor de la saga.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Claire Redfield è una civile determinata rimasta intrappolata a Raccoon City durante l'epidemia. Alla ricerca del fratello Chris, affronta zombi e creature bio-organiche con notevole sangue freddo. Meno esperta di un soldato, compensa con coraggio, lucidità e istinto di sopravvivenza in una città ostile dove ogni errore può essere fatale.
Curiosità: La sua giacca rossa “Made in Heaven” è diventata iconica, quasi quanto il logo Umbrella, simbolo maggiore della saga.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Claire Redfield ist eine entschlossene Zivilistin, die während des Ausbruchs in Raccoon City festsitzt. Auf der Suche nach ihrem Bruder Chris stellt sie sich Zombies und bio-organischen Kreaturen mit bemerkenswerter Ruhe. Weniger ausgebildet als ein Soldat, überlebt sie durch Mut, Klarheit und Instinkt in einer feindlichen Stadt, in der jeder Fehler tödlich sein kann.
Interessante Tatsache: Ihre rote “Made in Heaven”-Jacke wurde fast so ikonisch wie das Umbrella-Logo, ein wichtiges Symbol der Saga.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Claire Redfield é uma civil determinada que fica presa em Raccoon City durante o surto. Em busca de seu irmão Chris, enfrenta zumbis e criaturas bio-orgânicas com notável sangue-frio. Menos experiente que um soldado, compensa com coragem, lucidez e instinto de sobrevivência numa cidade hostil onde cada erro pode ser fatal.
Curiosidade: Sua jaqueta vermelha “Made in Heaven” virou icônica, quase tanto quanto o logo da Umbrella, símbolo maior da saga.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
