<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>Welcome to Retrobat. This is where you will be able to tune your different emulators supported by the beautiful front-end you have in your hands. In case of doubt or difficulty, come and join us on the discord so we can discuss it together.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Bienvenue sur Retrobat. C'est ici que vous allez pouvoir régler vos différents émulateurs pris en charge par le magnifique Front-end que vous avez entre les mains. En cas de doute ou de difficulté, venez nous rejoindre sur le discord qu'on en discute ensemble.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Willkommen bei Retrobat. Hier werden Sie Ihre verschiedenen Emulatoren einstellen können, die von dem großartigen Frontend, das Sie in Ihren Händen halten, unterstützt werden. Wenn Sie Zweifel oder Schwierigkeiten haben, kommen Sie zu uns in den Discord, damit wir gemeinsam darüber diskutieren können.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Bienvenido a Retrobat. Aquí es donde podrás tunear tus diferentes emuladores apoyándote en el precioso front-end que tienes en tus manos. En caso de duda o dificultad, ven y únete a nosotros en el discord para que podamos discutirlo juntos.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Benvenuti in Retrobat. Qui potrete mettere a punto i vostri diversi emulatori supportati dal bellissimo front-end che avete tra le mani. In caso di dubbi o difficoltà, unisciti a noi su discord per discuterne insieme.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>Retrobatへようこそ。ここでは、あなたの手にある美しいフロントエンドでサポートされているさまざまなエミュレータを調整することができます。疑問や困難がある場合は、discordに参加して、一緒に議論しましょう。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>Welkom bij Retrobat. Hier zul je je verschillende emulators kunnen tunen, ondersteund door de prachtige front-end die je in handen hebt. In geval van twijfel of moeilijkheden, kom bij ons op de discord zodat we het samen kunnen bespreken.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>Witamy w Retrobat. To tutaj będziesz mógł dostroić swoje różne emulatory wspierane przez piękny front-end, który masz w swoich rękach. W przypadku wątpliwości lub trudności, dołącz do nas na discordzie, abyśmy mogli wspólnie podyskutować.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Bem-vindo ao Retrobat. É aqui que poderá instalar os seus diferentes emuladores apoiados pela bela fachada que tem nas suas mãos. Em caso de dúvida ou dificuldade, venha juntar-se a nós na discórdia para que possamos discuti-la em conjunto.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>Добро пожаловать в Retrobat. Здесь вы сможете настроить различные эмуляторы, поддерживаемые прекрасным фронтэндом, который вы держите в руках. В случае сомнений или трудностей, присоединяйтесь к нам на discord, чтобы мы могли обсудить это вместе.</text>
</text>


<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>The RetroBat figurine, created by Aynshe, embodies the system’s visual identity with a modern, readable style inspired by the retro universe. This figurine was imagined with the help of AI, blending retro influences and futuristic touches in a result that feels both nostalgic and contemporary. It symbolizes easy access to many platforms and the unification of emulation on PC, through an interface designed to navigate easily between games and systems, while adding an unexpected spark of creativity.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>La figurine RetroBat, réalisée par Aynshe, incarne l’identité visuelle du système avec un style moderne et lisible inspiré de l’univers rétro. Cette figurine a été imaginée à l’aide de l’IA, mêlant influences rétro et touches futuristes dans un rendu à la fois nostalgique et contemporain. Elle symbolise l’accès simplifié à de nombreuses plateformes et l’unification de l’émulation sur PC, avec une interface pensée pour naviguer facilement entre les jeux et systèmes, tout en apportant une pointe de créativité inattendue.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>La figurina RetroBat, creada por Aynshe, encarna la identidad visual del sistema con un estilo moderno y legible inspirado en el universo retro. Fue imaginada con ayuda de la IA, mezclando influencias retro y toques futuristas en un resultado nostálgico y contemporáneo. Simboliza el acceso simplificado a muchas plataformas y la unificación de la emulación en PC, con una interfaz pensada para navegar fácilmente entre juegos y sistemas, aportando un toque de creatividad inesperada.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>La statuetta RetroBat, realizzata da Aynshe, incarna l’identità visiva del sistema con uno stile moderno e leggibile ispirato all’universo retro. È stata immaginata con l’aiuto dell’IA, mescolando influenze retro e tocchi futuristici in un risultato nostalgico e contemporaneo. Simboleggia l’accesso semplificato a molte piattaforme e l’unificazione dell’emulazione su PC, con un’interfaccia pensata per navigare facilmente tra giochi e sistemi, aggiungendo una nota di creatività inattesa.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Die RetroBat-Figur, erstellt von Aynshe, verkörpert die visuelle Identität des Systems mit einem modernen, klaren Stil, der von der Retro-Welt inspiriert ist. Sie wurde mit Hilfe von KI entworfen und verbindet Retro-Einflüsse mit futuristischen Akzenten zu einem zugleich nostalgischen und zeitgemäßen Ergebnis. Sie symbolisiert den einfachen Zugang zu vielen Plattformen und die Vereinheitlichung der Emulation auf dem PC, mit einer Oberfläche zum leichten Navigieren zwischen Spielen und Systemen sowie einem unerwarteten Hauch Kreativität.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>A figurinha RetroBat, criada por Aynshe, encarna a identidade visual do sistema com um estilo moderno e legível inspirado no universo retro. Foi imaginada com a ajuda da IA, misturando influências retro e toques futuristas num resultado nostálgico e contemporâneo. Simboliza o acesso simplificado a muitas plataformas e a unificação da emulação no PC, com uma interface pensada para navegar facilmente entre jogos e sistemas, trazendo ainda um toque de criatividade inesperada.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
