<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>Sammy Corporation (サミー株式会社, Samī kabushikigaisha?) is a Japanese company that has been in the business of developing and marketing pachinkos, pachislots and video games since 1975.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Sammy Corporation (サミー株式会社, Samī kabushikigaisha?) est une société japonaise qui exerce son activité dans le domaine du développement et commercialisation de pachinkos, de pachislots et de jeux vidéo depuis 1975.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Sammy Corporation (サミー株式会社, Samī kabushikigaisha?) ist ein japanisches Unternehmen, das seit 1975 im Bereich der Entwicklung und Vermarktung von Pachinkos, Pachislots und Videospielen tätig ist.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Sammy Corporation (サミー株式会社, Samī kabushikigaisha?) es una empresa japonesa dedicada al desarrollo y comercialización de pachinkos, pachislots y videojuegos desde 1975.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Sammy Corporation (サミー株式会社, Samī kabushikigaisha?) è un'azienda giapponese che dal 1975 si occupa dello sviluppo e della commercializzazione di pachinko, pachislot e videogiochi.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>サミー株式会社（Sammy Corporation, Samī kabushikigaisha? ）は、1975年以来、パチンコ、パチスロ、ビデオゲームの開発・販売事業を行う日本の企業である。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>Sammy Corporation (サミー株式会社, Samī kabushikigaisha?) is een Japanse onderneming die zich sinds 1975 bezighoudt met de ontwikkeling en verkoop van pachinko's, pachislots en videospelletjes.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>Sammy Corporation (サミー株式会社, Samī kabushikigaisha?) to japońska firma, która od 1975 roku zajmuje się rozwojem i marketingiem pachinkos, pachislots i gier wideo.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>A Sammy Corporation (サミー株式会社, Samī kabushikigaisha?) é uma empresa japonesa que se dedica ao desenvolvimento e comercialização de pachinkos, pachislots e jogos de vídeo desde 1975.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>Sammy Corporation (サミー株式会社, Samī kabushikigaisha?) - японская компания, занимающаяся разработкой и продажей пачинко, пахислотов и видеоигр с 1975 года.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
