<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>Sammy Corporation (サミー株式会社, Samī kabushikigaisha?) is a Japanese company that has been in the business of developing and marketing pachinkos, pachislots and video games since 1975.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Sammy Corporation (サミー株式会社, Samī kabushikigaisha?) est une société japonaise qui exerce son activité dans le domaine du développement et commercialisation de pachinkos, de pachislots et de jeux vidéo depuis 1975.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Sammy Corporation (サミー株式会社, Samī kabushikigaisha?) ist ein japanisches Unternehmen, das seit 1975 im Bereich der Entwicklung und Vermarktung von Pachinkos, Pachislots und Videospielen tätig ist.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Sammy Corporation (サミー株式会社, Samī kabushikigaisha?) es una empresa japonesa dedicada al desarrollo y comercialización de pachinkos, pachislots y videojuegos desde 1975.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Sammy Corporation (サミー株式会社, Samī kabushikigaisha?) è un'azienda giapponese che dal 1975 si occupa dello sviluppo e della commercializzazione di pachinko, pachislot e videogiochi.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>サミー株式会社（Sammy Corporation, Samī kabushikigaisha? ）は、1975年以来、パチンコ、パチスロ、ビデオゲームの開発・販売事業を行う日本の企業である。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>Sammy Corporation (サミー株式会社, Samī kabushikigaisha?) is een Japanse onderneming die zich sinds 1975 bezighoudt met de ontwikkeling en verkoop van pachinko's, pachislots en videospelletjes.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>Sammy Corporation (サミー株式会社, Samī kabushikigaisha?) to japońska firma, która od 1975 roku zajmuje się rozwojem i marketingiem pachinkos, pachislots i gier wideo.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>A Sammy Corporation (サミー株式会社, Samī kabushikigaisha?) é uma empresa japonesa que se dedica ao desenvolvimento e comercialização de pachinkos, pachislots e jogos de vídeo desde 1975.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>Sammy Corporation (サミー株式会社, Samī kabushikigaisha?) - японская компания, занимающаяся разработкой и продажей пачинко, пахислотов и видеоигр с 1975 года.</text>
</text>


<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Guilty Gear Isuka (2003)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>Guilty Gear Isuka keeps the nervous, eccentric Guilty Gear universe, with fast battles, huge weapons, aerial attacks and spectacular effects. Its wider arenas and lane-switching system, inspired by beat'em ups, give the game a more chaotic and unusual feel for a versus fighting title.
Fun fact: Guilty Gear Isuka was the first game in the series to allow battles with up to four players at the same time.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Guilty Gear Isuka reprend l’univers nerveux et excentrique de la série avec des combats rapides mêlant armes gigantesques, attaques aériennes et effets spectaculaires. Les affrontements utilisent des arènes élargies avec un système de changement de plan inspiré des beat’em up, donnant un style plus chaotique et inhabituel pour un jeu de versus fighting.
Fun fact : Guilty Gear Isuka est le premier épisode de la série à proposer des combats jusqu’à quatre joueurs simultanément.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Guilty Gear Isuka retoma el universo nervioso y excéntrico de la serie, con combates rápidos, armas enormes, ataques aéreos y efectos espectaculares. Sus arenas más amplias y el cambio de plano inspirado en los beat'em up le dan un estilo más caótico e inusual para un juego de lucha versus.
Dato curioso: Guilty Gear Isuka fue el primer episodio de la serie en permitir combates de hasta cuatro jugadores simultáneos.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Guilty Gear Isuka riprende l’universo frenetico ed eccentrico della serie, con combattimenti rapidi, armi enormi, attacchi aerei ed effetti spettacolari. Le arene più ampie e il cambio di piano ispirato ai beat'em up gli danno uno stile più caotico e insolito per un picchiaduro versus.
Curiosità: Guilty Gear Isuka fu il primo episodio della serie a proporre scontri fino a quattro giocatori simultanei.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Guilty Gear Isuka greift das schnelle und exzentrische Universum der Reihe auf, mit rasanten Kämpfen, riesigen Waffen, Luftangriffen und spektakulären Effekten. Breitere Arenen und ein Ebenenwechsel nach Beat'em-up-Art verleihen dem Versus-Kampf einen chaotischeren, ungewohnten Stil.
Interessante Tatsache: Guilty Gear Isuka war der erste Teil der Reihe mit Kämpfen für bis zu vier Spieler gleichzeitig.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Guilty Gear Isuka retoma o universo nervoso e excêntrico da série, com combates rápidos, armas gigantes, ataques aéreos e efeitos espetaculares. As arenas mais amplas e a troca de plano inspirada nos beat'em ups dão ao jogo um estilo mais caótico e incomum para um jogo de luta versus.
Curiosidade: Guilty Gear Isuka foi o primeiro episódio da série a permitir combates com até quatro jogadores simultâneos.</text>
</text>


</view>
</theme>
