<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>The Satellaview is an extension of the Super Famicom, marketed only in Japan. This system provided some additional technical capabilities as well as a download service for games, codes and information. All data was sent through a satellite TV station.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Le Satellaview est une extension de la Super Famicom commercialisée uniquement au Japon. Ce système apportait quelques capacités techniques supplémentaires ainsi qu'un service de téléchargement de jeux, de codes et d'informations. Toutes les données transitaient en effet par une station de télévision par satellite.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Das Satellaview war eine Erweiterung des Super Famicom, die nur in Japan vertrieben wurde. Das System bot einige zusätzliche technische Möglichkeiten sowie einen Service zum Herunterladen von Spielen, Codes und Informationen. Alle Daten wurden über eine Satelliten-TV-Station übertragen.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>El Satellaview es una extensión de la Super Famicom, comercializada únicamente en Japón. Este sistema ofrecía algunas capacidades técnicas adicionales, así como un servicio de descarga de juegos, códigos e información. Todos los datos se enviaban a través de una estación de televisión por satélite.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Il Satellaview è un'estensione del Super Famicom, commercializzato solo in Giappone. Questo sistema offriva alcune funzionalità tecniche aggiuntive e un servizio di download di giochi, codici e informazioni. Tutti i dati venivano inviati attraverso una stazione televisiva satellitare.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>サテラビューは、日本でのみ販売されたスーパーファミコンの拡張版である。このシステムは、ゲーム、コード、情報のダウンロードサービスだけでなく、いくつかの追加の技術的機能を提供しました。すべてのデータは衛星テレビ局を通じて送信されました。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>De Satellaview is een uitbreiding van de Super Famicom, die alleen in Japan op de markt werd gebracht. Dit systeem bood enkele extra technische mogelijkheden en een downloaddienst voor spelletjes, codes en informatie. Alle gegevens werden verzonden via een satelliet TV station.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>Satellaview to rozszerzenie Super Famicom, sprzedawane tylko w Japonii. System ten zapewniał pewne dodatkowe możliwości techniczne, a także usługę pobierania gier, kodów i informacji. Wszystkie dane były przesyłane za pośrednictwem satelitarnej stacji telewizyjnej.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>O Satellaview é uma extensão da Super Famicom, comercializada apenas no Japão. Este sistema forneceu algumas capacidades técnicas adicionais, bem como um serviço de download de jogos, códigos e informações. Todos os dados foram enviados através de uma estação de televisão por satélite.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>Satellaview - это продолжение Super Famicom, продававшееся только в Японии. Эта система предоставляла некоторые дополнительные технические возможности, а также услугу загрузки игр, кодов и информации. Все данные передавались через спутниковую телевизионную станцию.</text>
</text>


<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Kaizo Chojin Shubibinman Zero (1997)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>Raita and Azuki are two cyborgs thrown into a side-scrolling action game, with close combat, energy attacks and direct cooperation. This Satellaview version keeps the lively spirit of the Shubibinman series while changing the main duo, with a short, fast-paced progression designed for limited availability.
Fun fact: The game was only available as a download through the Satellaview service and was not sold on cartridge at release.</text>
<text lang="fr">Raita et Azuki sont deux cyborgs lancés dans un jeu d’action à défilement horizontal, entre coups rapprochés, attaques d’énergie et coopération directe. Cette version Satellaview conserve l’esprit vif de la série Shubibinman tout en changeant de duo principal, avec une progression courte, nerveuse et pensée pour une diffusion limitée.
Fun fact : Le jeu était uniquement disponible en téléchargement via le service Satellaview, et non vendu en cartouche à sa sortie.</text>
<text lang="es">Raita y Azuki son dos cyborgs lanzados a un juego de acción de desplazamiento lateral, con golpes cercanos, ataques de energía y cooperación directa. Esta versión Satellaview mantiene el espíritu ágil de la serie Shubibinman al cambiar el dúo principal, con un avance breve y rápido pensado para una disponibilidad limitada.
Dato curioso: El juego solo estaba disponible como descarga mediante Satellaview y no se vendió en cartucho al salir.</text>
<text lang="it">Raita e Azuki sono due cyborg lanciati in un gioco d’azione a scorrimento orizzontale, tra colpi ravvicinati, attacchi energetici e cooperazione diretta. Questa versione Satellaview conserva lo spirito vivace della serie Shubibinman cambiando il duo principale, con una progressione breve e rapida pensata per una disponibilità limitata.
Curiosità: Il gioco era disponibile solo come download tramite Satellaview e non fu venduto su cartuccia all’uscita.</text>
<text lang="de">Raita und Azuki sind zwei Cyborgs in einem seitlich scrollenden Actionspiel mit Nahkampfangriffen, Energieschüssen und direkter Kooperation. Diese Satellaview-Version bewahrt den lebhaften Geist der Shubibinman-Reihe, wechselt aber das Hauptduo und bietet einen kurzen, schnellen Ablauf für begrenzte Verfügbarkeit.
Interessante Tatsache: Das Spiel war nur als Download über Satellaview verfügbar und wurde zur Veröffentlichung nicht als Modul verkauft.</text>
<text lang="pt">Raita e Azuki são dois ciborgues lançados em um jogo de ação com rolagem lateral, entre golpes próximos, ataques de energia e cooperação direta. Esta versão Satellaview mantém o espírito ágil da série Shubibinman ao mudar a dupla principal, com progressão curta e rápida pensada para disponibilidade limitada.
Curiosidade: O jogo só estava disponível como download pelo serviço Satellaview e não foi vendido em cartucho no lançamento.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
