<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>Sega Corporation (株式会社セガ short for SErvice GAmes, commonly stylized SEGA) is a Japanese video game development and publishing company, as well as a manufacturer of arcade terminals and systems. In France, the company's motto is "Sega, c'est plus fort que toi!</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Sega Corporation (株式会社セガ abréviation de SErvice GAmes, couramment stylisé SEGA) est une société japonaise de développement et d'édition de jeux vidéo, ainsi qu'un fabricant de bornes et systèmes d'arcade. En France, la devise de la société est « Sega, c’est plus fort que toi ! ».</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Sega Corporation (株式会社セガ Abkürzung für SErvice GAmes, üblicherweise stilisiert SEGA) ist ein japanisches Unternehmen für die Entwicklung und Veröffentlichung von Videospielen sowie ein Hersteller von Arcade-Terminals und -Systemen. In Frankreich lautet das Motto des Unternehmens "Sega, c'est plus fort que toi!".</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Sega Corporation (株式会社セガ abreviatura de SErvice GAmes, comúnmente estilizada SEGA) es una empresa japonesa de desarrollo y publicación de videojuegos, así como fabricante de terminales y sistemas arcade. ¡En Francia, el lema de la empresa es "Sega, c'est plus fort que toi!</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Sega Corporation (株式会社セガ abbreviazione di SErvice GAmes, comunemente stilizzata SEGA) è una società giapponese di sviluppo e pubblicazione di videogiochi, nonché produttrice di terminali e sistemi arcade. In Francia, il motto dell'azienda è "Sega, c'est plus fort que toi!</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>株式会社セガ（株式会社セガ、SErvice GAmesの略、通称SEGA）は、日本のビデオゲーム開発・出版会社であり、アーケード端末・システムメーカーでもある。フランスでは「Sega, c'est plus fort que toi！」を社是としている。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>Sega Corporation (株式会社セガ kort voor SErvice GAmes, meestal gestileerd SEGA) is een Japans bedrijf dat videospelletjes ontwikkelt en uitgeeft, alsook een fabrikant van arcade-terminals en -systemen. In Frankrijk luidt het motto van het bedrijf: "Sega, c'est plus fort que toi!</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>Sega Corporation (株式会社セガ skrót od SErvice GAmes, potocznie stylizowany SEGA) to japońska firma zajmująca się tworzeniem i wydawaniem gier wideo, a także producent terminali i systemów arcade. We Francji motto firmy brzmi: "Sega, c'est plus fort que toi!</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Sega Corporation (株式会社セガ abreviatura de SErvice GAmes, comumente estilizada SEGA) é uma empresa japonesa de desenvolvimento e publicação de jogos de vídeo, bem como um fabricante de terminais e sistemas de arcade. Em França, o lema da empresa é "Sega, c'est plus fort que toi!</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>Sega Corporation (株式会社セガ сокращение от SErvice GAmes, обычно стилизация SEGA) - японская компания по разработке и изданию видеоигр, а также производитель аркадных терминалов и систем. Во Франции девиз компании звучит как "Sega, c'est plus fort que toi!</text>
</text>


<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Altered Beast (1988)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>The hero of Altered Beast is a warrior resurrected by Zeus to save his daughter from the underworld. After collecting spirit orbs, he can transform into a powerful creature, including the famous werewolf able to launch projectiles and unleash strength far beyond his human form. The game blends mythology, monsters and fantasy atmosphere in a progression strongly tied to Sega arcade action.
Fun fact: The line “Rise from your grave” spoken at the start became one of the most cult quotes in Sega history.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Le héros d’Altered Beast est un guerrier ressuscité par Zeus pour sauver sa fille des enfers. Après avoir récupéré des orbes spirituels, il peut se transformer en créature surpuissante, dont le célèbre homme-loup capable de lancer des projectiles et de déchaîner une force bien supérieure à sa forme humaine.
Fun fact : La phrase “Rise from your grave” prononcée au début du jeu est devenue l’une des répliques les plus cultes de l’histoire de Sega.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>El héroe de Altered Beast es un guerrero resucitado por Zeus para salvar a su hija del inframundo. Tras recoger orbes espirituales, puede transformarse en una criatura poderosa, incluido el famoso hombre lobo capaz de lanzar proyectiles y liberar una fuerza muy superior a su forma humana. El juego mezcla mitología, monstruos y fantasía en una progresión muy marcada por la acción arcade de Sega.
Dato curioso: La frase “Rise from your grave” pronunciada al inicio se convirtió en una de las citas más míticas de la historia de Sega.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>L’eroe di Altered Beast è un guerriero resuscitato da Zeus per salvare sua figlia dagli inferi. Dopo aver raccolto sfere spirituali, può trasformarsi in una creatura potentissima, incluso il celebre uomo lupo capace di lanciare proiettili e sprigionare una forza molto superiore alla forma umana.
Curiosità: La frase “Rise from your grave” pronunciata all’inizio è diventata una delle battute più cult della storia di Sega.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Der Held von Altered Beast ist ein von Zeus auferweckter Krieger, der dessen Tochter aus der Unterwelt retten soll. Nach dem Sammeln von Geisterkugeln kann er sich in mächtige Kreaturen verwandeln, darunter der berühmte Werwolf, der Projektile schleudert und weit stärkere Kräfte als seine menschliche Form entfesselt.
Interessante Tatsache: Der Satz “Rise from your grave” am Spielanfang wurde zu einem der kultigsten Zitate der Sega-Geschichte.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>O herói de Altered Beast é um guerreiro ressuscitado por Zeus para salvar a sua filha do submundo. Depois de recolher orbes espirituais, pode transformar-se numa criatura poderosa, incluindo o famoso homem-lobo capaz de lançar projéteis e libertar uma força muito superior à sua forma humana. O jogo mistura mitologia, monstros e fantasia numa progressão muito ligada à ação arcade da Sega.
Curiosidade: A frase “Rise from your grave” dita no início tornou-se uma das falas mais icónicas da história da Sega.</text>
</text>


</view>
</theme>
