<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>SemiCom (세미콤) is a former Korean indie studios who developing arcade-game founded in 1994.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>SemiCom (세미콤) est un ancien studio indépendant coréen de développement de jeux d'arcade fondé en 1994.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>SemiCom (세미콤) ist ein 1994 gegründetes koreanisches Indie-Studio, das Arcade-Spiele entwickelt.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>SemiCom (세미콤) es un antiguo estudio independiente coreano de desarrollo de juegos arcade fundado en 1994.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>SemiCom (세미콤) è un ex studio indie coreano che sviluppava giochi arcade fondato nel 1994.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>セミコム（세미콤）は、1994年に設立されたアーケードゲームを開発していた韓国のインディーズスタジオです。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>SemiCom (세미콤) is een voormalige Koreaanse indie-studio die arcade-games ontwikkelt, opgericht in 1994.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>SemiCom (세미콤) to byłe koreańskie studio indie, które tworzyło gry zręcznościowe założone w 1994 roku.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>SemiCom (세미콤) é um antigo estúdio indie coreano que desenvolveu um jogo arcade fundado em 1994.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>SemiCom (세미콤) - бывшая корейская инди-студия, разрабатывающая аркадные игры, основанная в 1994 году.</text>
</text>


<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Metal Saver (1994)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>Metal Saver blends action and platforming in a futuristic world filled with robots, explosions and industrial backdrops typical of Korean arcade productions from the early 1990s. The game focuses on fast progression, numerous mechanical enemies and an atmosphere strongly inspired by science-fiction anime, with characters that have a very distinctive style.
Fun fact: Metal Saver is one of the few Korean arcade games from that period to have circulated outside Korea in several Western arcades.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Metal Saver mélange action et plateformes dans un univers futuriste rempli de robots, d’explosions et de décors industriels typiques des productions arcade coréennes du début des années 90. Le jeu mise sur une progression rapide, des ennemis mécaniques nombreux et une ambiance fortement inspirée des animes de science-fiction, avec des personnages au style très marqué.
Fun fact : Metal Saver fait partie des rares jeux d’arcade coréens de cette période à avoir circulé hors de Corée dans plusieurs salles occidentales.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Metal Saver mezcla acción y plataformas en un universo futurista lleno de robots, explosiones y escenarios industriales típicos de las producciones arcade coreanas de principios de los años 90. El juego apuesta por una progresión rápida, muchos enemigos mecánicos y una atmósfera muy inspirada en el anime de ciencia ficción, con personajes de estilo muy marcado.
Dato curioso: Metal Saver es uno de los pocos juegos arcade coreanos de esa época que circularon fuera de Corea en varias salas occidentales.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Metal Saver mescola azione e piattaforme in un universo futuristico pieno di robot, esplosioni e scenari industriali tipici delle produzioni arcade coreane dei primi anni 90. Il gioco punta su una progressione rapida, molti nemici meccanici e un’atmosfera fortemente ispirata agli anime di fantascienza, con personaggi dallo stile molto marcato.
Curiosità: Metal Saver è tra i pochi giochi arcade coreani di quel periodo ad aver circolato fuori dalla Corea in diverse sale occidentali.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Metal Saver verbindet Action und Plattformspiel in einer futuristischen Welt voller Roboter, Explosionen und industrieller Kulissen, wie sie für koreanische Arcade-Produktionen der frühen 1990er typisch waren. Das Spiel setzt auf schnelles Vorankommen, zahlreiche mechanische Gegner und eine stark von Science-Fiction-Anime geprägte Atmosphäre mit sehr markanten Figuren.
Interessante Tatsache: Metal Saver gehört zu den wenigen koreanischen Arcade-Spielen dieser Zeit, die auch außerhalb Koreas in mehreren westlichen Spielhallen liefen.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Metal Saver mistura ação e plataformas num universo futurista cheio de robôs, explosões e cenários industriais típicos das produções arcade coreanas do início dos anos 90. O jogo aposta numa progressão rápida, muitos inimigos mecânicos e uma atmosfera fortemente inspirada em animes de ficção científica, com personagens de estilo muito marcado.
Curiosidade: Metal Saver está entre os poucos jogos arcade coreanos desse período que circularam fora da Coreia em várias salas ocidentais.</text>
</text>


</view>
</theme>
