<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>The SG-1000 (エスジー・セン), also known as the Sega Game 1000, is designed and marketed by Japanese manufacturer Sega Enterprises, Ltd. The console marks Sega's entry into home video gaming and is a foundation for the more successful Master System. It was released on the same day as Nintendo's Famicom in Japan.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>La SG-1000 (エスジー・セン), également connue sous le nom Sega Game 1000, marque l'entrée de Sega dans le jeu vidéo à domicile et constitue une base pour les petites soeurs à venir, la Mark III et la plus fructueuse Master System. Elle sort le même jour que la Famicom de Nintendo au Japon. Malgré des débuts prometteurs, elle connait une performance commerciale décevante mais contribue à forger une communauté de passionnés autour d'elle et de Sega.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Die SG-1000 (エスジー・セン), auch bekannt als Sega Game 1000, wird von dem japanischen Hersteller Sega Enterprises, Ltd. entwickelt und vermarktet. Die Konsole markiert Segas Einstieg in das Heimvideospiel und bildet die Grundlage für das erfolgreichere Master System. Sie wird am selben Tag wie Nintendos Famicom in Japan veröffentlicht.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>La SG-1000 (エスジー・セン), también conocida como Sega Game 1000, es una consola diseñada y comercializada por el fabricante japonés Sega Enterprises, Ltd. (Sega). La consola marca la entrada de Sega en los videojuegos domésticos y es la base de la más exitosa Master System. Salió a la venta el mismo día que la Famicom de Nintendo en Japón.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>La console SG-1000 (エスジー・セン), nota anche come Sega Game 1000, è stata progettata e commercializzata dal produttore giapponese Sega Enterprises, Ltd. La console segna l'ingresso di Sega nel settore dei videogiochi domestici e costituisce la base per il Master System, di maggior successo. È uscita in Giappone lo stesso giorno del Famicom di Nintendo.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>SG-1000（エスジー・セン）、別名セガゲーム1000は、日本のメーカーである株式会社セガ・エンタープライゼスが設計し、販売したものです。このゲーム機はセガの家庭用ゲーム機への参入を示すものであり、より成功したマスターシステムの基礎となるものである。日本では任天堂のファミコンと同日に発売された。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>De SG-1000 (エスジー・セン), ook bekend als de Sega Game 1000, is ontworpen en op de markt gebracht door de Japanse fabrikant Sega Enterprises, Ltd. De console markeert Sega's intrede in home video gaming en is een basis voor het meer succesvolle Master System. Het werd uitgebracht op dezelfde dag als Nintendo's Famicom in Japan.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>SG-1000 (エスジー・セン), znany również jako Sega Game 1000, został zaprojektowany i wprowadzony na rynek przez japońskiego producenta Sega Enterprises, Ltd. Konsola zaznacza wejście Sega w domowe gry wideo i jest podstawą dla bardziej udanego Master System. Został wydany w tym samym dniu, co Nintendo's Famicom w Japonii.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>O SG-1000 (エスジー・セン), também conhecido como Sega Game 1000, é concebido e comercializado pelo fabricante japonês Sega Enterprises, Ltd. A consola marca a entrada da Sega em jogos de vídeo em casa e é uma base para o sistema Master mais bem sucedido. Foi lançada no mesmo dia que a Famicom da Nintendo no Japão.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>SG-1000 (エスジー・セン), также известная как Sega Game 1000, разработана и продается японским производителем Sega Enterprises, Ltd. Консоль была разработана и продается японской компанией Sega. Консоль знаменует собой выход Sega на рынок домашних видеоигр и является основой для более успешной Master System. Она была выпущена в тот же день, что и Nintendo Famicom в Японии.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
