<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>MSU-1 Game Boy games are hacks or modifications of Game Boy games that use the MSU-1 chip. This chip makes it possible to add high-quality audio tracks. This can give games a new lease of life with enhanced sounds, often made by passionate retro-gaming fans.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Les jeux MSU-1 sur Game Boy sont des hacks ou des modifications de jeux Game Boy qui utilisent la puce MSU-1. Cette puce permet d'ajouter des pistes audio de haute qualité. Cela peut donner aux jeux une nouvelle vie avec des sons améliorés, souvent réalisés par des fans passionnés de rétro-gaming.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Los juegos MSU-1 de Game Boy son hacks o modificaciones de juegos de Game Boy que utilizan el chip MSU-1. Este chip permite añadir pistas de audio de alta calidad. Esto puede dar nueva vida a los juegos con sonidos mejorados, a menudo creados por apasionados aficionados al retro-gaming.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>I giochi MSU-1 per Game Boy sono hack o modifiche di giochi Game Boy che utilizzano il chip MSU-1. Questo chip permette di aggiungere tracce audio di alta qualità. Può dare nuova vita ai giochi con suoni migliorati, spesso realizzati da appassionati di retro-gaming.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>MSU-1-Game-Boy-Spiele sind Hacks oder Modifikationen von Game-Boy-Spielen, die den MSU-1-Chip nutzen. Dieser Chip ermöglicht das Hinzufügen hochwertiger Audiospuren. So können Spiele mit verbesserten Klängen neues Leben erhalten, oft erstellt von leidenschaftlichen Retro-Gaming-Fans.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Os jogos MSU-1 para Game Boy são hacks ou modificações de jogos Game Boy que utilizam o chip MSU-1. Este chip permite adicionar faixas de áudio de alta qualidade. Isso pode dar nova vida aos jogos com sons melhorados, muitas vezes criados por fãs apaixonados de retro-gaming.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Pokémon Rouge et Bleu (1996)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>Dragonite is the final evolution of Dratini in Pokémon Red and Blue, a powerful creature with a dragon design that contrasts with its surprisingly gentle appearance. Rare and difficult to obtain, it represents the end of a long and demanding progression through Kanto, quickly becoming one of the most memorable Pokémon of the first generation.
Fun fact: Dragonite is obtained only at level 55, making it one of the latest evolutions in the first generation.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Dracolosse est l’évolution finale de Minidraco dans Pokémon Rouge et Bleu, une créature puissante au design de dragon qui contraste avec son apparence étonnamment douce. Rare et difficile à obtenir, il incarne l’aboutissement d’une progression longue et exigeante au sein de l’univers de Kanto, devenant rapidement l’un des Pokémon les plus marquants de la première génération.
Fun fact : Dracolosse s’obtient seulement au niveau 55, ce qui en fait l’une des évolutions les plus tardives de la première génération.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Dragonite es la evolución final de Dratini en Pokémon Rojo y Azul, una criatura poderosa con diseño de dragón que contrasta con su aspecto sorprendentemente amable. Raro y difícil de obtener, representa el final de una progresión larga y exigente por Kanto, convirtiéndose pronto en uno de los Pokémon más recordados de la primera generación.
Dato curioso: Dragonite se obtiene solo en el nivel 55, una de las evoluciones más tardías de la primera generación.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Dragonite è l’evoluzione finale di Dratini in Pokémon Rosso e Blu, una creatura potente dal design draconico che contrasta con il suo aspetto sorprendentemente dolce. Raro e difficile da ottenere, rappresenta il culmine di una progressione lunga e impegnativa a Kanto, diventando presto uno dei Pokémon più memorabili della prima generazione.
Curiosità: Dragonite si ottiene solo al livello 55, una delle evoluzioni più tardive della prima generazione.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Dragoran ist die letzte Entwicklung von Dratini in Pokémon Rot und Blau, ein mächtiges Wesen mit Drachendesign, das zu seinem überraschend sanften Aussehen kontrastiert. Selten und schwer zu erhalten, steht es für den Abschluss eines langen und anspruchsvollen Weges durch Kanto und wurde schnell zu einem der einprägsamsten Pokémon der ersten Generation.
Interessante Tatsache: Dragoran entwickelt sich erst auf Level 55 und gehört damit zu den spätesten Entwicklungen der ersten Generation.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Dragonite é a evolução final de Dratini em Pokémon Red e Blue, uma criatura poderosa com visual de dragão que contrasta com a sua aparência surpreendentemente dócil. Raro e difícil de obter, representa o fim de uma progressão longa e exigente por Kanto, tornando-se rapidamente um dos Pokémon mais marcantes da primeira geração.
Curiosidade: Dragonite só é obtido no nível 55, uma das evoluções mais tardias da primeira geração.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
