<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>Shmups (shoot 'em up) are action games in which the player controls a ship or a character who must shoot at waves of enemies while avoiding their projectiles. Very popular in the 80s and 90s, they come in several sub-genres, such as bullet hell and run and gun. Nervous gameplay and high difficulty make these games demanding but highly addictive.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Les shmups (shoot 'em up) sont des jeux d'action où le joueur contrôle un vaisseau ou un personnage qui doit tirer sur des vagues d’ennemis tout en évitant leurs projectiles. Très populaires dans les années 80 et 90, ils se déclinent en plusieurs sous-genres comme le bullet hell ou le run and gun. Leur gameplay nerveux et leur difficulté élevée en font des jeux exigeants mais très addictifs.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Los shmups (shoot 'em up) son juegos de acción en los que el jugador controla una nave o un personaje que debe disparar a oleadas de enemigos mientras esquiva sus proyectiles. Muy populares en los años 80 y 90, se dividen en varios subgéneros, como bullet hell y run and gun. Su ritmo nervioso y su alta dificultad los hacen exigentes pero muy adictivos.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Gli shmups (shoot 'em up) sono giochi d'azione in cui il giocatore controlla una nave o un personaggio che deve sparare a ondate di nemici evitando i loro proiettili. Molto popolari negli anni 80 e 90, comprendono vari sottogeneri, come bullet hell e run and gun. Il gameplay frenetico e l'elevata difficoltà li rendono impegnativi ma molto coinvolgenti.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Shmups (Shoot 'em up) sind Actionspiele, in denen der Spieler ein Schiff oder eine Figur steuert, die auf Gegnerwellen schießen und deren Projektilen ausweichen muss. In den 80er und 90er Jahren sehr beliebt, umfassen sie mehrere Untergenres wie Bullet Hell und Run and Gun. Ihr nervöses Gameplay und der hohe Schwierigkeitsgrad machen sie anspruchsvoll, aber sehr fesselnd.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Shmups (shoot 'em up) são jogos de ação em que o jogador controla uma nave ou personagem que deve atirar em ondas de inimigos enquanto desvia de seus projéteis. Muito populares nos anos 80 e 90, incluem vários subgêneros, como bullet hell e run and gun. O ritmo intenso e a alta dificuldade tornam esses jogos exigentes, mas muito viciantes.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Raiden (Arcade, 1990)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>Raiden's ship is a futuristic fighter built to repel a massive alien invasion. Agile and heavily armed, it crosses hostile zones under a constant storm of enemy fire. Its evolving arsenal, mixing raw power and precision, makes it a formidable war machine, a shoot'em up reference and a symbol of control and reflexes.
Fun fact: The name “Raiden” refers to the Japanese god of thunder, directly linked to the destructive power of the ship.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Le vaisseau de Raiden est un chasseur futuriste conçu pour repousser une invasion extraterrestre massive. Agile et lourdement armé, il traverse des zones hostiles sous un déluge constant de tirs ennemis. Son arsenal évolutif, mêlant puissance brute et précision, en fait une machine de guerre redoutable, devenue une référence du shoot’em up et un symbole de maîtrise et de réflexes.
Fun fact : Le nom “Raiden” fait référence au dieu japonais du tonnerre, en lien direct avec la puissance destructrice du vaisseau.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>La nave de Raiden es un caza futurista diseñado para repeler una invasión alienígena masiva. Ágil y fuertemente armada, cruza zonas hostiles bajo una lluvia constante de disparos enemigos. Su arsenal evolutivo, que mezcla potencia bruta y precisión, la convierte en una máquina de guerra temible, referencia del shoot'em up y símbolo de control y reflejos.
Dato curioso: El nombre “Raiden” hace referencia al dios japonés del trueno, ligado directamente al poder destructivo de la nave.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>La nave di Raiden è un caccia futuristico progettato per respingere una massiccia invasione aliena. Agile e pesantemente armata, attraversa zone ostili sotto una pioggia costante di colpi nemici. Il suo arsenale evolutivo, tra potenza bruta e precisione, la rende una macchina da guerra temibile, riferimento dello shoot'em up e simbolo di controllo e riflessi.
Curiosità: Il nome “Raiden” fa riferimento al dio giapponese del tuono, legato direttamente alla potenza distruttiva della nave.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Raidens Schiff ist ein futuristischer Jäger, gebaut zur Abwehr einer massiven Alien-Invasion. Wendig und schwer bewaffnet durchquert es feindliche Zonen unter einem ständigen Hagel gegnerischer Schüsse. Sein wachsendes Arsenal, zwischen roher Kraft und Präzision, macht es zu einer gefürchteten Kriegsmaschine, einem Shoot'em-up-Vorbild und Symbol für Kontrolle und Reflexe.
Interessante Tatsache: Der Name “Raiden” verweist auf den japanischen Donnergott und passt direkt zur zerstörerischen Kraft des Schiffs.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>A nave de Raiden é um caça futurista criado para repelir uma invasão alienígena massiva. Ágil e fortemente armada, cruza zonas hostis sob uma chuva constante de tiros inimigos. Seu arsenal evolutivo, entre força bruta e precisão, faz dela uma máquina de guerra temível, referência do shoot'em up e símbolo de controle e reflexos.
Curiosidade: O nome “Raiden” faz referência ao deus japonês do trovão, ligado diretamente ao poder destrutivo da nave.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
