<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>The Simpsons games are a series of video games inspired by the famous animated series. Since the 90s, they have explored various genres, including beat'em up (The Simpsons Arcade Game), racing (Road Rage) and action-adventure (Hit and Run). Appreciated for their true-to-series humor, they immerse players in the wacky world of Springfield. Some titles, like Hit and Run, have become cult hits with fans.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Les jeux Simpsons sont une série de jeux vidéo inspirés de la célèbre série animée. Depuis les années 90, ils explorent divers genres, comme le beat'em up (The Simpsons Arcade Game), la course (Road Rage) ou l’action-aventure (Hit and Run). Appréciés pour leur humour fidèle à la série, ils plongent les joueurs dans l’univers déjanté de Springfield. Certains titres, comme Hit and Run, sont devenus cultes auprès des fans.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Los juegos de The Simpsons son una serie de videojuegos inspirados en la famosa serie animada. Desde los años 90, han explorado varios géneros, como el beat'em up (The Simpsons Arcade Game), las carreras (Road Rage) y la acción-aventura (Hit and Run). Apreciados por su humor fiel a la serie, sumergen a los jugadores en el disparatado mundo de Springfield. Algunos títulos, como Hit and Run, se han vuelto de culto entre los fans.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>I giochi dei Simpsons sono una serie di videogiochi ispirati alla celebre serie animata. Dagli anni 90 hanno esplorato vari generi, tra cui beat'em up (The Simpsons Arcade Game), corse (Road Rage) e azione-avventura (Hit and Run). Apprezzati per l'umorismo fedele alla serie, immergono i giocatori nel folle mondo di Springfield. Alcuni titoli, come Hit and Run, sono diventati cult per i fan.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Die Simpsons-Spiele sind eine Reihe von Videospielen, die von der berühmten Zeichentrickserie inspiriert wurden. Seit den 90er Jahren erkunden sie verschiedene Genres, darunter Beat'em up (The Simpsons Arcade Game), Rennspiele (Road Rage) und Action-Adventure (Hit and Run). Wegen ihres seriennahen Humors beliebt, führen sie die Spieler in die verrückte Welt von Springfield. Einige Titel, wie Hit and Run, wurden bei Fans zu Kultspielen.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Os jogos dos Simpsons são uma série de videogames inspirados na famosa série animada. Desde os anos 90, exploram vários gêneros, como beat'em up (The Simpsons Arcade Game), corrida (Road Rage) e ação-aventura (Hit and Run). Apreciados pelo humor fiel à série, mergulham os jogadores no mundo maluco de Springfield. Alguns títulos, como Hit and Run, tornaram-se cult entre os fãs.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;The Simpsons: Bart vs. the Space Mutants (NES, 1991)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>Bart Simpson is a restless kid always ready to challenge authority, skateboard in hand and a mischievous grin on his face. In this episode, he tries to stop an alien invasion with nerve and observation. His rebellious attitude, mixed with real cleverness, makes him an unlikely but iconic hero in The Simpsons universe.
Fun fact: In the 90s, Bart and his skateboard helped popularize the image of the rebellious skater for an entire generation.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Bart Simpson est un enfant turbulent toujours prêt à défier l’autorité, skate à la main et sourire malicieux aux lèvres. Dans cet épisode, il tente de déjouer une invasion extraterrestre en comptant sur son audace et son sens de l’observation. Son attitude rebelle, mêlée à une certaine ingéniosité, en fait un héros improbable mais emblématique de l’univers des Simpsons.
Fun fact : Dans les années 90, Bart et son skate ont contribué à populariser l’image du skater rebelle auprès d’une génération entière.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Bart Simpson es un niño inquieto siempre dispuesto a desafiar la autoridad, con el skate en la mano y una sonrisa traviesa. En este episodio intenta frustrar una invasión alienígena usando audacia y observación. Su actitud rebelde, unida a cierta astucia, lo convierte en un héroe improbable pero emblemático del universo de Los Simpson.
Dato curioso: En los años 90, Bart y su skate ayudaron a popularizar la imagen del skater rebelde para toda una generación.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Bart Simpson è un ragazzo turbolento sempre pronto a sfidare l'autorità, con lo skate in mano e un sorriso malizioso. In questo episodio cerca di sventare un'invasione aliena contando su audacia e spirito di osservazione. Il suo atteggiamento ribelle, unito a una certa astuzia, lo rende un eroe improbabile ma emblematico dell'universo dei Simpsons.
Curiosità: Negli anni 90, Bart e il suo skate hanno contribuito a diffondere l'immagine dello skater ribelle per un'intera generazione.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Bart Simpson ist ein unruhiger Junge, der stets bereit ist, Autorität herauszufordern, mit Skateboard in der Hand und frechem Grinsen. In diesem Spiel versucht er, eine Alien-Invasion mit Mut und Beobachtungsgabe zu stoppen. Seine rebellische Haltung und sein Einfallsreichtum machen ihn zu einem unwahrscheinlichen, aber prägenden Helden der Simpsons-Welt.
Interessante Tatsache: In den 90er Jahren machten Bart und sein Skateboard das Bild des rebellischen Skaters für eine ganze Generation populär.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Bart Simpson é um garoto agitado sempre pronto para desafiar a autoridade, com o skate na mão e um sorriso malicioso. Neste episódio, ele tenta impedir uma invasão alienígena usando ousadia e observação. Sua atitude rebelde, somada a certa esperteza, faz dele um herói improvável, mas emblemático do universo dos Simpsons.
Curiosidade: Nos anos 90, Bart e seu skate ajudaram a popularizar a imagem do skatista rebelde para uma geração inteira.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
