<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>Hypseus Singe is a fork of Matt Ownby's Daphne. It's a program to play laserdisc arcade games on a PC, Mac or Raspberry Pi. This version includes Singe support for Fan Made and American Laser Games.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Hypseus Singe est un fork de Daphne de Matt Ownby. C'est un programme qui permet de jouer à des jeux d'arcade laserdisc sur un PC, un Mac ou un Raspberry Pi. Cette version inclut le support Singe pour les jeux Fan Made et American Laser Games.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Hypseus Singe es un fork de Daphne de Matt Ownby. Es un programa para jugar a juegos arcade de laserdisc en un PC, Mac o Raspberry Pi. Esta versión incluye soporte Singe para Fan Made y American Laser Games.</text>
</text>


<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Hypseus Singe è un fork di Daphne di Matt Ownby. È un programma che permette di giocare ai giochi arcade laserdisc su PC, Mac o Raspberry Pi. Questa versione include il supporto Singe per giochi Fan Made e American Laser Games.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Hypseus Singe ist ein Fork von Matt Ownbys Daphne. Es ist ein Programm, mit dem Laserdisc-Arcade-Spiele auf PC, Mac oder Raspberry Pi gespielt werden können. Diese Version enthält Singe-Unterstützung für Fan Made und American Laser Games.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Hypseus Singe é um fork do Daphne de Matt Ownby. É um programa que permite jogar jogos arcade em laserdisc no PC, Mac ou Raspberry Pi. Esta versão inclui suporte Singe para jogos Fan Made e American Laser Games.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Who Shot Johnny Rock? (1994)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>This woman in the red suit embodies the game’s provocative, theatrical style, with a strong presence inspired by classic film noir figures. The figurine highlights her elegant look and confident attitude, matching the offbeat tone of Who Shot Johnny Rock?, an FMV title built around real actors and exaggerated staging typical of 1990s interactive productions.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Cette silhouette féminine au tailleur rouge incarne parfaitement l’esthétique provocante et théâtrale du jeu, avec une présence marquée et un style directement inspiré des figures emblématiques du film noir. La figurine met en valeur son allure élégante et son attitude assurée, fidèle à l’ambiance décalée du titre, basé sur des séquences FMV avec acteurs réels.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Esta silueta femenina con traje rojo encarna la estética provocadora y teatral del juego, con una presencia marcada y un estilo inspirado en figuras clásicas del cine negro. La figura destaca su elegancia y actitud segura, fiel al tono excéntrico de Who Shot Johnny Rock?, un título FMV basado en secuencias con actores reales.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Questa figura femminile in tailleur rosso incarna l’estetica provocante e teatrale del gioco, con una presenza forte e uno stile ispirato alle figure classiche del noir. La statuetta valorizza il suo aspetto elegante e l’atteggiamento sicuro, fedele al tono eccentrico di Who Shot Johnny Rock?, titolo FMV basato su scene con attori reali.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Diese weibliche Silhouette im roten Kostüm verkörpert die provokante, theatrale Ästhetik des Spiels, mit starker Präsenz und einem Stil, der an klassische Film-noir-Figuren erinnert. Die Figur betont ihr elegantes Auftreten und ihre selbstsichere Haltung, passend zum schrägen Ton von Who Shot Johnny Rock?, einem FMV-Spiel mit echten Schauspielern.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Esta silhueta feminina de fato vermelho encarna a estética provocante e teatral do jogo, com presença marcante e um estilo inspirado nas figuras clássicas do film noir. A figura destaca sua elegância e atitude confiante, fiel ao tom excêntrico de Who Shot Johnny Rock?, um título FMV baseado em cenas com atores reais.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
