<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>MSU-1 Super Nintendo games are modified versions of SNES titles using the MSU-1 chip. This virtual chip allows the addition of high-quality audio tracks, offering enhanced sound experiences and giving classic games a new atmosphere created by dedicated retro-gaming fans.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Les jeux MSU-1 sur Super Nintendo sont des versions modifiées de jeux SNES utilisant la puce MSU-1. Cette puce virtuelle permet d’ajouter des pistes audio de haute qualité et d’offrir une expérience sonore enrichie, redonnant une nouvelle ambiance aux jeux classiques.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Los juegos MSU-1 de Super Nintendo son versiones modificadas de títulos SNES que utilizan el chip MSU-1. Este chip virtual permite añadir pistas de audio de alta calidad y ofrecer una experiencia sonora mejorada, dando nueva vida a los juegos clásicos.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>I giochi MSU-1 per Super Nintendo sono versioni modificate di titoli SNES che utilizzano il chip MSU-1. Questo chip virtuale permette di aggiungere tracce audio di alta qualità, offrendo un’esperienza sonora migliorata ai giochi classici.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>MSU-1-Spiele für das Super Nintendo sind modifizierte SNES-Titel, die den MSU-1-Chip nutzen. Dieser virtuelle Chip ermöglicht hochwertige Audiotracks und bietet eine verbesserte Klangkulisse für klassische Spiele.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Os jogos MSU-1 para Super Nintendo são versões modificadas de títulos SNES que utilizam o chip MSU-1. Este chip virtual permite adicionar faixas de áudio de alta qualidade, oferecendo uma experiência sonora melhorada aos jogos clássicos.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Demon’s Crest (1994)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>Firebrand is a winged demon able to fly, breathe fire and transform into stronger forms. Driven by the conquest of the six elemental crests, he explores a dark world filled with danger and hidden paths. His adventure combines demanding action, exploration and progression within a gothic setting built around discovery and power upgrades.
Fun fact: Demon’s Crest is the third game in the Gargoyle’s Quest spin-off series from Ghosts ’n Goblins.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Firebrand est un démon ailé capable de voler, cracher du feu et se transformer en formes redoutables. Obsédé par la conquête des six pierres élémentaires, il parcourt un monde sombre rempli de dangers et de passages cachés. Son aventure mêle action exigeante, exploration et progression dans un univers gothique structuré autour des transformations.
Fun fact : Demon’s Crest est le troisième épisode de la série dérivée Gargoyle’s Quest, issue de Ghosts ’n Goblins.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Firebrand es un demonio alado capaz de volar, escupir fuego y transformarse en formas más poderosas. Obsesionado con conquistar los seis emblemas elementales, recorre un mundo oscuro lleno de peligros y caminos ocultos. Su aventura combina acción exigente, exploración y progresión en un entorno gótico centrado en las transformaciones.
Dato curioso: Demon’s Crest es el tercer juego de la serie derivada Gargoyle’s Quest de Ghosts ’n Goblins.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Firebrand è un demone alato capace di volare, sputare fuoco e trasformarsi in forme più potenti. Ossessionato dalla conquista dei sei stemmi elementali, attraversa un mondo oscuro pieno di pericoli e percorsi nascosti. La sua avventura unisce azione impegnativa, esplorazione e progressione in un universo gotico basato sulle trasformazioni.
Curiosità: Demon’s Crest è il terzo episodio della serie Gargoyle’s Quest derivata da Ghosts ’n Goblins.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Firebrand ist ein geflügelter Dämon, der fliegen, Feuer speien und sich verwandeln kann. Getrieben von der Suche nach den sechs elementaren Wappen erkundet er eine dunkle Welt voller Gefahren und geheimer Wege. Sein Abenteuer verbindet anspruchsvolle Action, Erkundung und Fortschritt in einem gotischen Umfeld mit Fokus auf Verwandlungen.
Interessante Tatsache: Demon’s Crest ist der dritte Teil der Gargoyle’s-Quest-Reihe aus Ghosts ’n Goblins.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Firebrand é um demónio alado capaz de voar, cuspir fogo e transformar-se em formas mais poderosas. Obcecado pela conquista dos seis emblemas elementares, percorre um mundo sombrio cheio de perigos e caminhos ocultos. A sua aventura combina ação exigente, exploração e progressão num universo gótico centrado nas transformações.
Curiosidade: Demon’s Crest é o terceiro jogo da série Gargoyle’s Quest derivada de Ghosts ’n Goblins.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>