<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>Sonic the Hedgehog is a series of platform games created by Sega, centered on Sonic, a super-fast hedgehog, who battles the evil Dr. Robotnik. The gameplay is characterized by fast-paced levels, loops and a strong emphasis on speed. With allies like Tails and Knuckles, the series has evolved over the years while remaining true to its dynamic spirit. Sonic is one of the most iconic franchises in video game history.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Sonic the Hedgehog est une série de jeux de plateforme créée par Sega, centrée sur Sonic, un hérisson super rapide, qui lutte contre le maléfique Dr. Robotnik. Le gameplay se distingue par des niveaux rapides, des loops et une forte emphasis sur la vitesse. Avec des alliés comme Tails et Knuckles, la série a évolué au fil des ans tout en restant fidèle à son esprit dynamique. Sonic est l'une des franchises les plus emblématiques de l'histoire du jeu vidéo.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Sonic the Hedgehog es una serie de juegos de plataformas creada por Sega, centrada en Sonic, un erizo superrápido que lucha contra el malvado Dr. Robotnik. Su jugabilidad se caracteriza por niveles veloces, bucles y un fuerte énfasis en la velocidad. Con aliados como Tails y Knuckles, la serie ha evolucionado con los años sin perder su espíritu dinámico. Sonic es una de las franquicias más icónicas de la historia del videojuego.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Sonic the Hedgehog è una serie di giochi platform creata da Sega, incentrata su Sonic, un riccio velocissimo che combatte il malvagio Dr. Robotnik. Il gameplay è caratterizzato da livelli rapidi, loop e una forte enfasi sulla velocità. Con alleati come Tails e Knuckles, la serie si è evoluta negli anni restando fedele al suo spirito dinamico. Sonic è una delle serie più iconiche della storia dei videogiochi.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Sonic the Hedgehog ist eine von Sega entwickelte Plattformspielreihe rund um Sonic, einen superschnellen Igel, der gegen den bösen Dr. Robotnik kämpft. Das Gameplay ist geprägt von schnellen Leveln, Loopings und einem starken Fokus auf Geschwindigkeit. Mit Verbündeten wie Tails und Knuckles entwickelte sich die Reihe weiter, blieb ihrem dynamischen Geist aber treu. Sonic zählt zu den bekanntesten Marken der Videospielgeschichte.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Sonic the Hedgehog é uma série de jogos de plataforma criada pela Sega, centrada em Sonic, um ouriço super-rápido que enfrenta o maligno Dr. Robotnik. A jogabilidade é marcada por fases velozes, loops e uma forte ênfase na velocidade. Com aliados como Tails e Knuckles, a série evoluiu ao longo dos anos mantendo seu espírito dinâmico. Sonic é uma das franquias mais icônicas da história dos videogames.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Sonic the Hedgehog (Mega Drive, 1991)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>Sonic is a supersonic hedgehog able to run at extreme speed, embodying the energy and flow of the gameplay. Between speed, precision and exploration, Sonic symbolizes a new approach to platform games built on rhythm and momentum.
Fun fact: Green Hill Zone was designed to show Sonic's speed immediately, becoming one of the most recognizable levels in video game history.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Sonic est un hérisson supersonique capable de courir à des vitesses extrêmes, incarnant l’énergie et la fluidité du gameplay. Entre vitesse, précision et exploration, Sonic symbolise une nouvelle approche du jeu de plateforme marquée par le rythme et l’élan.
Fun fact : Green Hill Zone a été conçue pour illustrer immédiatement la vitesse de Sonic, devenant l’un des niveaux les plus reconnaissables de toute l’histoire du jeu vidéo.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Sonic es un erizo supersónico capaz de correr a velocidades extremas, encarnando la energía y la fluidez del gameplay. Entre velocidad, precisión y exploración, Sonic simboliza una nueva forma de entender el juego de plataformas basada en ritmo e impulso.
Dato curioso: Green Hill Zone fue diseñada para mostrar de inmediato la velocidad de Sonic, convirtiéndose en uno de los niveles más reconocibles de la historia del videojuego.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Sonic è un riccio supersonico capace di correre a velocità estreme, incarnando l'energia e la fluidità del gameplay. Tra velocità, precisione ed esplorazione, Sonic rappresenta un nuovo approccio al platform basato su ritmo e slancio.
Curiosità: Green Hill Zone fu progettata per mostrare subito la velocità di Sonic, diventando uno dei livelli più riconoscibili della storia dei videogiochi.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Sonic ist ein überschallschneller Igel, der mit extremem Tempo rennt und die Energie sowie den Fluss des Gameplays verkörpert. Zwischen Geschwindigkeit, Präzision und Erkundung steht Sonic für einen neuen Plattformspiel-Ansatz voller Rhythmus und Schwung.
Interessante Tatsache: Green Hill Zone wurde entworfen, um Sonics Geschwindigkeit sofort zu zeigen, und wurde zu einem der bekanntesten Level der Videospielgeschichte.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Sonic é um ouriço supersônico capaz de correr a velocidades extremas, representando a energia e a fluidez da jogabilidade. Entre velocidade, precisão e exploração, Sonic simboliza uma nova abordagem dos jogos de plataforma baseada em ritmo e impulso.
Curiosidade: Green Hill Zone foi criada para mostrar imediatamente a velocidade de Sonic, tornando-se uma das fases mais reconhecíveis da história dos videogames.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
