<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>Spectravideo International Limited (SVI) was an American computer manufacturer and software company.  The company produced video games and other software for the VIC-20, the Atari 2600 and its CompuMate peripheral. Some of their own computers were compatible with Microsoft's MSX or IBM's PC.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Spectravideo International Limited (SVI) était un fabricant d'ordinateurs et un éditeur de logiciels américain.  La société a produit des jeux vidéo et d'autres logiciels pour le VIC-20, l'Atari 2600 et son périphérique CompuMate. Certains de leurs propres ordinateurs étaient compatibles avec le MSX de Microsoft ou le PC d'IBM.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Spectravideo International Limited (SVI) war ein US-amerikanischer Computerhersteller und Softwareentwickler.  Das Unternehmen produzierte Videospiele und andere Software für den VIC-20, den Atari 2600 und dessen Peripheriegerät CompuMate. Einige ihrer eigenen Computer waren mit dem MSX von Microsoft oder dem PC von IBM kompatibel.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Spectravideo International Limited (SVI) fue una empresa estadounidense fabricante de ordenadores y software.  La empresa producía videojuegos y otros programas para el VIC-20, el Atari 2600 y su periférico CompuMate. Algunos de sus ordenadores eran compatibles con Microsoft MSX o IBM PC.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Spectravideo International Limited (SVI) era un'azienda americana produttrice di computer e software.  L'azienda produceva videogiochi e altri software per il VIC-20, l'Atari 2600 e la sua periferica CompuMate. Alcuni dei suoi computer erano compatibili con il Microsoft MSX o l'IBM PC.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>Spectravideo International Limited（SVI）は、アメリカのコンピュータメーカー、ソフトウェア会社である。 同社はVIC-20やAtari2600、その周辺機器であるCompuMate向けにビデオゲームやその他のソフトウェアを製造していました。自社のコンピュータの中には、マイクロソフト社のMSXやIBM PCと互換性のあるものもあった。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>Spectravideo International Limited (SVI) was een Amerikaanse computerfabrikant en softwarebedrijf.  Het bedrijf produceerde videospelletjes en andere software voor de VIC-20, de Atari 2600 en zijn CompuMate-randapparaat. Sommige van hun eigen computers waren compatibel met de Microsoft MSX of IBM PC.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>Spectravideo International Limited (SVI) był amerykańskim producentem komputerów i firmą produkującą oprogramowanie.  Firma produkowała gry wideo i inne oprogramowanie dla VIC-20, Atari 2600 i jego peryferii CompuMate. Niektóre z ich własnych komputerów były kompatybilne z Microsoft MSX lub IBM PC.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Spectravideo International Limited (SVI) era um fabricante americano de computadores e uma empresa de software.  A empresa produzia jogos de vídeo e outro software para o VIC-20, o Atari 2600 e o seu periférico CompuMate. Alguns dos seus próprios computadores eram compatíveis com o Microsoft MSX ou IBM PC.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>Spectravideo International Limited (SVI) - американский производитель компьютеров и программного обеспечения.  Компания выпускала видеоигры и другое программное обеспечение для VIC-20, Atari 2600 и периферийного устройства CompuMate. Некоторые из их собственных компьютеров были совместимы с Microsoft MSX или IBM PC.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Boulder Dash (1984)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>Boulder Dash is an action puzzle game where Rockford digs through caves to collect diamonds while avoiding falling rocks and enemies. Each stage relies on gravity, timing and anticipation, forcing the player to plan every move without getting trapped. Its simple but demanding design made it a classic of 1980s home computers.
Fun fact: Created by Peter Liepa and Chris Gray, Boulder Dash gave its hero Rockford a lasting identity across many ports, sequels and later remakes.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Boulder Dash est un jeu de réflexion et d’action où Rockford creuse des galeries pour collecter des diamants tout en évitant chutes de rochers et ennemis. Chaque niveau repose sur la gravité, le timing et l’anticipation, obligeant à planifier chaque déplacement sans se piéger. Son gameplay simple mais exigeant en fait un classique des micro-ordinateurs des années 80.
Fun fact : Créé par Peter Liepa et Chris Gray, Boulder Dash a donné à son héros Rockford une identité durable à travers de nombreux portages, suites et remakes.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Boulder Dash es un juego de acción y puzle donde Rockford excava cuevas para recoger diamantes mientras evita rocas que caen y enemigos. Cada nivel se apoya en la gravedad, el ritmo y la anticipación, obligando a planificar cada movimiento para no quedar atrapado. Su diseño simple pero exigente lo convirtió en un clásico de los microordenadores de los años 80.
Dato curioso: Creado por Peter Liepa y Chris Gray, Boulder Dash dio a su héroe Rockford una identidad duradera en numerosos ports, secuelas y remakes.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Boulder Dash è un gioco d’azione e rompicapo in cui Rockford scava gallerie per raccogliere diamanti evitando rocce in caduta e nemici. Ogni livello si basa su gravità, tempismo e anticipazione, costringendo a pianificare ogni movimento per non restare intrappolati. Il suo design semplice ma esigente lo rese un classico dei microcomputer anni 80.
Curiosità: Creato da Peter Liepa e Chris Gray, Boulder Dash diede al suo eroe Rockford un’identità duratura in molti porting, sequel e remake.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Boulder Dash ist ein Action-Puzzlespiel, in dem Rockford Höhlen gräbt, Diamanten sammelt und fallenden Felsen sowie Gegnern ausweicht. Jede Stufe basiert auf Schwerkraft, Timing und Voraussicht, sodass jeder Schritt geplant werden muss, um nicht gefangen zu werden. Das einfache, aber fordernde Design machte es zu einem Heimcomputer-Klassiker der 80er.
Interessante Tatsache: Boulder Dash wurde von Peter Liepa und Chris Gray geschaffen und gab seinem Helden Rockford eine dauerhafte Identität in vielen Umsetzungen, Fortsetzungen und Remakes.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Boulder Dash é um jogo de ação e puzzle em que Rockford escava cavernas para recolher diamantes enquanto evita rochas em queda e inimigos. Cada nível depende da gravidade, do ritmo e da antecipação, obrigando a planear cada movimento para não ficar preso. O seu design simples mas exigente tornou-o um clássico dos microcomputadores dos anos 80.
Curiosidade: Criado por Peter Liepa e Chris Gray, Boulder Dash deu ao herói Rockford uma identidade duradoura em muitos ports, sequelas e remakes.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
