<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>Steam is an online content distribution platform developed by Valve. Oriented towards video games, it allows users to buy games, content for games, automatically update them, manage the multiplayer part of games and offers community tools around games using Steam.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Steam est une plateforme de distribution de contenu en ligne développée par Valve. Orientée vers les jeux vidéo, elle permet aux utilisateurs d'acheter des jeux, du contenu pour les jeux, de les mettre à jour automatiquement, de gérer la partie multijoueur des jeux et offre des outils communautaires autour des jeux utilisant Steam.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Steam ist eine von Valve entwickelte Online-Plattform für den Vertrieb von Inhalten. Sie ist auf Videospiele ausgerichtet und ermöglicht es den Nutzern, Spiele und Inhalte für Spiele zu kaufen, diese automatisch zu aktualisieren, den Mehrspielerpart von Spielen zu verwalten und bietet Community-Tools rund um die Spiele, die Steam nutzen.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Steam es una plataforma de distribución de contenidos en línea desarrollada por Valve. Orientada a los videojuegos, permite a los usuarios comprar juegos, contenidos para juegos, actualizar automáticamente los juegos, gestionar la parte multijugador de los juegos y ofrece herramientas de comunidad en torno a los juegos que utilizan Steam.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Steam è una piattaforma di distribuzione di contenuti online sviluppata da Valve. Orientata ai videogiochi, consente agli utenti di acquistare giochi, contenuti per i giochi, di aggiornare automaticamente i giochi, di gestire la parte multigiocatore dei giochi e di offrire strumenti per la comunità che utilizza Steam.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>Steamは、Valve社が開発したオンラインコンテンツ配信プラットフォームです。ビデオゲームに特化しており、ゲームやゲーム用コンテンツの購入、ゲームの自動アップデート、ゲームのマルチプレイヤーパートの管理、Steamを使用したゲームに関するコミュニティツールの提供などが可能です。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>Steam is een door Valve ontwikkeld platform voor de distributie van online inhoud. Het is gericht op videogames en stelt gebruikers in staat games en content voor games te kopen, games automatisch bij te werken, het multiplayer gedeelte van games te beheren en biedt community tools rond games met behulp van Steam.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>Steam to platforma dystrybucji treści online opracowana przez firmę Valve. Zorientowana na gry wideo, pozwala użytkownikom kupować gry, zawartość do gier, automatycznie aktualizować gry, zarządzać częścią wieloosobową gier i oferuje narzędzia społecznościowe wokół gier za pomocą Steam.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Steam é uma plataforma de distribuição de conteúdo online desenvolvida pela Valve. Orientada para jogos de vídeo, permite aos utilizadores comprar jogos, conteúdo para jogos, actualizar automaticamente jogos, gerir a parte multijogadores de jogos e oferece ferramentas de comunidade em torno de jogos utilizando o Steam.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>Steam - это онлайн-платформа для распространения контента, разработанная компанией Valve. Ориентированная на видеоигры, она позволяет пользователям приобретать игры, контент для игр, автоматически обновлять их, управлять многопользовательской частью игр и предлагает инструменты сообщества для игр, использующих Steam.</text>
</text>


<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Far Cry 3 (2012)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>Far Cry 3 drops the player on a dangerous tropical island filled with enemy camps, wildlife and open exploration. Jason Brody changes from a stranded tourist into a fighter able to hunt, infiltrate bases and use the environment to survive. The game marked the series with its dense open world, darker tone and Vaas, an iconic antagonist.
Fun fact: Vaas’ line about the definition of insanity became one of the most famous scenes in modern video games.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Far Cry 3 plonge le joueur sur une île tropicale dangereuse, entre camps ennemis, faune sauvage et exploration libre. Jason Brody y évolue d’un simple touriste survivant à un combattant capable de chasser, infiltrer des bases et utiliser l’environnement à son avantage. Le jeu marque la série par son monde ouvert dense, son ton plus sombre et son antagoniste Vaas, devenu emblématique.
Fun fact : Le monologue “Did I ever tell you the definition of insanity?” de Vaas est devenu l’une des scènes les plus célèbres du jeu vidéo moderne.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Far Cry 3 lleva al jugador a una peligrosa isla tropical, entre campamentos enemigos, fauna salvaje y exploración libre. Jason Brody pasa de turista perdido a combatiente capaz de cazar, infiltrarse en bases y usar el entorno para sobrevivir. El juego marcó la serie con su mundo abierto denso, su tono más oscuro y Vaas, un antagonista icónico.
Dato curioso: El monólogo de Vaas sobre la definición de locura se convirtió en una de las escenas más famosas del videojuego moderno.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Far Cry 3 porta il giocatore su un’isola tropicale pericolosa, tra campi nemici, fauna selvatica ed esplorazione libera. Jason Brody passa da turista disperso a combattente capace di cacciare, infiltrarsi nelle basi e usare l’ambiente per sopravvivere. Il gioco ha segnato la serie con un mondo aperto denso, un tono più cupo e Vaas, antagonista iconico.
Curiosità: Il monologo di Vaas sulla definizione di follia è diventato una delle scene più celebri del videogioco moderno.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Far Cry 3 versetzt den Spieler auf eine gefährliche Tropeninsel mit feindlichen Lagern, Wildtieren und freier Erkundung. Jason Brody entwickelt sich vom gestrandeten Touristen zu einem Kämpfer, der jagt, Basen infiltriert und die Umgebung zum Überleben nutzt. Das Spiel prägte die Reihe durch seine dichte offene Welt, den dunkleren Ton und Vaas als ikonischen Gegenspieler.
Interessante Tatsache: Vaas’ Monolog über die Definition von Wahnsinn wurde zu einer der bekanntesten Szenen moderner Videospiele.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Far Cry 3 coloca o jogador numa ilha tropical perigosa, entre acampamentos inimigos, fauna selvagem e exploração livre. Jason Brody passa de turista perdido a combatente capaz de caçar, infiltrar bases e usar o ambiente para sobreviver. O jogo marcou a série com o seu mundo aberto denso, tom mais sombrio e Vaas, um antagonista icónico.
Curiosidade: O monólogo de Vaas sobre a definição de loucura tornou-se uma das cenas mais famosas dos videojogos modernos.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
