<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>The SuFami Turbo is an adapter that allows you to put specially adapted game cartridges. It is a proprietary format created by Bandaï and released only in Japan. It had two cartridge ports, to allow a friend to exchange backup data.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Le SuFami Turbo est un adaptateur permettant de mettre des cartouches de jeux spécialement adaptées. C'est un format propriétaire créé par Bandaï et sorti uniquement au Japon. Il avait deux ports cartouche, pour permettre à un ami d'échanger des données de sauvegarde.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Der SuFami Turbo ist ein Adapter, in den speziell angepasste Spielkassetten eingesetzt werden können. Es ist ein proprietäres Format, das von Bandai entwickelt und nur in Japan veröffentlicht wurde. Er hatte zwei Cartridge-Anschlüsse, um einem Freund den Austausch von Speicherdaten zu ermöglichen.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>El SuFami Turbo es un adaptador que permite poner cartuchos de juegos especialmente adaptados. Es un formato propietario creado por Bandai y lanzado sólo en Japón. Tenía dos puertos para cartuchos, para permitir a un amigo intercambiar datos de copia de seguridad.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Il SuFami Turbo è un adattatore che consente di inserire cartucce di gioco appositamente adattate. Si tratta di un formato proprietario creato da Bandai e rilasciato solo in Giappone. Aveva due porte per le cartucce, per consentire a un amico di scambiare i dati di backup.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>SuFamiターボは、特別にアレンジされたゲームカートリッジを入れることができるアダプターです。バンダイが作成した独自のフォーマットで、日本でのみ発売された。カートリッジポートが2つあり、友人とバックアップデータの交換ができるようになっていた。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>De SuFami Turbo is een adapter waarmee je speciaal aangepaste spelcassettes kunt plaatsen. Het is een eigen formaat gemaakt door Bandai en alleen in Japan uitgebracht. Het had twee cartridge-poorten, zodat een vriend back-up gegevens kon uitwisselen.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>SuFami Turbo to adapter, który pozwala na umieszczenie specjalnie przystosowanych kartridży z grami. Jest to zastrzeżony format stworzony przez Bandai i wydany tylko w Japonii. Posiadał dwa porty kartridży, aby umożliwić znajomemu wymianę danych kopii zapasowych.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>O SuFami Turbo é um adaptador que lhe permite colocar cartuchos de jogo especialmente adaptados. É um formato proprietário criado pela Bandai e lançado apenas no Japão. Tinha duas portas de cartuchos, para permitir a um amigo a troca de dados de reserva.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>SuFami Turbo - это адаптер, который позволяет ставить специально адаптированные игровые картриджи. Это проприетарный формат, созданный компанией Bandai и выпущенный только в Японии. Он имел два порта для картриджей, чтобы позволить другу обмениваться резервными данными.</text>
</text>



<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;SD Gundam Generation (1996)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>Gundam is an iconic figure of Japanese mecha, featuring giant robots at the heart of futuristic military conflicts. In SD Gundam Generation on SuFami Turbo, the machines appear in a more compact and stylized form while keeping their weapons and abilities, in a strategy game where every move and attack must be carefully considered.
Fun fact: SD stands for "Super Deformed", a deliberately caricatured version of characters and robots that became very popular in Japan.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Gundam est une figure emblématique du mecha japonais, mettant en scène des robots géants au cœur de conflits militaires futuristes. Dans SD Gundam Generation sur Sufami Turbo, les machines apparaissent dans une version plus compacte et stylisée, tout en conservant leurs armes et capacités, dans un jeu de stratégie où chaque déplacement et attaque doivent être réfléchis.
Fun fact : Le style SD signifie "Super Deformed", une version volontairement caricaturale des personnages et robots, très populaire au Japon.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Gundam es una figura emblemática del mecha japonés, con robots gigantes en el centro de conflictos militares futuristas. En SD Gundam Generation para SuFami Turbo, las máquinas aparecen en una versión más compacta y estilizada, pero conservan sus armas y capacidades, en un juego de estrategia donde cada movimiento y ataque debe pensarse con cuidado.
Dato curioso: El estilo SD significa "Super Deformed", una versión deliberadamente caricaturesca de personajes y robots muy popular en Japón.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Gundam è una figura emblematica del mecha giapponese, con robot giganti al centro di conflitti militari futuristici. In SD Gundam Generation per SuFami Turbo, le macchine appaiono in una versione più compatta e stilizzata, pur mantenendo armi e capacità, in un gioco di strategia dove ogni movimento e attacco va valutato con attenzione.
Curiosità: Lo stile SD significa "Super Deformed", una versione volutamente caricaturale di personaggi e robot molto popolare in Giappone.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Gundam ist eine Ikone des japanischen Mecha-Genres, mit riesigen Robotern im Mittelpunkt futuristischer Militärkonflikte. In SD Gundam Generation für SuFami Turbo erscheinen die Maschinen kompakter und stilisierter, behalten aber ihre Waffen und Fähigkeiten, in einem Strategiespiel, bei dem jede Bewegung und jeder Angriff gut überlegt sein muss.
Interessante Tatsache: SD bedeutet "Super Deformed", eine bewusst karikierte Version von Figuren und Robotern, die in Japan sehr beliebt wurde.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Gundam é uma figura emblemática do mecha japonês, com robôs gigantes no centro de conflitos militares futuristas. Em SD Gundam Generation para SuFami Turbo, as máquinas aparecem numa versão mais compacta e estilizada, mas mantêm as suas armas e capacidades, num jogo de estratégia em que cada movimento e ataque devem ser bem pensados.
Curiosidade: O estilo SD significa "Super Deformed", uma versão deliberadamente caricatural de personagens e robôs muito popular no Japão.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
