<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>The SuperGrafx is an improved version of the PC-Engine (or CoreGrafX). Compared to the latter, it has four times more memory for the processor, a second video chip with its own memory, and a priority controller that allowed combining the output of the two video chips in different ways.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>La SuperGrafx est une version améliorée de la PC-Engine (ou CoreGrafX). Comparée à cette dernière, elle a quatre fois plus de mémoire pour le processeur, une deuxième puce vidéo avec sa propre mémoire, et un contrôleur de priorité qui permettait de combiner la sortie des deux puces vidéo de différentes manières.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Die SuperGrafx ist eine verbesserte Version der PC-Engine (oder CoreGrafX). Im Vergleich zu dieser hatte sie viermal so viel Speicher für den Prozessor, einen zweiten Videochip mit eigenem Speicher und einen Prioritätscontroller, der es ermöglichte, die Ausgabe der beiden Videochips auf verschiedene Weise zu kombinieren.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>La SuperGrafx es una versión mejorada de la PC-Engine (o CoreGrafX). En comparación con el PC-Engine, tiene cuatro veces más memoria para el procesador, un segundo chip de vídeo con su propia memoria y un controlador de prioridad que permitía combinar la salida de los dos chips de vídeo de diferentes maneras.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Il SuperGrafx è una versione migliorata del PC-Engine (o CoreGrafX). Rispetto al PC-Engine, dispone di una memoria quattro volte superiore per il processore, di un secondo chip video con memoria propria e di un controller di priorità che permetteva di combinare l'uscita dei due chip video in modi diversi.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>SuperGrafxは、PC-Engine（またはCoreGrafX）の改良版である。PC-Engineに比べ、プロセッサのメモリが4倍になり、独自のメモリを持つ第2のビデオチップを搭載し、2つのビデオチップの出力を異なる方法で組み合わせることができるプライオリティコントローラが搭載されました。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>De SuperGrafx is een verbeterde versie van de PC-Engine (of CoreGrafX). Vergeleken met de PC-Engine heeft hij vier keer meer geheugen voor de processor, een tweede videochip met een eigen geheugen en een prioriteitscontroller waarmee de output van de twee videochips op verschillende manieren kon worden gecombineerd.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>SuperGrafx to ulepszona wersja komputera PC-Engine (lub CoreGrafX). W porównaniu z PC-Engine posiadał cztery razy więcej pamięci dla procesora, drugi układ wideo z własną pamięcią oraz kontroler priorytetów, który pozwalał na łączenie w różny sposób wyjścia obu układów wideo.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>O SuperGrafx é uma versão melhorada do PC-Engine (ou CoreGrafX). Em comparação com o PC-Engine, tem quatro vezes mais memória para o processador, um segundo chip de vídeo com memória própria, e um controlador prioritário que permitiu combinar a saída dos dois chips de vídeo de formas diferentes.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>SuperGrafx - это улучшенная версия PC-Engine (или CoreGrafX). По сравнению с PC-Engine, она имеет в четыре раза больше памяти для процессора, второй видеочип с собственной памятью и контроллер приоритетов, который позволял комбинировать вывод двух видеочипов различными способами.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Daimakaimura / Ghouls ’n Ghosts (1990)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>Arthur crosses Daimakaimura in his shining armor, facing demons, undead creatures and grotesque monsters with demanding precision. On SuperGrafx, this adaptation of Ghouls ’n Ghosts stands out for its striking visual fidelity to the arcade version, while preserving the series’ brutal difficulty and unforgiving jumps.
Fun fact: As in the arcade game, finishing it once is not enough; a second loop must be completed to reach the true ending.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Le chevalier Arthur traverse Daimakaimura dans son armure brillante, affrontant démons, morts-vivants et créatures grotesques avec une précision exigeante. Sur SuperGrafx, cette adaptation de Ghouls ’n Ghosts se distingue par une fidélité visuelle remarquable à l’arcade, tout en conservant la difficulté brutale et les sauts impitoyables de la série.
Fun fact : Comme dans la version arcade, terminer le jeu une première fois ne suffit pas, il faut recommencer une seconde boucle pour accéder à la véritable fin.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>El caballero Arthur atraviesa Daimakaimura con su armadura brillante, enfrentándose a demonios, muertos vivientes y criaturas grotescas con una precisión exigente. En SuperGrafx, esta adaptación de Ghouls ’n Ghosts destaca por su notable fidelidad visual al arcade, manteniendo la dificultad brutal y los saltos implacables de la serie.
Dato curioso: Como en la versión arcade, terminar el juego una vez no basta; hay que completar una segunda vuelta para ver el verdadero final.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Il cavaliere Arthur attraversa Daimakaimura nella sua armatura lucente, affrontando demoni, non morti e creature grottesche con una precisione severa. Su SuperGrafx, questo adattamento di Ghouls ’n Ghosts si distingue per la notevole fedeltà visiva all’arcade, conservando la difficoltà brutale e i salti spietati della serie.
Curiosità: Come nella versione arcade, finire il gioco una sola volta non basta; bisogna completare un secondo giro per raggiungere il vero finale.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Der Ritter Arthur durchquert Daimakaimura in seiner glänzenden Rüstung und stellt sich Dämonen, Untoten und grotesken Kreaturen mit hoher Präzision. Auf der SuperGrafx fällt diese Umsetzung von Ghouls ’n Ghosts durch ihre bemerkenswerte visuelle Nähe zur Arcade-Version auf, während sie die brutale Schwierigkeit und gnadenlosen Sprünge der Reihe bewahrt.
Interessante Tatsache: Wie in der Arcade-Version reicht ein einmaliges Durchspielen nicht aus; erst eine zweite Runde führt zum wahren Ende.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>O cavaleiro Arthur atravessa Daimakaimura com a sua armadura brilhante, enfrentando demónios, mortos-vivos e criaturas grotescas com uma precisão exigente. Na SuperGrafx, esta adaptação de Ghouls ’n Ghosts destaca-se pela forte fidelidade visual ao arcade, mantendo a dificuldade brutal e os saltos implacáveis da série.
Curiosidade: Como na versão arcade, terminar o jogo uma vez não basta; é preciso completar uma segunda volta para chegar ao verdadeiro final.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
