<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>Taito Corporation is a Japanese company specializing in video games, toys, arcade terminals and game centers, based in Shinjuku, Tokyo. It began producing video games in 1973. In 2005, Taito was acquired by Square Enix and became a wholly-owned subsidiary in 2006.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Taito Corporation est une entreprise japonaise spécialisée dans les jeux vidéo, les jouets, les bornes d'arcade et les centres de jeux, basée à Shinjuku, Tokyo. Elle a commencé à produire des jeux vidéo en 1973. En 2005, Taito a été rachetée par Square Enix, dont elle est devenue une filiale à part entière en 2006.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Die Taito Corporation ist ein japanisches Unternehmen mit Sitz in Shinjuku, Tokio, das sich auf Videospiele, Spielzeug, Arcade-Terminals und Spielzentren spezialisiert hat. Sie begann 1973 mit der Produktion von Videospielen. Im Jahr 2005 wurde Taito von Square Enix aufgekauft und ist seit 2006 eine hundertprozentige Tochtergesellschaft des Unternehmens.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Taito Corporation es una empresa japonesa especializada en videojuegos, juguetes, terminales arcade y centros de juego, con sede en Shinjuku, Tokio. Comenzó a producir videojuegos en 1973. En 2005, Taito fue adquirida por Square Enix y se convirtió en una filial al 100% en 2006.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Taito Corporation è un'azienda giapponese specializzata in videogiochi, giocattoli, terminali arcade e centri di gioco, con sede a Shinjuku, Tokyo. Ha iniziato a produrre videogiochi nel 1973. Nel 2005 Taito è stata acquisita da Square Enix e nel 2006 è diventata una società interamente controllata.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>株式会社タイトーは、東京都新宿区に本社を置く、ビデオゲーム、玩具、アーケード端末、ゲームセンターを専門に扱う日本の企業です。1973年にビデオゲームの生産を開始した。2005年、タイトーはスクウェア・エニックスに買収され、2006年に完全子会社となった。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>Taito Corporation is een Japanse onderneming die gespecialiseerd is in videospelletjes, speelgoed, arcade-terminals en spelcentra, gevestigd in Shinjuku, Tokio. Het begon videospelletjes te produceren in 1973. In 2005 werd Taito overgenomen door Square Enix en in 2006 werd het een volledige dochteronderneming.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>Taito Corporation to japońska firma specjalizująca się w grach wideo, zabawkach, terminalach arcade i centrach gier, z siedzibą w Shinjuku w Tokio. Rozpoczęła produkcję gier wideo w 1973 roku. W 2005 roku Taito zostało przejęte przez Square Enix, a w 2006 roku stało się spółką zależną w całości.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Taito Corporation é uma empresa japonesa especializada em jogos de vídeo, brinquedos, terminais de jogos e centros de jogos, sediada em Shinjuku, Tóquio. Começou a produzir jogos de vídeo em 1973. Em 2005, a Taito foi adquirida pela Square Enix e tornou-se uma subsidiária totalmente detida em 2006.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>Taito Corporation - японская компания, специализирующаяся на производстве видеоигр, игрушек, аркадных терминалов и игровых центров, расположенная в Синдзюку, Токио. Она начала выпускать видеоигры в 1973 году. В 2005 году Taito была приобретена компанией Square Enix, а в 2006 году стала ее дочерней компанией.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;The NewZealand Story (1988)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>Tiki is a small kiwi armed with a bow, setting out to rescue his friends through stages filled with traps, enemies and floating platforms. The NewZealand Story mixes colorful worlds, precise movement and temporary mounts found along the way, in an arcade adventure known for its cute look and sometimes fearsome difficulty.
Fun fact: In some areas, losing the final life can send the player to a secret stage called “Heaven” instead of an immediate game over.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Tiki est un petit kiwi armé d’un arc parti sauver ses amis capturés à travers des niveaux remplis de pièges, d’ennemis et de plateformes flottantes. The NewZealand Story mélange univers coloré, déplacements précis et montures temporaires récupérées en cours de route, dans une aventure arcade connue pour son apparence mignonne mais sa difficulté parfois redoutable.
Fun fact : Dans certaines zones, perdre sa dernière vie peut envoyer le joueur dans un niveau secret appelé “Heaven” au lieu d’un game over immédiat.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Tiki es un pequeño kiwi armado con un arco que parte a rescatar a sus amigos por niveles llenos de trampas, enemigos y plataformas flotantes. The NewZealand Story combina mundos coloridos, movimientos precisos y monturas temporales encontradas durante el recorrido, en una aventura arcade conocida por su aspecto adorable y su dificultad a veces temible.
Dato curioso: En algunas zonas, perder la última vida puede enviar al jugador a una fase secreta llamada “Heaven” en lugar de un game over inmediato.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Tiki è un piccolo kiwi armato di arco che parte per salvare i suoi amici in livelli pieni di trappole, nemici e piattaforme sospese. The NewZealand Story unisce mondi colorati, movimenti precisi e cavalcature temporanee trovate lungo il percorso, in un’avventura arcade nota per l’aspetto tenero e la difficoltà a volte severa.
Curiosità: In alcune zone, perdere l’ultima vita può mandare il giocatore in un livello segreto chiamato “Heaven” invece di un game over immediato.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Tiki ist ein kleiner Kiwi mit Bogen, der seine gefangenen Freunde durch Level voller Fallen, Gegner und schwebender Plattformen retten muss. The NewZealand Story verbindet bunte Welten, präzise Bewegung und unterwegs gefundene temporäre Reittiere zu einem Arcade-Abenteuer, das für seinen niedlichen Look und seine teils harte Schwierigkeit bekannt ist.
Interessante Tatsache: In manchen Bereichen kann der Verlust des letzten Lebens den Spieler in ein geheimes Level namens “Heaven” statt sofort zum Game Over schicken.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Tiki é um pequeno kiwi armado com um arco que parte para salvar seus amigos em fases cheias de armadilhas, inimigos e plataformas flutuantes. The NewZealand Story mistura mundos coloridos, movimentos precisos e montarias temporárias encontradas pelo caminho, em uma aventura arcade conhecida pelo visual fofo e pela dificuldade às vezes severa.
Curiosidade: Em algumas áreas, perder a última vida pode enviar o jogador para uma fase secreta chamada “Heaven” em vez de um game over imediato.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
