<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>Technōs Japan Corporation (株式会社テクノスジャパン) is a Japanese company founded in 1981. Now defunct, it was active in the arcade game market. Its most popular franchises are the Nekketsu Kōha Kunio-kun license and the Double Dragon series both created by Yoshihisa Kishimoto.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Technōs Japan Corporation (株式会社テクノスジャパン) est une société japonaise fondée en 1981. Aujourd'hui disparue, elle a été active sur le marché des jeux d'arcade. Ses franchises les plus populaires sont la licence Nekketsu Kōha Kunio-kun et la série Double Dragon toutes deux créées par Yoshihisa Kishimoto.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Technōs Japan Corporation (株式会社テクノスジャパン) ist ein japanisches Unternehmen, das 1981 gegründet wurde. Das heute nicht mehr existierende Unternehmen war auf dem Markt für Arcade-Spiele aktiv. Seine beliebtesten Franchises sind die Nekketsu-Lizenz Kōha Kunio-kun und die Double Dragon-Serie, die beide von Yoshihisa Kishimoto entwickelt wurden.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Technōs Japan Corporation (株式会社テクノスジャパン) es una empresa japonesa fundada en 1981. Actualmente desaparecida, estuvo activa en el mercado de los juegos arcade. Sus franquicias más populares son la licencia Nekketsu Kōha Kunio-kun y la serie Double Dragon, ambas creadas por Yoshihisa Kishimoto.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Technōs Japan Corporation (株式会社テクノスジャパン) è una società giapponese fondata nel 1981. Oggi scomparsa, era attiva nel mercato dei giochi arcade. I suoi franchise più popolari sono la licenza Nekketsu Kōha Kunio-kun e la serie Double Dragon, entrambe create da Yoshihisa Kishimoto.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>テクノスジャパン株式会社（株式会社テクノスジャパン）は、1981年に設立された日本の企業である。現在では消滅していますが、アーケードゲーム市場で活躍していました。最も人気のあるフランチャイズは、岸本義久が作った『熱血行進曲 くにお君』ライセンスと『ダブルドラゴン』シリーズです。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>Technōs Japan Corporation (株式会社テクノスジャパン) is een Japanse onderneming die in 1981 werd opgericht. Het is nu ter ziele, maar was actief op de markt van arcadespellen. De populairste franchises zijn de Nekketsu Kōha Kunio-kun licentie en de Double Dragon serie, beide gemaakt door Yoshihisa Kishimoto.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>Technōs Japan Corporation (株式会社テクノスジャパン) to japońska firma założona w 1981 roku. Obecnie nieistniejąca, działała na rynku gier arcade. Jej najpopularniejsze franczyzy to licencja Nekketsu Kōha Kunio-kun oraz seria Double Dragon, obie stworzone przez Yoshihisę Kishimoto.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Technōs Japan Corporation (株式会社テクノスジャパン) é uma empresa japonesa fundada em 1981. Agora extinta, estava activa no mercado dos jogos arcade. As suas franquias mais populares são a licença Nekketsu Kōha Kunio-kun e a série Double Dragon, ambas criadas por Yoshihisa Kishimoto.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>Technōs Japan Corporation (株式会社テクノスジャパン) - японская компания, основанная в 1981 году. Ныне не существующая, она активно работала на рынке аркадных игр. Наиболее популярными франшизами компании являются лицензия Nekketsu Kōha Kunio-kun и серия Double Dragon, созданная Йошихисой Кисимото.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Double Dragon (1987)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>Billy Lee is one of two martial artist brothers fighting through the streets to face the Black Warriors gang and rescue Marian. In Double Dragon, he stands out with his blue outfit, punches, kicks, throws and elbow strikes, at the heart of an urban beat’em up that strongly shaped arcade gaming.
Fun fact: Double Dragon helped popularize two-player cooperative beat’em up action, with Billy and Jimmy fighting side by side.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Billy Lee est l’un des deux frères experts en arts martiaux lancés dans les rues pour affronter le gang des Black Warriors et sauver Marian. Dans Double Dragon, il se distingue par sa tenue bleue, ses coups de poing, coups de pied, projections et attaques au coude, au cœur d’un beat’em up urbain qui a fortement marqué l’arcade.
Fun fact : Double Dragon a popularisé le beat’em up coopératif à deux joueurs, avec Billy et Jimmy combattant côte à côte.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Billy Lee es uno de los dos hermanos expertos en artes marciales que recorren las calles para enfrentarse a la banda Black Warriors y rescatar a Marian. En Double Dragon destaca por su ropa azul, puñetazos, patadas, proyecciones y codazos, dentro de un beat’em up urbano que marcó con fuerza el arcade.
Dato curioso: Double Dragon popularizó el beat’em up cooperativo para dos jugadores, con Billy y Jimmy luchando lado a lado.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Billy Lee è uno dei due fratelli esperti di arti marziali che attraversano le strade per affrontare la gang Black Warriors e salvare Marian. In Double Dragon si distingue per l’abito blu, pugni, calci, prese e gomitate, al centro di un beat’em up urbano che ha segnato profondamente l’arcade.
Curiosità: Double Dragon ha reso popolare il beat’em up cooperativo per due giocatori, con Billy e Jimmy fianco a fianco.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Billy Lee ist einer von zwei Brüdern und Kampfsportexperten, die sich durch die Straßen kämpfen, um die Black Warriors zu besiegen und Marian zu retten. In Double Dragon fällt er durch sein blaues Outfit, Schläge, Tritte, Würfe und Ellbogenangriffe auf, in einem urbanen Beat’em-up, das die Arcade stark prägte.
Interessante Tatsache: Double Dragon machte kooperative Beat’em-up-Action für zwei Spieler populär, mit Billy und Jimmy Seite an Seite.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Billy Lee é um dos dois irmãos especialistas em artes marciais que percorrem as ruas para enfrentar o gangue Black Warriors e salvar Marian. Em Double Dragon, destaca-se pela roupa azul, socos, chutes, arremessos e cotoveladas, no centro de um beat’em up urbano que marcou muito os arcades.
Curiosidade: Double Dragon popularizou o beat’em up cooperativo para dois jogadores, com Billy e Jimmy lutando lado a lado.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
