<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>Tekken is a fighting game series developed by Bandai Namco, known for its fluid gameplay and deep combo mechanics. Each character has a distinct fighting style, ranging from martial arts to more exotic techniques. The saga is distinguished by its 3D fighting system, iconic characters and complex storylines. Tekken is one of the most popular and influential fighting franchises in video games.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Tekken est une série de jeux de combat développée par Bandai Namco, connue pour son gameplay fluide et ses mécaniques profondes de combos. Chaque personnage a un style de combat distinct, allant des arts martiaux aux techniques plus exotiques. La saga se distingue par son système de combat en 3D, ses personnages emblématiques et ses intrigues complexes. Tekken est l'une des franchises de combat les plus populaires et influentes du jeu vidéo.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Tekken es una serie de juegos de lucha desarrollada por Bandai Namco, conocida por su jugabilidad fluida y sus mecánicas profundas de combos. Cada personaje tiene un estilo de combate distinto, desde artes marciales hasta técnicas más exóticas. La saga destaca por su sistema de lucha en 3D, sus personajes icónicos y sus historias complejas.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Tekken è una serie di picchiaduro sviluppata da Bandai Namco, nota per il gameplay fluido e le profonde meccaniche di combo. Ogni personaggio ha uno stile di combattimento distinto, dalle arti marziali a tecniche più esotiche. La saga si distingue per il sistema di lotta in 3D, i personaggi iconici e le trame complesse.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Tekken ist eine von Bandai Namco entwickelte Kampfspielreihe, bekannt für ihr flüssiges Gameplay und ihre tiefen Combo-Mechaniken. Jede Figur besitzt einen eigenen Kampfstil, von Kampfkünsten bis zu exotischeren Techniken. Die Saga zeichnet sich durch ihr 3D-Kampfsystem, ikonische Figuren und komplexe Geschichten aus.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Tekken é uma série de jogos de luta desenvolvida pela Bandai Namco, conhecida por sua jogabilidade fluida e mecânicas profundas de combos. Cada personagem tem um estilo de combate próprio, das artes marciais a técnicas mais exóticas. A saga se destaca por seu sistema de luta em 3D, personagens icônicos e histórias complexas.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Tekken 3 (Arcade, 1997)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>Jin Kazama is a tormented fighter, heir to the Mishima style and marked by a constant inner struggle. Trained in traditional martial arts, he seeks to free himself from the evil influence eating away at him while confronting his own bloodline. His style blends power, discipline and precision, making him one of Tekken’s most iconic characters.
Fun fact: Jin replaced Kazuya as the central character in Tekken 3, marking a major turning point in the series.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Jin Kazama est un combattant au destin tourmenté, héritier du style Mishima et marqué par une lutte intérieure constante. Formé aux arts martiaux traditionnels, il cherche à se libérer de l’influence maléfique qui le ronge tout en affrontant sa propre lignée. Son style allie puissance, discipline et précision, faisant de lui l’un des personnages les plus emblématiques de Tekken.
Fun fact : Jin a remplacé Kazuya comme personnage central dans Tekken 3, marquant un tournant majeur dans l’histoire de la saga.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Jin Kazama es un luchador de destino atormentado, heredero del estilo Mishima y marcado por una lucha interior constante. Entrenado en artes marciales tradicionales, busca liberarse de la influencia maligna que lo consume mientras enfrenta su propio linaje. Su estilo combina poder, disciplina y precisión, convirtiéndolo en uno de los personajes más emblemáticos de Tekken.
Dato curioso: Jin reemplazó a Kazuya como personaje central en Tekken 3, marcando un gran giro en la saga.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Jin Kazama è un combattente dal destino tormentato, erede dello stile Mishima e segnato da una lotta interiore costante. Addestrato nelle arti marziali tradizionali, cerca di liberarsi dall’influenza maligna che lo consuma mentre affronta la propria stirpe. Il suo stile unisce potenza, disciplina e precisione, rendendolo uno dei personaggi più iconici di Tekken.
Curiosità: Jin ha sostituito Kazuya come personaggio centrale in Tekken 3, segnando una svolta importante nella saga.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Jin Kazama ist ein Kämpfer mit gequältem Schicksal, Erbe des Mishima-Stils und geprägt von einem ständigen inneren Kampf. In traditionellen Kampfkünsten ausgebildet, versucht er, sich vom bösen Einfluss in ihm zu befreien, während er sich seiner eigenen Blutlinie stellt. Sein Stil verbindet Kraft, Disziplin und Präzision und macht ihn zu einer der prägendsten Figuren von Tekken.
Interessante Tatsache: Jin ersetzte Kazuya als zentrale Figur in Tekken 3 und markierte einen großen Wendepunkt der Saga.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Jin Kazama é um lutador de destino atormentado, herdeiro do estilo Mishima e marcado por uma luta interna constante. Treinado em artes marciais tradicionais, ele busca se libertar da influência maligna que o consome enquanto enfrenta sua própria linhagem. Seu estilo combina força, disciplina e precisão, tornando-o um dos personagens mais emblemáticos de Tekken.
Curiosidade: Jin substituiu Kazuya como personagem central em Tekken 3, marcando uma grande virada na saga.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
