<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>Produced by Texas Instruments, this computer has some similarities with the concept of a video game console. It can be connected to a television set via a SCART socket, can read cartridges and has a connector allowing two game controllers to be attached. It can also use audio cassettes.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Produit par Texas Instruments, cet ordinateur présente quelques similarités avec le concept de console de jeux vidéo. Il peut se brancher sur un téléviseur par l'intermédiaire d'une prise péritel, peut lire des cartouches et dispose d'un connecteur permettant de lui adjoindre deux manettes de jeu. Il peut également utiliser des cassettes audio.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Dieser von Texas Instruments hergestellte Computer weist einige Ähnlichkeiten mit dem Konzept der Videospielkonsole auf. Er kann über einen Scart-Anschluss an einen Fernseher angeschlossen werden, kann Spielkassetten abspielen und hat einen Anschluss für zwei Joysticks. Er kann auch Audiokassetten verwenden.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Fabricado por Texas Instruments, este ordenador tiene algunas similitudes con el concepto de consola de videojuegos. Puede conectarse a un televisor a través de una toma SCART, puede leer cartuchos y tiene un conector para dos mandos de juego. También puede utilizar casetes de audio.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Prodotto da Texas Instruments, questo computer presenta alcune analogie con il concetto di console per videogiochi. Può essere collegato a un televisore tramite una presa SCART, può leggere cartucce e dispone di un connettore per due controller di gioco. Può anche utilizzare cassette audio.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>テキサス・インスツルメンツ社が製造したこのコンピュータは、ビデオゲーム機のコンセプトと似ているところがある。SCARTソケットでテレビに接続でき、カートリッジを読み込むことができ、2つのゲームコントローラー用のコネクタを備えています。また、オーディオカセットも使用可能です。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>Deze computer, geproduceerd door Texas Instruments, vertoont enige overeenkomsten met het concept van een videospelconsole. Hij kan worden aangesloten op een televisie via een SCART-aansluiting, kan cassettes lezen en heeft een aansluiting voor twee spelcontrollers. Hij kan ook audiocassettes gebruiken.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>Wyprodukowany przez Texas Instruments, komputer ten ma pewne podobieństwa do koncepcji konsoli do gier wideo. Może być podłączony do telewizora przez gniazdo SCART, może czytać kasety i ma złącze dla dwóch kontrolerów gier. Może również korzystać z kaset audio.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Produzido pela Texas Instruments, este computador tem algumas semelhanças com o conceito de uma consola de videojogo. Pode ser ligado a um aparelho de televisão através de uma tomada SCART, pode ler cartuchos e tem um conector para dois controladores de jogos. Pode também utilizar cassetes áudio.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>Произведенный компанией Texas Instruments, этот компьютер имеет некоторое сходство с концепцией игровой приставки. Он может быть подключен к телевизору через разъем SCART, может считывать картриджи и имеет разъем для двух джойстиков. Он также может использовать аудиокассеты.</text>
</text>


<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Hunt the Wumpus (1981)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>Hunt the Wumpus is an exploration and deduction game where the player moves through a cave network to hunt a hidden creature. Each room gives clues about nearby dangers, such as the Wumpus, pits or bats, forcing the player to remember the map and plan each move before shooting.
Fun fact: Created in 1973 on mainframe computers such as the PDP-10, the game was later adapted for many home computers.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Hunt the Wumpus est un jeu d’exploration et de déduction où le joueur progresse dans un réseau de cavernes pour traquer une créature cachée. Chaque salle fournit des indices sur les dangers proches, comme le Wumpus, les fosses ou les chauves-souris, obligeant à mémoriser la carte et à anticiper ses déplacements avant de tirer.
Fun fact : Créé en 1973 sur ordinateur mainframe comme le PDP-10, le jeu a ensuite été adapté sur de nombreux micro-ordinateurs.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Hunt the Wumpus es un juego de exploración y deducción donde el jugador avanza por una red de cuevas para cazar a una criatura oculta. Cada sala ofrece pistas sobre peligros cercanos, como el Wumpus, pozos o murciélagos, obligando a recordar el mapa y anticipar cada movimiento antes de disparar.
Dato curioso: Creado en 1973 en ordenadores centrales como el PDP-10, el juego fue adaptado después a muchos microordenadores.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Hunt the Wumpus è un gioco di esplorazione e deduzione in cui il giocatore avanza in una rete di caverne per cacciare una creatura nascosta. Ogni stanza offre indizi sui pericoli vicini, come il Wumpus, le fosse o i pipistrelli, obbligando a ricordare la mappa e prevedere le mosse prima di tirare.
Curiosità: Creato nel 1973 su computer mainframe come il PDP-10, il gioco fu poi adattato su molti microcomputer.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Hunt the Wumpus ist ein Erkundungs- und Deduktionsspiel, in dem der Spieler ein Höhlennetz durchquert, um eine verborgene Kreatur zu jagen. Jeder Raum liefert Hinweise auf nahe Gefahren wie den Wumpus, Gruben oder Fledermäuse, sodass Karte und Bewegungen gut geplant werden müssen.
Interessante Tatsache: Das Spiel entstand 1973 auf Mainframe-Computern wie dem PDP-10 und wurde später auf viele Heimcomputer angepasst.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Hunt the Wumpus é um jogo de exploração e dedução onde o jogador avança por uma rede de cavernas para caçar uma criatura escondida. Cada sala dá pistas sobre perigos próximos, como o Wumpus, poços ou morcegos, obrigando a memorizar o mapa e antecipar os movimentos antes de disparar.
Curiosidade: Criado em 1973 em computadores mainframe como o PDP-10, o jogo foi depois adaptado para muitos microcomputadores.</text>
</text>


</view>
</theme>
