<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>Inspired by the Pico-8, the TIC-80 is a fantasy console under a free license (there is also a paid version with more options). It works with Android, HTML5 (in WebAssembly4), Linux, macOS and Windows platforms.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Inspirée du Pico-8, le TIC-80 est une fantasy console sous licence libre (il existe également une version payante avec plus d'options), . Elle fonctionne avec les plateformes Android, HTML5 (en WebAssembly4), Linux, macOS et Windows.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Die TIC-80 ist eine Fantasy-Konsole unter einer freien Lizenz (es gibt auch eine kostenpflichtige Version mit mehr Optionen), die vom Pico-8 inspiriert wurde. Sie funktioniert mit den Plattformen Android, HTML5 (in WebAssembly4), Linux, macOS und Windows.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Inspirada en el Pico-8, la TIC-80 es una consola de fantasía de código abierto (también hay una versión de pago con más opciones). Funciona con plataformas Android, HTML5 (en WebAssembly4), Linux, macOS y Windows.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Ispirato al Pico-8, il TIC-80 è una console fantasy open source (esiste anche una versione a pagamento con più opzioni). Funziona con le piattaforme Android, HTML5 (in WebAssembly4), Linux, macOS e Windows.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>Pico-8にインスパイアされたTIC-80は、オープンソースのファンタジーコンソールです（より多くのオプションを備えた有料版もあります）。Android、HTML5（WebAssembly4で）、Linux、macOS、Windowsプラットフォームで動作します。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>Geïnspireerd door de Pico-8 is de TIC-80 een open source fantasieconsole (er is ook een betaalde versie met meer opties). Het werkt met Android, HTML5 (in WebAssembly4), Linux, macOS en Windows platforms.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>Zainspirowany przez Pico-8, TIC-80 jest konsolą fantasy o otwartym kodzie źródłowym (istnieje również wersja płatna z większą ilością opcji). Działa z platformami Android, HTML5 (w WebAssembly4), Linux, macOS i Windows.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Inspirado no Pico-8, o TIC-80 é uma consola de fantasia de código aberto (há também uma versão paga com mais opções). Funciona com Android, HTML5 (em WebAssembly4), Linux, macOS e plataformas Windows.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>Вдохновленная Pico-8, TIC-80 - это фантазийная консоль с открытым исходным кодом (есть также платная версия с более широкими возможностями). Она работает на платформах Android, HTML5 (на WebAssembly4), Linux, macOS и Windows.</text>
</text>


<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Super Meat Boy TIC-80 Demake (2020)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>Super Meat Boy TIC-80 Demake captures the spirit of the original game in a tiny version built for the TIC-80 fantasy console. Meat Boy crosses short, dangerous stages where every jump demands precision, speed and instant retries after failure, keeping the die and retry rhythm in a compact retro format.
Fun fact: Meat Boy first appeared in a 2008 Flash game called Meat Boy before becoming the more famous console release Super Meat Boy.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Super Meat Boy TIC-80 Demake reprend l’esprit du jeu original dans une version miniature pensée pour la fantasy console TIC-80. Meat Boy traverse des niveaux courts et dangereux où chaque saut demande précision, vitesse et reprise immédiate après l’échec. Le jeu conserve l’idée centrale du die and retry, avec une action nerveuse adaptée à un format rétro très compact.
Fun fact : Le personnage de Meat Boy vient à l’origine d’un jeu Flash appelé Meat Boy, créé en 2008, avant de devenir la version plus connue sortie sur consoles.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Super Meat Boy TIC-80 Demake recupera el espíritu del juego original en una versión en miniatura creada para la fantasy console TIC-80. Meat Boy supera niveles cortos y peligrosos donde cada salto exige precisión, velocidad y reintentos inmediatos tras fallar, conservando el ritmo die and retry en formato retro compacto.
Dato curioso: Meat Boy apareció primero en un juego Flash de 2008 llamado Meat Boy, antes de convertirse en el lanzamiento de consola Super Meat Boy.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Super Meat Boy TIC-80 Demake riprende lo spirito del gioco originale in una versione in miniatura creata per la fantasy console TIC-80. Meat Boy attraversa livelli brevi e pericolosi dove ogni salto richiede precisione, velocità e tentativi immediati dopo l’errore, mantenendo il ritmo die and retry in formato retro compatto.
Curiosità: Meat Boy apparve prima in un gioco Flash del 2008 chiamato Meat Boy, prima di diventare la più celebre uscita su console Super Meat Boy.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Super Meat Boy TIC-80 Demake übernimmt den Geist des Originals in einer Miniaturversion für die Fantasy-Konsole TIC-80. Meat Boy durchquert kurze, gefährliche Level, in denen jeder Sprung Präzision, Tempo und sofortige Neustarts nach Fehlern verlangt, mit kompaktem Retro-Die-and-Retry-Rhythmus.
Interessante Tatsache: Meat Boy erschien zuerst 2008 in einem Flash-Spiel namens Meat Boy, bevor daraus die bekanntere Konsolenversion Super Meat Boy wurde.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Super Meat Boy TIC-80 Demake recupera o espírito do jogo original numa versão em miniatura criada para a fantasy console TIC-80. Meat Boy atravessa níveis curtos e perigosos onde cada salto exige precisão, velocidade e novas tentativas imediatas após o erro, mantendo o ritmo die and retry em formato retro compacto.
Curiosidade: Meat Boy apareceu primeiro num jogo Flash de 2008 chamado Meat Boy, antes de se tornar no lançamento de consola Super Meat Boy.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
