<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>Inspired by the Pico-8, the TIC-80 is a fantasy console under a free license (there is also a paid version with more options). It works with Android, HTML5 (in WebAssembly4), Linux, macOS and Windows platforms.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Inspirée du Pico-8, le TIC-80 est une fantasy console sous licence libre (il existe également une version payante avec plus d'options), . Elle fonctionne avec les plateformes Android, HTML5 (en WebAssembly4), Linux, macOS et Windows.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Die TIC-80 ist eine Fantasy-Konsole unter einer freien Lizenz (es gibt auch eine kostenpflichtige Version mit mehr Optionen), die vom Pico-8 inspiriert wurde. Sie funktioniert mit den Plattformen Android, HTML5 (in WebAssembly4), Linux, macOS und Windows.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Inspirada en el Pico-8, la TIC-80 es una consola de fantasía de código abierto (también hay una versión de pago con más opciones). Funciona con plataformas Android, HTML5 (en WebAssembly4), Linux, macOS y Windows.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Ispirato al Pico-8, il TIC-80 è una console fantasy open source (esiste anche una versione a pagamento con più opzioni). Funziona con le piattaforme Android, HTML5 (in WebAssembly4), Linux, macOS e Windows.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>Pico-8にインスパイアされたTIC-80は、オープンソースのファンタジーコンソールです（より多くのオプションを備えた有料版もあります）。Android、HTML5（WebAssembly4で）、Linux、macOS、Windowsプラットフォームで動作します。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>Geïnspireerd door de Pico-8 is de TIC-80 een open source fantasieconsole (er is ook een betaalde versie met meer opties). Het werkt met Android, HTML5 (in WebAssembly4), Linux, macOS en Windows platforms.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>Zainspirowany przez Pico-8, TIC-80 jest konsolą fantasy o otwartym kodzie źródłowym (istnieje również wersja płatna z większą ilością opcji). Działa z platformami Android, HTML5 (w WebAssembly4), Linux, macOS i Windows.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Inspirado no Pico-8, o TIC-80 é uma consola de fantasia de código aberto (há também uma versão paga com mais opções). Funciona com Android, HTML5 (em WebAssembly4), Linux, macOS e plataformas Windows.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>Вдохновленная Pico-8, TIC-80 - это фантазийная консоль с открытым исходным кодом (есть также платная версия с более широкими возможностями). Она работает на платформах Android, HTML5 (на WebAssembly4), Linux, macOS и Windows.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
