<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>Toaplan is a Japanese company created in 1984 which carries out its activity in the development of the video game and which closed in 1994. It is known for its innovative arcade games for the time, mainly shoot them up like Tiger Heli, Twin Cobra, Out Zone or Batsugun.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Toaplan est une entreprise japonaise créée en 1984 qui exerce son activité dans le développement du jeu vidéo et qui a fermé en 1994. Elle est connu pour ses jeux d'arcade novateurs pour l'époque, principalement des shoot them up comme Tiger Heli, Twin Cobra, Out Zone ou encore Batsugun.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Toaplan ist ein japanisches Unternehmen, das 1984 gegründet wurde, sich mit der Entwicklung von Videospielen beschäftigte und 1994 geschlossen wurde. Sie ist bekannt für ihre für die damalige Zeit innovativen Arcade-Spiele, hauptsächlich Shoot them up-Spiele wie Tiger Heli, Twin Cobra, Out Zone oder Batsugun.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Toaplan es una empresa japonesa creada en 1984 que se dedicaba al desarrollo de videojuegos y que cerró en 1994. Es conocida por sus juegos arcade innovadores para la época, principalmente de disparos como Tiger Heli, Twin Cobra, Out Zone o Batsugun.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Toaplan è un'azienda giapponese creata nel 1984, attiva nello sviluppo di videogiochi e chiusa nel 1994. È nota per i suoi giochi arcade innovativi per l'epoca, soprattutto sparatutto come Tiger Heli, Twin Cobra, Out Zone o Batsugun.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>トアプランは、1984年に設立され、ビデオゲームの開発で活躍した日本の会社で、1994年に閉鎖された。タイガーヘリ」「ツインコブラ」「アウトゾーン」「バツグン」など、当時としては斬新なシューティングゲームを中心としたアーケードゲームで知られています。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>Toaplan is een in 1984 opgericht Japans bedrijf dat zich bezighield met de ontwikkeling van videospelletjes en dat in 1994 werd gesloten. Het staat bekend om zijn innovatieve arcadespellen voor die tijd, voornamelijk schietspellen zoals Tiger Heli, Twin Cobra, Out Zone of Batsugun.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>Toaplan to japońska firma powstała w 1984 roku, która zajmowała się tworzeniem gier wideo i która została zamknięta w 1994 roku. Znana jest z innowacyjnych jak na tamte czasy gier zręcznościowych, głównie shoot them up jak Tiger Heli, Twin Cobra, Out Zone czy Batsugun.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>A Toaplan é uma empresa japonesa criada em 1984 que estava activa no desenvolvimento de jogos de vídeo e que encerrou em 1994. É conhecida pelos seus jogos de arcada inovadores da época, principalmente jogos de tiro como Tiger Heli, Twin Cobra, Out Zone ou Batsugun.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>Toaplan - это японская компания, созданная в 1984 году и занимавшаяся разработкой видеоигр, которая закрылась в 1994 году. Она известна своими инновационными для того времени аркадными играми, в основном стрелялками, такими как Tiger Heli, Twin Cobra, Out Zone или Batsugun.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Snow Bros. (1990)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>Nick is Tom's brother in Snow Bros., two snowmen fighting monsters through fixed-screen stages filled with platforms and traps. The game is built around enemies gradually covered in snow before being turned into huge balls that sweep away everything in their path, with fast action and cooperative gameplay that became an arcade classic.
Fun fact: Snow Bros. is often compared to Bubble Bobble for its fixed-screen gameplay and very accessible co-op mode.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Nick est le frère de Tom dans Snow Bros., deux bonshommes de neige chargés de combattre des monstres à travers une série de tableaux fixes remplis de plateformes et de pièges. Le jeu repose sur des ennemis recouverts progressivement de neige avant d’être transformés en énormes boules capables d’emporter tout sur leur passage, avec une action rapide et un gameplay coopératif devenu culte en arcade.
Fun fact : Snow Bros. est souvent comparé à Bubble Bobble pour son gameplay en écran fixe et son mode coopératif très accessible.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Nick es el hermano de Tom en Snow Bros., dos muñecos de nieve que combaten monstruos en pantallas fijas llenas de plataformas y trampas. El juego se basa en cubrir poco a poco a los enemigos con nieve antes de convertirlos en enormes bolas capaces de arrastrar todo a su paso, con acción rápida y un modo cooperativo que se volvió un clásico arcade.
Dato curioso: Snow Bros. suele compararse con Bubble Bobble por su jugabilidad de pantalla fija y su modo cooperativo muy accesible.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Nick è il fratello di Tom in Snow Bros., due pupazzi di neve impegnati a combattere mostri in schermate fisse piene di piattaforme e trappole. Il gioco ruota attorno a nemici ricoperti gradualmente di neve prima di trasformarli in enormi palle capaci di travolgere tutto, con azione rapida e un gameplay cooperativo diventato un classico arcade.
Curiosità: Snow Bros. viene spesso paragonato a Bubble Bobble per il gameplay a schermata fissa e la modalità cooperativa molto accessibile.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Nick ist Toms Bruder in Snow Bros., zwei Schneemänner, die in festen Bildschirmen voller Plattformen und Fallen gegen Monster kämpfen. Das Spiel basiert darauf, Gegner nach und nach mit Schnee zu bedecken, bevor sie zu riesigen Kugeln werden, die alles mitreißen, mit schneller Action und kooperativem Gameplay, das zum Arcade-Klassiker wurde.
Interessante Tatsache: Snow Bros. wird wegen seines festen Bildschirmaufbaus und des leicht zugänglichen Koop-Modus oft mit Bubble Bobble verglichen.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Nick é o irmão de Tom em Snow Bros., dois bonecos de neve que enfrentam monstros em ecrãs fixos cheios de plataformas e armadilhas. O jogo gira em torno de cobrir os inimigos com neve até os transformar em enormes bolas capazes de levar tudo pelo caminho, com ação rápida e uma jogabilidade cooperativa que se tornou clássica nas arcades.
Curiosidade: Snow Bros. é muitas vezes comparado a Bubble Bobble pela jogabilidade em ecrã fixo e pelo modo cooperativo muito acessível.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
