<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>Universal Entertainment Corporation is a Japanese manufacturer of pachinko, slot machines, arcade games and other gaming products, as well as a video game publisher. It is also the licensee of the Shadow Hearts video game franchise. </text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Universal Entertainment Corporation est un fabricant japonais de pachinko, de machines à sous, de jeux d'arcade et d'autres produits de jeu, ainsi qu'un éditeur de jeux vidéo. Il est également le détenteur de la licence de la franchise de jeux vidéo Shadow Hearts.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Die Universal Entertainment Corporation ist ein japanischer Hersteller von Pachinko, Spielautomaten, Arcade-Spielen und anderen Glücksspielprodukten sowie ein Videospielverlag. Sie ist außerdem der Lizenznehmer des Videospiel-Franchise Shadow Hearts. </text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Universal Entertainment Corporation es un fabricante japonés de pachinko, máquinas tragaperras, juegos arcade y otros productos de juego, así como un editor de videojuegos. También es licenciataria de la franquicia de videojuegos Shadow Hearts. </text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Universal Entertainment Corporation è un produttore giapponese di pachinko, slot machine, giochi arcade e altri prodotti di gioco, nonché editore di videogiochi. È anche licenziataria della serie di videogiochi Shadow Hearts. </text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>株式会社ユニバーサルエンターテインメントは、パチンコ、スロットマシン、アーケードゲーム、その他のゲーム製品の日本のメーカーであり、ビデオゲームのパブリッシャーでもあります。また、ビデオゲームフランチャイズ「シャドウハーツ」のライセンシーである。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>Universal Entertainment Corporation is een Japanse fabrikant van pachinko, speelautomaten, arcadespellen en andere spelproducten, alsook een uitgever van videospellen. Het is ook de licentiehouder van het videospel Shadow Hearts. </text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>Universal Entertainment Corporation to japoński producent pachinko, automatów do gry, gier zręcznościowych i innych produktów do gier, a także wydawca gier wideo. Jest również licencjobiorcą franczyzy gier wideo Shadow Hearts. </text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>A Universal Entertainment Corporation é um fabricante japonês de pachinko, slot machines, jogos arcade e outros produtos de jogos, bem como uma editora de jogos de vídeo. É também o licenciado da franquia de jogos de vídeo da Shadow Hearts. </text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>Universal Entertainment Corporation - японский производитель пачинко, игровых автоматов, аркадных игр и других игровых продуктов, а также издатель видеоигр. Она также является лицензиатом франшизы видеоигр Shadow Hearts. </text>
</text>


<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Mr. Do! (1982)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>Mr. Do is a clown armed with a bouncing ball, moving through mazes filled with monsters and fruit to collect. The game mixes quick thinking, precise movement and risk management, with enemies that can be crushed under large apples falling from above. Its fast pace and scoring depth made it one of the major arcade hits of the early 1980s.
Fun fact: Mr. Do! was one of the first arcade games to seriously compete with Pac-Man’s success in arcades.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Mr. Do est un clown armé d’une balle rebondissante parcourant des labyrinthes remplis de monstres et de fruits à récupérer. Le jeu mélange réflexion rapide, déplacements précis et gestion du risque, avec la possibilité d’écraser les ennemis sous de grosses pommes tombant depuis les niveaux supérieurs. Son rythme nerveux et son scoring élaboré en ont fait l’un des grands succès arcade du début des années 80.
Fun fact : Mr. Do! a été l’un des premiers jeux arcade à concurrencer sérieusement le succès de Pac-Man dans les salles.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Mr. Do es un payaso armado con una pelota rebotadora que recorre laberintos llenos de monstruos y frutas por recoger. El juego combina reflejos, movimientos precisos y gestión del riesgo, con la posibilidad de aplastar enemigos bajo grandes manzanas que caen desde los niveles superiores. Su ritmo rápido y su sistema de puntuación lo convirtieron en un gran éxito arcade de principios de los 80.
Dato curioso: Mr. Do! fue uno de los primeros arcades en competir seriamente con el éxito de Pac-Man en los salones.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Mr. Do è un clown armato di una palla rimbalzante che attraversa labirinti pieni di mostri e frutti da raccogliere. Il gioco unisce riflessi rapidi, movimenti precisi e gestione del rischio, con la possibilità di schiacciare i nemici sotto grandi mele che cadono dai livelli superiori. Il suo ritmo veloce e il sistema di punteggio lo resero un grande successo arcade dei primi anni 80.
Curiosità: Mr. Do! fu uno dei primi arcade a competere seriamente con il successo di Pac-Man nelle sale giochi.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Mr. Do ist ein Clown mit einem springenden Ball, der Labyrinthe voller Monster und Früchte durchquert. Das Spiel verbindet schnelle Reaktionen, präzise Bewegungen und Risikomanagement, wobei Gegner von großen Äpfeln aus höheren Ebenen zerquetscht werden können. Sein hohes Tempo und das ausgefeilte Punktesystem machten es zu einem großen Arcade-Erfolg der frühen 80er.
Interessante Tatsache: Mr. Do! war eines der ersten Arcade-Spiele, das ernsthaft mit dem Erfolg von Pac-Man in Spielhallen konkurrierte.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Mr. Do é um palhaço armado com uma bola saltitante que percorre labirintos cheios de monstros e frutas para recolher. O jogo mistura reflexos rápidos, movimentos precisos e gestão de risco, com a possibilidade de esmagar inimigos sob grandes maçãs que caem dos níveis superiores. O ritmo intenso e a pontuação elaborada fizeram dele um grande sucesso arcade do início dos anos 80.
Curiosidade: Mr. Do! foi um dos primeiros arcades a competir seriamente com o sucesso de Pac-Man nos salões.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
