<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>The Uzebox is an open source video game console with minimalist retro graphics. It is based on an 8-bit AVR microcontroller, manufactured by the company Atmel. The particularity of the system is the use of an interrupted conducted core, and that it has no framebuffer. The games can be developed in C. </text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>La Uzebox est une console de jeu vidéo open source aux graphismes rétro minimalistes. Elle est basée sur un microcontrôleur AVR 8-bit, fabriqué par la société Atmel. La particularité du système est l'utilisation d'un noyau conduit interrompu, et qu'il n'a pas de framebuffer. Les jeux sont développables en C. </text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Die Uzebox ist eine Open-Source-Videospielkonsole mit minimalistischer Retro-Grafik. Sie basiert auf einem 8-Bit AVR-Mikrocontroller, der von der Firma Atmel hergestellt wird. Die Besonderheit des Systems ist die Verwendung eines unterbrochenen Conduit-Kernels und dass es keinen Framebuffer hat. Die Spiele sind in C entwickelbar. </text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>La Uzebox es una videoconsola de código abierto con gráficos retro minimalistas. Se basa en un microcontrolador AVR de 8 bits, fabricado por la empresa Atmel. La particularidad del sistema es el uso de un núcleo conducido interrumpido, y que no tiene framebuffer. Los juegos pueden desarrollarse en C. </text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Uzebox è una console per videogiochi open source con una grafica retrò minimalista. È basata su un microcontrollore AVR a 8 bit, prodotto dalla società Atmel. La particolarità del sistema è l'uso di un core a conduzione interrotta e l'assenza di framebuffer. I giochi possono essere sviluppati in C. </text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>Uzeboxは、最小限のレトロなグラフィックを持つオープンソースのビデオゲーム機です。Atmel社製の8ビットAVRマイクロコントローラをベースにしています。このシステムの特徴は、割り込み伝導コアを使用していることと、フレームバッファがないことです。ゲームはC言語で開発することができます。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>De Uzebox is een open source videospelconsole met minimalistische retro graphics. Hij is gebaseerd op een 8-bit AVR microcontroller, vervaardigd door het bedrijf Atmel. De bijzonderheid van het systeem is het gebruik van een onderbroken geleide kern, en dat het geen framebuffer heeft. De spellen kunnen worden ontwikkeld in C. </text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>Uzebox to opensource'owa konsola do gier wideo z minimalistyczną grafiką retro. Oparta jest na 8-bitowym mikrokontrolerze AVR, wyprodukowanym przez firmę Atmel. Specyfiką układu jest użycie przerwanego rdzenia przewodzącego oraz to, że nie posiada on framebuffera. Gry mogą być tworzone w języku C. </text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>A Uzebox é uma consola de videojogos de código aberto com gráficos retro minimalistas. Baseia-se num microcontrolador AVR de 8 bits, fabricado pela empresa Atmel. A particularidade do sistema é a utilização de um núcleo conduzido interrompido, e que não tem tampão de fotogramas. Os jogos podem ser desenvolvidos em C. </text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>Uzebox - это игровая консоль с открытым исходным кодом и минималистичной ретро-графикой. Она основана на 8-битном микроконтроллере AVR, производимом компанией Atmel. Особенностью системы является использование ядра с прерыванием и отсутствие фреймбуфера. Игры могут быть разработаны на языке C. </text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Tron (2010)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>The character of Tron evokes the digital imagination of the 1982 cult film, with virtual arenas, glowing lines and light cycle battles. On Uzebox, the game turns this idea into a simple, direct competitive duel, where each player must force the other to hit a wall, the edge of the screen or the trail left by the vehicles.
Fun fact: The light cycle concept in Tron inspired many multiplayer games based on territory control and avoidance.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Le personnage de Tron renvoie à l’imaginaire numérique du film culte de 1982, entre arènes virtuelles, lignes lumineuses et affrontements de light cycles. Sur Uzebox, le jeu reprend cette idée sous forme de duel compétitif simple et direct, où chaque joueur doit pousser l’autre à heurter un mur, le bord de l’écran ou la traînée laissée par les véhicules.
Fun fact : Le concept des light cycles dans Tron a inspiré de nombreux jeux multijoueurs basés sur le principe de territoire et d’évitement.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>El personaje de Tron remite al imaginario digital de la película de culto de 1982, con arenas virtuales, líneas luminosas y duelos de light cycles. En Uzebox, el juego transforma esta idea en un duelo competitivo simple y directo, donde cada jugador debe hacer que el otro choque contra un muro, el borde de la pantalla o la estela de los vehículos.
Dato curioso: El concepto de los light cycles de Tron inspiró muchos juegos multijugador basados en el control del territorio y la evasión.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Il personaggio di Tron richiama l’immaginario digitale del film cult del 1982, tra arene virtuali, linee luminose e scontri tra light cycle. Su Uzebox, il gioco riprende questa idea come un duello competitivo semplice e diretto, in cui ogni giocatore deve spingere l’altro contro un muro, il bordo dello schermo o la scia lasciata dai veicoli.
Curiosità: Il concetto delle light cycle di Tron ha ispirato molti giochi multigiocatore basati su territorio ed evitamento.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Die Figur Tron verweist auf die digitale Vorstellungswelt des Kultfilms von 1982, mit virtuellen Arenen, leuchtenden Linien und Kämpfen zwischen Light Cycles. Auf Uzebox wird daraus ein einfacher, direkter Wettkampf, bei dem jeder Spieler den anderen gegen eine Wand, den Bildschirmrand oder die Spur der Fahrzeuge drängen muss.
Interessante Tatsache: Das Light-Cycle-Konzept aus Tron inspirierte viele Mehrspielerspiele, die auf Gebietskontrolle und Ausweichen basieren.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>O personagem Tron remete ao imaginário digital do filme de culto de 1982, com arenas virtuais, linhas luminosas e duelos de light cycles. Na Uzebox, o jogo transforma essa ideia num duelo competitivo simples e direto, em que cada jogador deve levar o outro a bater num muro, na borda do ecrã ou no rasto deixado pelos veículos.
Curiosidade: O conceito dos light cycles de Tron inspirou muitos jogos multijogador baseados em território e esquiva.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
