<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>The Interton VC4000 is an 8-bit cartridge video game console released in Germany. The console is not well known outside Germany, but many systems with compatible software can be found in several European countries. </text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>L'Interton VC4000 est une console de jeux vidéo 8-bits à cartouches sortie en Allemagne. La console est assez peu connue en dehors de l'Allemagne, mais de nombreux systèmes aux logiciels compatibles peuvent être trouvés dans plusieurs pays européens.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Der Interton VC4000 ist eine 8-Bit-Videospielkonsole mit Kassetten, die in Deutschland veröffentlicht wurde. Die Konsole ist außerhalb Deutschlands recht unbekannt, aber viele Systeme mit kompatibler Software sind in mehreren europäischen Ländern zu finden. </text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>La Interton VC4000 es una videoconsola de cartuchos de 8 bits lanzada en Alemania. La consola no es muy conocida fuera de Alemania, pero se pueden encontrar muchos sistemas con software compatible en varios países europeos. </text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Interton VC4000 è una console per videogiochi a cartuccia a 8 bit rilasciata in Germania. La console non è molto conosciuta al di fuori della Germania, ma si possono trovare molti sistemi con software compatibile in diversi paesi europei. </text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>インタートンVC4000は、ドイツで発売された8ビットカートリッジ式ビデオゲーム機である。ドイツ以外ではあまり知られていないゲーム機ですが、ヨーロッパ数カ国では互換ソフトを搭載したシステムが多く見られます。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>De Interton VC4000 is een in Duitsland uitgebrachte 8-bit spelcomputer met cartridges. De console is niet bekend buiten Duitsland, maar in verschillende Europese landen zijn veel systemen met compatibele software te vinden. </text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>Interton VC4000 to 8-bitowa konsola do gier wideo na kartridżach wydana w Niemczech. Konsola nie jest dobrze znana poza Niemcami, ale wiele systemów z kompatybilnym oprogramowaniem można znaleźć w kilku krajach europejskich. </text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>O Interton VC4000 é uma consola de videojogos de 8-bit baseada em cartuchos lançada na Alemanha. A consola não é bem conhecida fora da Alemanha, mas muitos sistemas com software compatível podem ser encontrados em vários países europeus. </text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>Interton VC4000 - это 8-битная игровая консоль на картриджах, выпущенная в Германии. Консоль не очень известна за пределами Германии, но многие системы с совместимым программным обеспечением можно найти в нескольких европейских странах. </text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Soccer (1981)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>Soccer brings football to the very simple format of the Video Computer VC4000, with readable shapes, direct movement and action focused on the duel in front of goal. The goalkeeper figurine reflects this minimal logic: ready stance, eyes on the shot and a sober silhouette faithful to the graphic limits of early cartridge consoles.
Fun fact: The VC4000 offered around forty different cartridges, all compatible with many clone consoles, making it a surprisingly open system for its time.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Soccer adapte le football au format très simple du Video Computer VC4000, avec des formes lisibles, des déplacements directs et une action centrée sur le duel devant le but. La figurine de gardien traduit cette logique minimale : posture prête à réagir, regard vers le tir et silhouette sobre, fidèle aux limites graphiques des premières consoles à cartouches.
Fun fact : Le VC4000 proposait une quarantaine de cassettes différentes, toutes compatibles avec de nombreuses consoles clones, ce qui en faisait un système étonnamment ouvert pour l’époque.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Soccer adapta el fútbol al formato muy simple del Video Computer VC4000, con formas legibles, movimientos directos y una acción centrada en el duelo frente a la portería. La figura del guardameta refleja esa lógica mínima: postura lista para reaccionar, mirada hacia el disparo y una silueta sobria, fiel a los límites gráficos de las primeras consolas de cartuchos.
Dato curioso: El VC4000 ofrecía unas cuarenta cassettes diferentes, todas compatibles con muchas consolas clónicas, lo que lo convertía en un sistema sorprendentemente abierto para su época.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Soccer adatta il calcio al formato molto semplice del Video Computer VC4000, con forme leggibili, movimenti diretti e un’azione centrata sul duello davanti alla porta. La statuetta del portiere riflette questa logica minima: posa pronta a reagire, sguardo verso il tiro e una silhouette sobria, fedele ai limiti grafici delle prime console a cartucce.
Curiosità: Il VC4000 offriva circa quaranta cassette diverse, tutte compatibili con molte console clone, rendendolo un sistema sorprendentemente aperto per l’epoca.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Soccer überträgt Fußball auf das sehr einfache Format des Video Computer VC4000, mit klar lesbaren Formen, direkter Bewegung und einem Spielgeschehen rund um das Duell vor dem Tor. Die Torwartfigur greift diese reduzierte Logik auf: reaktionsbereite Haltung, Blick zum Schuss und eine schlichte Silhouette, passend zu den grafischen Grenzen früher Modul-Konsolen.
Interessante Tatsache: Für den VC4000 gab es rund vierzig verschiedene Kassetten, die mit vielen Klon-Konsolen kompatibel waren, was ihn für seine Zeit erstaunlich offen machte.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Soccer adapta o futebol ao formato muito simples do Video Computer VC4000, com formas legíveis, movimentos diretos e uma ação centrada no duelo diante da baliza. A figura do guarda-redes traduz essa lógica mínima: postura pronta a reagir, olhar para o remate e uma silhueta sóbria, fiel aos limites gráficos das primeiras consolas de cartuchos.
Curiosidade: O VC4000 oferecia cerca de quarenta cassetes diferentes, todas compatíveis com muitas consolas clone, tornando-o um sistema surpreendentemente aberto para a época.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
