<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>Virtua Fighter is a series of 3D fighting games developed by SEGA, which pioneered the genre in 1993. It stands out for its realism, technical gameplay and three-button fighting system: fist, foot and guard. Each opus improves the graphics and fluidity of combat, influencing many other franchises. Its strategic approach has made it a benchmark for fighting game enthusiasts.</text>
<text lang="fr">Virtua Fighter est une série de jeux de combat 3D développée par SEGA, pionnière du genre dès 1993. Elle se distingue par son réalisme, son gameplay technique et son système de combat basé sur trois boutons  poing, pied et garde. Chaque opus améliore les graphismes et la fluidité des combats, influençant de nombreuses autres franchises. Son approche stratégique en a fait une référence pour les amateurs de jeux de combat.</text>
<text lang="es">Virtua Fighter es una serie de juegos de lucha en 3D desarrollada por SEGA, pionera del género desde 1993. Destaca por su realismo, su jugabilidad técnica y su sistema de tres botones: puño, patada y guardia. Cada entrega mejora los gráficos y la fluidez de los combates, influyendo en muchas otras franquicias. Su enfoque estratégico la convirtió en una referencia para los aficionados.</text>
<text lang="it">Virtua Fighter è una serie di giochi di combattimento 3D sviluppata da SEGA, pioniera del genere dal 1993. Si distingue per realismo, gameplay tecnico e sistema a tre pulsanti: pugno, calcio e guardia. Ogni capitolo migliora grafica e fluidità degli scontri, influenzando molte altre serie. Il suo approccio strategico l’ha resa un riferimento per gli appassionati.</text>
<text lang="de">Virtua Fighter ist eine von SEGA entwickelte 3D-Kampfspielreihe, die das Genre seit 1993 mitgeprägt hat. Sie zeichnet sich durch Realismus, technisches Gameplay und ein Drei-Tasten-System aus: Schlag, Tritt und Block. Jeder Teil verbesserte Grafik und Kampffluss und beeinflusste viele andere Serien. Ihr strategischer Ansatz machte sie zu einer Referenz für Fans.</text>
<text lang="pt">Virtua Fighter é uma série de jogos de luta em 3D desenvolvida pela SEGA, pioneira do gênero desde 1993. Destaca-se pelo realismo, pela jogabilidade técnica e pelo sistema de três botões: soco, chute e defesa. Cada jogo melhora os gráficos e a fluidez dos combates, influenciando muitas franquias. Sua abordagem estratégica virou referência entre os fãs.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Virtua Fighter (Arcade, 1993)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>Sarah Bryant is a skilled martial artist with a fast style based on jeet kune do. Kidnapped and manipulated by a criminal organization, she fights to recover her freedom and identity. Her combat relies on fluid combos and strong mobility, making her a dangerous opponent able to unsettle rivals with speed and precision. Fun fact: Sarah was one of the first playable female characters in a 3D fighting game, marking an important step for the genre.</text>
<text lang="fr">Sarah Bryant est une combattante experte en arts martiaux, spécialisée dans un style rapide basé sur le jeet kune do. Enlevée puis manipulée par une organisation criminelle, elle lutte pour retrouver sa liberté et son identité. Son style repose sur des enchaînements fluides et une grande mobilité, faisant d’elle une adversaire redoutable par sa vitesse et sa précision. Fun fact : Sarah a été l’un des premiers personnages féminins jouables dans un jeu de combat en 3D, marquant une étape importante pour le genre.</text>
<text lang="es">Sarah Bryant es una experta en artes marciales, especializada en un estilo rápido basado en el jeet kune do. Secuestrada y manipulada por una organización criminal, lucha por recuperar su libertad e identidad. Su estilo usa combos fluidos y gran movilidad, convirtiéndola en una rival peligrosa por su velocidad y precisión. Dato curioso: Sarah fue una de las primeras mujeres jugables en un juego de lucha en 3D.</text>
<text lang="it">Sarah Bryant è un’esperta di arti marziali, specializzata in uno stile rapido basato sul jeet kune do. Rapita e manipolata da un’organizzazione criminale, combatte per ritrovare libertà e identità. Il suo stile usa combo fluide e grande mobilità, rendendola una rivale pericolosa per velocità e precisione. Curiosità: Sarah fu tra i primi personaggi femminili giocabili in un picchiaduro 3D.</text>
<text lang="de">Sarah Bryant ist eine erfahrene Kampfkünstlerin mit einem schnellen Stil, der auf Jeet Kune Do basiert. Von einer kriminellen Organisation entführt und manipuliert, kämpft sie um Freiheit und Identität. Ihr Stil setzt auf flüssige Kombinationen und hohe Beweglichkeit, was sie durch Tempo und Präzision gefährlich macht. Interessante Tatsache: Sarah war eine der ersten spielbaren Frauen in einem 3D-Kampfspiel.</text>
<text lang="pt">Sarah Bryant é uma especialista em artes marciais, com um estilo rápido baseado no jeet kune do. Sequestrada e manipulada por uma organização criminosa, luta para recuperar sua liberdade e identidade. Seu combate usa sequências fluidas e grande mobilidade, tornando-a perigosa pela velocidade e precisão. Curiosidade: Sarah foi uma das primeiras personagens femininas jogáveis em um jogo de luta 3D.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
