<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>Wonder Boy is a series of games published by SEGA, mixing platformers and action-RPGs. Beginning in 1986 as a scrolling action game, the series evolved into richer adventures with weapons, transformations and quests. It stands out for its colorful worlds, varied gameplay and influence on other titles. Several remakes and sequels have modernized the franchise while retaining its retro charm.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Wonder Boy est une série de jeux publiée par SEGA, mélangeant plateformes et action-RPG. Débutant en 1986 comme un jeu d'action à défilement, la série évolue vers des aventures plus riches avec des armes, transformations et quêtes. Elle se distingue par ses mondes colorés, son gameplay varié et son influence sur d’autres titres. Plusieurs remakes et suites ont modernisé la franchise tout en conservant son charme rétro.</text>
</text>


<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Wonder Boy es una serie publicada por SEGA, que mezcla plataformas y acción RPG. Comenzó en 1986 como un juego de acción de desplazamiento y evolucionó hacia aventuras más ricas con armas, transformaciones y misiones. Destaca por sus mundos coloridos, su jugabilidad variada y su influencia en otros títulos. Varios remakes y secuelas modernizaron la franquicia conservando su encanto retro.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Wonder Boy è una serie pubblicata da SEGA, che unisce platform e action RPG. Nata nel 1986 come gioco d’azione a scorrimento, si è evoluta in avventure più ricche con armi, trasformazioni e missioni. Si distingue per mondi colorati, gameplay vario e influenza su altri titoli. Diversi remake e sequel hanno modernizzato la serie mantenendo il suo fascino retrò.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Wonder Boy ist eine von SEGA veröffentlichte Spielreihe, die Plattformspiel und Action-RPG verbindet. Sie begann 1986 als scrollendes Actionspiel und entwickelte sich zu reicheren Abenteuern mit Waffen, Verwandlungen und Quests. Die Reihe fällt durch farbenfrohe Welten, abwechslungsreiches Gameplay und ihren Einfluss auf andere Titel auf. Mehrere Remakes und Fortsetzungen modernisierten sie mit Retro-Charme.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Wonder Boy é uma série publicada pela SEGA, misturando plataforma e ação RPG. Começou em 1986 como um jogo de ação com rolagem e evoluiu para aventuras mais ricas com armas, transformações e missões. Destaca-se pelos mundos coloridos, pela jogabilidade variada e pela influência em outros títulos. Remakes e sequências modernizaram a franquia mantendo seu charme retrô.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Wonder Boy in Monster Land (Arcade, 1987)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>Blending platforming and action RPG elements, Wonder Boy fights monsters and bosses while improving his equipment. His simple look contrasts with a demanding adventure, remembered for its mix of progression and exploration. Fun fact: Wonder Boy in Monster Land helped bring RPG elements into platform games, influencing many later titles.</text>
<text lang="fr">À mi-chemin entre plateforme et action-RPG, Wonder Boy progresse en affrontant monstres et boss tout en améliorant son équipement. Son apparence simple contraste avec une aventure exigeante, devenue une référence pour son mélange de progression et d’exploration. Fun fact : Wonder Boy in Monster Land est l’un des premiers jeux à introduire des éléments de RPG dans un jeu de plateforme, influençant de nombreux titres par la suite.</text>
<text lang="es">A medio camino entre plataformas y acción RPG, avanza luchando contra monstruos y jefes mientras mejora su equipo. Su aspecto sencillo contrasta con una aventura exigente, recordada por mezclar progresión y exploración. Dato curioso: Wonder Boy in Monster Land ayudó a introducir elementos de RPG en los juegos de plataformas.</text>
<text lang="it">A metà tra platform e action RPG, avanza affrontando mostri e boss mentre migliora l’equipaggiamento. Il suo aspetto semplice contrasta con un’avventura impegnativa, ricordata per il mix di progressione ed esplorazione. Curiosità: Wonder Boy in Monster Land contribuì a portare elementi RPG nei platform.</text>
<text lang="de">Zwischen Plattformspiel und Action-RPG kämpft er gegen Monster und Bosse und verbessert seine Ausrüstung. Sein schlichtes Aussehen steht im Kontrast zu einem anspruchsvollen Abenteuer voller Fortschritt und Erkundung. Interessante Tatsache: Wonder Boy in Monster Land brachte frühe RPG-Elemente in Plattformspiele.</text>
<text lang="pt">Entre plataforma e ação RPG, avança enfrentando monstros e chefes enquanto melhora seu equipamento. Seu visual simples contrasta com uma aventura exigente, lembrada pela mistura de progressão e exploração. Curiosidade: Wonder Boy in Monster Land ajudou a levar elementos de RPG aos jogos de plataforma.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
