<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>The Sharp X68000 is a personal computer marketed in Japan. The first model used a 10 MHz Motorola 68000 microprocessor, with 1 megabyte of RAM and no hard disk. The latest model, launched in 1993, had a Motorola 68030 at 25 MHz, with 4 MB of RAM and an optional 80 MB SCSI hard disk.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Le Sharp X68000 est un ordinateur personnel commercialisé au Japon. Le premier modèle utilisait un microprocesseur Motorola 68000 à 10 MHz, avec 1 mégaoctet de mémoire vive et aucun disque dur. Le dernier modèle, lancé en 1993, avait un Motorola 68030 à 25 MHz, avec 4 Mio de mémoire vive et un disque dur SCSI de 80 Mo en option.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Der Sharp X68000 ist ein in Japan vertriebener Personal Computer. Das erste Modell verwendete einen Motorola 68000 Mikroprozessor mit 10 MHz, 1 Megabyte RAM und keine Festplatte. Das letzte Modell, das 1993 auf den Markt kam, hatte einen Motorola 68030 mit 25 MHz, 4 Mio. RAM und eine optionale 80-MB-SCSI-Festplatte.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>El Sharp X68000 es un ordenador personal comercializado en Japón. El primer modelo utilizaba un microprocesador Motorola 68000 a 10 MHz, con 1 megabyte de RAM y sin disco duro. El último modelo, lanzado en 1993, tenía un Motorola 68030 a 25 MHz, con 4 MB de RAM y un disco duro SCSI opcional de 80 MB.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Lo Sharp X68000 è un personal computer commercializzato in Giappone. Il primo modello utilizzava un microprocessore Motorola 68000 a 10 MHz, con 1 megabyte di RAM e nessun disco rigido. L'ultimo modello, lanciato nel 1993, aveva un Motorola 68030 a 25 MHz, con 4 MB di RAM e un disco rigido SCSI opzionale da 80 MB.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>シャープX68000は、日本で販売されたパーソナルコンピュータである。最初のモデルは10MHzのモトローラ68000マイクロプロセッサーを使用し、1メガバイトのRAMとハードディスクを備えていなかった。1993年に発売された最新モデルは、25MHzのモトローラ68030を搭載し、4MBのRAMとオプションで80MBのSCSIハードディスクを搭載しています。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>De Sharp X68000 is een personal computer die in Japan op de markt werd gebracht. Het eerste model gebruikte een 10 MHz Motorola 68000 microprocessor, met 1 megabyte RAM en geen harde schijf. Het laatste model, gelanceerd in 1993, had een Motorola 68030 op 25 MHz, met 4 MB RAM en een optionele 80 MB SCSI harde schijf.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>Sharp X68000 to komputer osobisty sprzedawany w Japonii. Pierwszy model wykorzystywał mikroprocesor Motorola 68000 o częstotliwości 10 MHz, z 1 megabajtem pamięci RAM i bez twardego dysku. Ostatni model, wprowadzony na rynek w 1993 roku, miał Motorolę 68030 o częstotliwości 25 MHz, z 4 MB pamięci RAM i opcjonalnym dyskiem twardym 80 MB SCSI.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>O Sharp X68000 é um computador pessoal comercializado no Japão. O primeiro modelo utilizou um microprocessador Motorola 68000 de 10 MHz, com 1 megabyte de RAM e sem disco rígido. O último modelo, lançado em 1993, tinha um Motorola 68030 a 25 MHz, com 4 MB de RAM e um disco rígido SCSI de 80 MB opcional.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>Sharp X68000 - персональный компьютер, продававшийся в Японии. В первой модели использовался микропроцессор Motorola 68000 с частотой 10 МГц, оперативная память составляла 1 мегабайт, жесткий диск отсутствовал. Последняя модель, выпущенная в 1993 году, имела 25 МГц Motorola 68030, 4 МБ оперативной памяти и дополнительный жесткий диск SCSI объемом 80 МБ.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>
