<theme>
    <formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
    <view name="system">

        <text name="system_description" extra="true">
            <text>The Sharp X68000 is a Japanese home computer released in 1987 by Sharp. Known for its powerful hardware and arcade-perfect ports, it became a favorite platform for developers, especially for action and shooting games. Its architecture closely resembles arcade systems of the time.</text>
        </text>
        <text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
            <text>Le Sharp X68000 est un ordinateur japonais sorti en 1987 par Sharp. Réputé pour sa puissance et ses adaptations fidèles des jeux d’arcade, il devient une plateforme privilégiée pour les jeux d’action et de tir. Son architecture est très proche des systèmes d’arcade de l’époque.</text>
        </text>
        <text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
            <text>El Sharp X68000 es un ordenador japonés lanzado en 1987 por Sharp. Conocido por su potencia y conversiones fieles de arcade, se convirtió en una plataforma destacada para juegos de acción y disparos. Su arquitectura es muy cercana a los sistemas arcade de la época.</text>
        </text>
        <text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
            <text>Lo Sharp X68000 è un computer giapponese rilasciato nel 1987 da Sharp. Conosciuto per la sua potenza e per le conversioni arcade fedeli, è diventato una piattaforma importante per giochi d’azione e sparatutto. La sua architettura è molto simile ai sistemi arcade dell’epoca.</text>
        </text>
        <text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
            <text>Der Sharp X68000 ist ein japanischer Heimcomputer, der 1987 von Sharp veröffentlicht wurde. Bekannt für seine Leistung und originalgetreuen Arcade-Umsetzungen, wurde er zu einer wichtigen Plattform für Action- und Shoot'em-up-Spiele. Seine Architektur ähnelt stark den Arcade-Systemen der Zeit.</text>
        </text>
        <text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
            <text>O Sharp X68000 é um computador japonês lançado em 1987 pela Sharp. Conhecido pelo seu desempenho e conversões fiéis de arcade, tornou-se uma plataforma importante para jogos de ação e tiro. A sua arquitetura é muito semelhante aos sistemas arcade da época.</text>
        </text>

        <text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
            <text>&#160;&#160;Castlevania (1993)&#160;&#160;</text>
        </text>

        <text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
            <text>Castlevania on Sharp X68000 is an expanded version of the original game with reworked environments, higher difficulty and a darker gothic atmosphere. The player takes on a vampire hunter facing classic creatures in demanding stages requiring precise jumps and attacks.
Fun fact: This X68000 version later served as the basis for Castlevania Chronicles on PlayStation, reusing its visuals and structure.</text>
        </text>

        <text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
            <text>Castlevania sur Sharp X68000 propose une version étendue du premier épisode avec des environnements retravaillés, une difficulté plus marquée et une ambiance gothique renforcée. Le joueur incarne un chasseur de vampires affrontant des créatures classiques dans des niveaux exigeants où chaque saut et attaque demandent précision.
Fun fact : Cette version X68000 a servi de base au remake Castlevania Chronicles sur PlayStation, qui reprend directement ses graphismes et sa structure.</text>
        </text>

        <text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
            <text>Castlevania en Sharp X68000 ofrece una versión ampliada del juego original con entornos rediseñados, mayor dificultad y una atmósfera gótica más marcada. El jugador controla a un cazador de vampiros enfrentándose a criaturas clásicas en niveles exigentes que requieren precisión.
Dato curioso: Esta versión X68000 sirvió de base para Castlevania Chronicles en PlayStation, reutilizando sus gráficos y estructura.</text>
        </text>

        <text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
            <text>Castlevania su Sharp X68000 propone una versione ampliata del gioco originale con ambienti rielaborati, maggiore difficoltà e un’atmosfera gotica più intensa. Il giocatore controlla un cacciatore di vampiri affrontando creature classiche in livelli impegnativi.
Curiosità: Questa versione X68000 ha servito da base per Castlevania Chronicles su PlayStation, riutilizzandone grafica e struttura.</text>
        </text>

        <text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
            <text>Castlevania auf dem Sharp X68000 ist eine erweiterte Version des Originals mit überarbeiteten Umgebungen, höherem Schwierigkeitsgrad und stärkerer gotischer Atmosphäre. Der Spieler steuert einen Vampirjäger in anspruchsvollen Levels.
Interessante Tatsache: Diese Version diente als Grundlage für Castlevania Chronicles auf PlayStation und übernahm Grafik und Struktur.</text>
        </text>

        <text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
            <text>Castlevania no Sharp X68000 apresenta uma versão expandida do jogo original com cenários retrabalhados, maior dificuldade e uma atmosfera gótica mais intensa. O jogador controla um caçador de vampiros em níveis exigentes.
Curiosidade: Esta versão serviu de base para Castlevania Chronicles na PlayStation, reutilizando gráficos e estrutura.</text>
        </text>

    </view>
</theme>