<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>The first steps of microsoft in the sector of video game consoles. It is part of the sixth generation whose main competitors are Sony's PlayStation 2, Nintendo's Gamecube and Sega's Dreamcast. The console has a catalog of more than 825 games, with series like Halo, Star Wars and Fable.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Les premiers pas de microsoft dans le secteur des consoles de jeux video. Elle fait partie de la sixième génération dont les principales concurrentes sont la PlayStation 2 de Sony, la Gamecube de Nintendo et la Dreamcast de Sega. La console possède un catalogue de plus de 825 jeux, avec des séries comme Halo, Star Wars et Fable.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Die ersten Schritte von microsoft im Bereich der Videospielkonsolen. Sie gehört zur sechsten Generation, deren Hauptkonkurrenten die PlayStation 2 von Sony, der Gamecube von Nintendo und die Dreamcast von Sega sind. Die Konsole verfügt über einen Katalog mit über 825 Spielen, darunter Serien wie Halo, Star Wars und Fable.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Primeros pasos de Microsoft en el sector de las consolas de videojuegos. Forma parte de la sexta generación, cuyos principales competidores son la PlayStation 2 de Sony, la Gamecube de Nintendo y la Dreamcast de Sega. La consola cuenta con un catálogo de más de 825 juegos, con series como Halo, Star Wars y Fable.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>I primi passi di Microsoft nel settore delle console per videogiochi. Fa parte della sesta generazione, i cui principali concorrenti sono PlayStation 2 di Sony, Gamecube di Nintendo e Dreamcast di Sega. La console ha un catalogo di oltre 825 giochi, con serie come Halo, Star Wars e Fable.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>マイクロソフトがゲーム機部門に参入した最初の一歩。ソニーのプレイステーション2、任天堂のゲームキューブ、セガのドリームキャストを主なライバルとする第6世代に属します。このゲーム機には825以上のゲームカタログがあり、Halo、Star Wars、Fableなどのシリーズがあります。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>De eerste stappen van Microsoft op het gebied van videogameconsoles. Hij maakt deel uit van de zesde generatie waarvan de belangrijkste concurrenten de PlayStation 2 van Sony, de Gamecube van Nintendo en de Dreamcast van Sega zijn. De console heeft een catalogus van meer dan 825 spellen, met series als Halo, Star Wars en Fable.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>Pierwsze kroki Microsoftu w sektorze konsol do gier wideo. Należy ona do szóstej generacji, której głównymi konkurentami są PlayStation 2 firmy Sony, Gamecube firmy Nintendo oraz Dreamcast firmy Sega. Konsola posiada katalog ponad 825 gier, z takimi seriami jak Halo, Star Wars czy Fable.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Os primeiros passos da Microsoft no sector das consolas de videojogos. Faz parte da sexta geração cujos principais concorrentes são a PlayStation 2 da Sony, o Gamecube da Nintendo e a Dreamcast da Sega. A consola tem um catálogo de mais de 825 jogos, com séries como Halo, Star Wars e Fábula.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>Первые шаги Microsoft в секторе игровых консолей. Она относится к шестому поколению, основными конкурентами которого являются PlayStation 2 от Sony, Gamecube от Nintendo и Dreamcast от Sega. Каталог консоли насчитывает более 825 игр, среди которых такие серии, как Halo, Star Wars и Fable.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Halo: Combat Evolved (2001)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>Master Chief is the hero of Halo on Xbox, a science-fiction FPS released with the console and defined by its military universe, open combat and tactical rhythm. Between the war against the Covenant, the exploration of a mysterious ringworld and memorable co-op play, the game became a major symbol of the first Xbox.
Fun fact: Initially developed by Bungie for Mac and PC, the game was reshaped after Microsoft acquired the studio to become the flagship Xbox launch title in 2001.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Le Master Chief est le héros de Halo sur Xbox, un FPS de science-fiction qui accompagne le lancement de la console et impose son univers militaire, ses combats ouverts et son rythme tactique. Entre guerre contre l’Alliance Covenante, exploration d’un anneau-monde mystérieux et coopération marquante, le jeu devient un symbole majeur de la première Xbox.
Fun fact : Initialement développé par Bungie pour Mac et PC, le jeu est transformé après le rachat du studio par Microsoft pour devenir le titre phare du lancement de la Xbox en 2001.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Master Chief es el héroe de Halo en Xbox, un FPS de ciencia ficción que acompañó el lanzamiento de la consola e impuso su universo militar, sus combates abiertos y su ritmo táctico. Entre la guerra contra el Covenant, la exploración de un misterioso mundo anillo y un modo cooperativo memorable, el juego se convirtió en un símbolo importante de la primera Xbox.
Dato curioso: Desarrollado inicialmente por Bungie para Mac y PC, el juego fue transformado tras la compra del estudio por Microsoft para convertirse en el título estrella del lanzamiento de Xbox en 2001.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Master Chief è l’eroe di Halo su Xbox, un FPS di fantascienza che accompagnò il lancio della console e impose il suo universo militare, i combattimenti aperti e il ritmo tattico. Tra la guerra contro i Covenant, l’esplorazione di un misterioso mondo ad anello e una cooperativa memorabile, il gioco divenne un simbolo importante della prima Xbox.
Curiosità: Inizialmente sviluppato da Bungie per Mac e PC, il gioco fu trasformato dopo l’acquisizione dello studio da parte di Microsoft per diventare il titolo di punta del lancio di Xbox nel 2001.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Master Chief ist der Held von Halo auf der Xbox, einem Science-Fiction-FPS, der den Start der Konsole begleitete und durch sein militärisches Universum, offene Gefechte und taktischen Rhythmus auffiel. Zwischen dem Krieg gegen die Covenant, der Erkundung einer geheimnisvollen Ringwelt und prägendem Koop-Spiel wurde es zu einem wichtigen Symbol der ersten Xbox.
Interessante Tatsache: Ursprünglich von Bungie für Mac und PC entwickelt, wurde das Spiel nach der Übernahme des Studios durch Microsoft umgestaltet und 2001 zum wichtigsten Starttitel der Xbox.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Master Chief é o herói de Halo na Xbox, um FPS de ficção científica que acompanhou o lançamento da consola e impôs o seu universo militar, combates abertos e ritmo tático. Entre a guerra contra o Covenant, a exploração de um misterioso mundo em anel e uma cooperação marcante, o jogo tornou-se um símbolo importante da primeira Xbox.
Curiosidade: Inicialmente desenvolvido pela Bungie para Mac e PC, o jogo foi transformado após a compra do estúdio pela Microsoft para se tornar o título principal do lançamento da Xbox em 2001.</text>
</text>
</view>
</theme>
