<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>The Sinclair ZX81 is an 8-bit personal computer, designed by Sinclair Research and marketed by Timex Corporation. Based on a Zilog Z80A microprocessor running at 3.25 MHz, it had 1 kB of RAM. The display was in black and white (24 lines of 32 characters) on a standard television set. The computer did not have a sound output.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Le Sinclair ZX81 est un ordinateur personnel 8 bits, conçu par Sinclair Research et commercialisé par Timex Corporation. Basé sur un microprocesseur Zilog Z80A cadencé à 3,25 MHz, il possédait 1 ko de mémoire vive. L'affichage se faisait en noir et blanc (24 lignes de 32 caractères) sur un téléviseur standard. L'ordinateur ne possédait pas de sortie son.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>El Sinclair ZX81 fue un ordenador personal de 8 bits diseñado por Sinclair Research y comercializado por Timex Corporation. Basado en un microprocesador Zilog Z80A que funcionaba a 3,25 MHz, tenía 1 kB de RAM. La pantalla era en blanco y negro (24 líneas de 32 caracteres) en un televisor estándar. El ordenador no tenía salida de sonido.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Il Sinclair ZX81 era un personal computer a 8 bit progettato da Sinclair Research e commercializzato da Timex Corporation. Basato su un microprocessore Zilog Z80A funzionante a 3,25 MHz, aveva 1 kB di RAM. La visualizzazione era in bianco e nero (24 righe di 32 caratteri) su un televisore standard. Il computer non disponeva di un'uscita audio.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Der Sinclair ZX81 war ein 8-Bit-Personalcomputer, der von Sinclair Research entwickelt und von der Timex Corporation vermarktet wurde. Er basierte auf einem Zilog Z80A Mikroprozessor mit einer Taktfrequenz von 3,25 MHz und verfügte über 1 KB RAM. Die Anzeige erfolgte in Schwarz-Weiß (24 Zeilen à 32 Zeichen) auf einem Standardfernseher. Der Computer verfügte über keinen Tonausgang.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>O Sinclair ZX81 era um computador pessoal de 8 bits, concebido pela Sinclair Research e comercializado pela Timex Corporation. Baseado num microprocessador Zilog Z80A que funciona a 3,25 MHz, tinha 1 kB de RAM. O visor estava a preto e branco (24 linhas de 32 caracteres) num aparelho de televisão padrão. O computador não tinha uma saída de som.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>Sinclair ZX81は、Sinclair Researchが設計し、Timex Corporationが販売した8ビットパーソナルコンピュータです。3.25MHzで動作するZilog Z80Aマイクロプロセッサーをベースに、1kBのRAMを搭載していました。ディスプレイは、標準的なテレビに白黒（24行32文字）で表示されていた。このコンピュータには、サウンド出力はなかった。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>De Sinclair ZX81 was een 8-bit personal computer ontworpen door Sinclair Research en op de markt gebracht door Timex Corporation. Hij was gebaseerd op een Zilog Z80A microprocessor die draaide op 3,25 MHz en beschikte over 1 kB RAM. Het display was in zwart-wit (24 regels van 32 tekens) op een standaard televisietoestel. De computer had geen geluidsweergave.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>Sinclair ZX81 był 8-bitowym komputerem osobistym zaprojektowanym przez Sinclair Research i sprzedawanym przez Timex Corporation. Oparty na mikroprocesorze Zilog Z80A pracującym z częstotliwością 3,25 MHz, posiadał 1 kB pamięci RAM. Wyświetlacz był czarno-biały (24 linie po 32 znaki) na standardowym telewizorze. Komputer nie posiadał wyjścia dźwiękowego.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>Sinclair ZX81 был 8-битным персональным компьютером, разработанным компанией Sinclair Research и продаваемым корпорацией Timex. Основанный на микропроцессоре Zilog Z80A, работающем на частоте 3,25 МГц, он имел 1 кБ оперативной памяти. Дисплей был черно-белым (24 строки по 32 символа) и отображался на экране стандартного телевизора. Компьютер не имел звукового выхода.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;3D Monster Maze (1981)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>The dinosaur from 3D Monster Maze embodies a sudden threat inside a first-person maze where the player moves square by square while trying to escape its unpredictable appearances, creating constant tension despite the ZX81’s strict limits.
Fun fact: 3D Monster Maze is often considered one of the first first-person horror games on a home computer.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Le dinosaure de 3D Monster Maze incarne une menace invisible puis soudaine dans un labyrinthe en vue subjective où le joueur avance case par case, tente d’échapper à ses apparitions imprévisibles et ressent une tension constante malgré les limites du ZX81.
Fun fact : 3D Monster Maze est souvent considéré comme l’un des premiers jeux d’horreur en vue subjective sur micro-ordinateur.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>El dinosaurio de 3D Monster Maze encarna una amenaza repentina en un laberinto en primera persona donde el jugador avanza casilla a casilla, intenta escapar de sus apariciones imprevisibles y mantiene una tensión constante pese a los límites del ZX81.
Dato curioso: 3D Monster Maze suele considerarse uno de los primeros juegos de terror en primera persona para microordenador.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Il dinosauro di 3D Monster Maze incarna una minaccia improvvisa in un labirinto in prima persona dove il giocatore avanza casella dopo casella, cerca di sfuggire alle sue apparizioni imprevedibili e vive una tensione costante nonostante i limiti dello ZX81.
Curiosità: 3D Monster Maze è spesso considerato uno dei primi giochi horror in prima persona su microcomputer.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Der Dinosaurier aus 3D Monster Maze verkörpert eine plötzliche Bedrohung in einem Ego-Labyrinth, in dem sich der Spieler Feld für Feld bewegt, seinen unberechenbaren Auftritten entkommen muss und trotz der Grenzen des ZX81 ständige Spannung erlebt.
Interessante Tatsache: 3D Monster Maze gilt oft als eines der ersten Ego-Horrorspiele auf einem Heimcomputer.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>O dinossauro de 3D Monster Maze representa uma ameaça súbita num labirinto em primeira pessoa onde o jogador avança casa a casa, tenta escapar às suas aparições imprevisíveis e sente tensão constante apesar dos limites do ZX81.
Curiosidade: 3D Monster Maze é muitas vezes considerado um dos primeiros jogos de terror em primeira pessoa para microcomputador.</text>
</text>

</view>
</theme>