<!--
Theme: Animatix-DX for Retrobat / Batocera / Emuelec
author: Snapouille
license: creative commons CC-BY-NC-SA
originally based on: "carbon"
-->

<theme>
<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
<view name="system">

<text name="system_description" extra="true">
<text>The ZX Spectrum is a small personal computer put on the market by the English manufacturer Sinclair Research. Based on the Zilog Z80 processor running at 3.5 MHz, the Spectrum was equipped with 16 kB of RAM (an extension was also available to go from 16 to 48 kB). It was the first consumer personal computer in the UK.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Le ZX Spectrum est un petit ordinateur personnel mis sur le marché par le constructeur anglais Sinclair Research. Basé sur le processeur Zilog Z80 tournant à 3,5 MHz, le Spectrum était équipé avec 16 ko de mémoire vive (une extension était aussi disponible pour passer de 16 à 48 ko). Il s'agit du premier ordinateur personnel grand public au Royaume-Uni.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Der ZX Spectrum war ein kleiner Personalcomputer, der von dem englischen Hersteller Sinclair Research auf den Markt gebracht wurde. Der Spectrum basierte auf dem Zilog Z80-Prozessor mit 3,5 MHz und war mit 16 KB RAM ausgestattet (eine Erweiterung von 16 auf 48 KB war ebenfalls erhältlich). Es handelte sich um den ersten Personal Computer für den Massenmarkt in Großbritannien.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>El ZX Spectrum es un pequeño ordenador personal comercializado por el fabricante británico Sinclair Research. Basado en el procesador Z80 de Zilog que funcionaba a 3,5 MHz, el Spectrum estaba equipado con 16 kB de RAM (también existía una ampliación para pasar de 16 a 48 kB). Fue el primer ordenador personal de consumo del Reino Unido.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Lo ZX Spectrum è un piccolo personal computer commercializzato dal produttore britannico Sinclair Research. Basato sul processore Zilog Z80 a 3,5 MHz, lo Spectrum era dotato di 16 kB di RAM (era disponibile anche un'estensione per passare da 16 a 48 kB). È stato il primo personal computer di consumo del Regno Unito.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ja">
<text>ZX Spectrumは、イギリスのメーカーSinclair Researchが販売した小型パーソナルコンピュータです。3.5MHzで動作するZilog Z80プロセッサをベースに、Spectrumは16kBのRAMを搭載していた（16kBから48kBに拡張することも可能だった）。英国初の民生用パーソナルコンピュータである。</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="nl">
<text>De ZX Spectrum is een kleine personal computer die op de markt werd gebracht door de Britse fabrikant Sinclair Research. De Spectrum is gebaseerd op de Zilog Z80-processor op 3,5 MHz en was uitgerust met 16 kB RAM (er was ook een uitbreiding beschikbaar van 16 naar 48 kB). Het was de eerste personal computer voor consumenten in het Verenigd Koninkrijk.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pl">
<text>ZX Spectrum to mały komputer osobisty wprowadzony na rynek przez brytyjskiego producenta Sinclair Research. Oparty na procesorze Zilog Z80 pracującym z częstotliwością 3,5 MHz, Spectrum był wyposażony w 16 kB pamięci RAM (dostępne było również rozszerzenie pozwalające na przejście z 16 do 48 kB). Był to pierwszy konsumencki komputer osobisty w Wielkiej Brytanii.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>O ZX Spectrum é um pequeno computador pessoal comercializado pelo fabricante britânico Sinclair Research. Com base no processador Zilog Z80 a 3,5 MHz, o Spectrum foi equipado com 16 kB de RAM (uma extensão também estava disponível para ir de 16 a 48 kB). Foi o primeiro computador pessoal de consumo no Reino Unido.</text>
</text>

<text name="system_description" extra="true" lang="ru">
<text>ZX Spectrum - это небольшой персональный компьютер, выпущенный на рынок британской компанией Sinclair Research. Основанный на процессоре Zilog Z80, работающем на частоте 3,5 МГц, Spectrum был оснащен 16 кБ оперативной памяти (также было доступно расширение для увеличения объема памяти с 16 до 48 кБ). Это был первый потребительский персональный компьютер в Великобритании.</text>
</text>


<text name="figurine_title, figurine_title_mask" extra="true">
<text>&#160;&#160;Kwik Snax (1990)&#160;&#160;</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true">
<text>Dizzy is thrown into a fast maze game where he must collect fruit and free his captured friends. On ZX Spectrum, Kwik Snax relies on clear screens, quick movement and an arcade puzzle logic close to Fast Food, with enemies to avoid and routes to optimize.
Fun fact: Dizzy became one of Europe’s most popular computer game mascots of the late 80s, strong enough to rival Japanese icons on microcomputers.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="fr">
<text>Dizzy se retrouve dans un jeu de labyrinthe nerveux où il doit ramasser les fruits et libérer ses amis prisonniers. Sur ZX Spectrum, Kwik Snax mise sur des écrans lisibles, des déplacements rapides et une logique de puzzle arcade proche de Fast Food, avec des ennemis à éviter et des chemins à optimiser.
Fun fact : Dizzy est devenu l’une des mascottes européennes les plus populaires des années 80, au point de concurrencer les figures japonaises comme Mario sur les micro-ordinateurs.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="es">
<text>Dizzy acaba en un juego de laberintos rápido donde debe recoger fruta y liberar a sus amigos capturados. En ZX Spectrum, Kwik Snax apuesta por pantallas claras, movimientos ágiles y una lógica de puzle arcade cercana a Fast Food, con enemigos que evitar y rutas que optimizar.
Dato curioso: Dizzy se convirtió en una de las mascotas europeas más populares de los años 80, capaz de rivalizar con iconos japoneses en los microordenadores.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="it">
<text>Dizzy finisce in un frenetico gioco di labirinti dove deve raccogliere frutta e liberare i suoi amici prigionieri. Su ZX Spectrum, Kwik Snax punta su schermate leggibili, movimenti rapidi e una logica da puzzle arcade vicina a Fast Food, con nemici da evitare e percorsi da ottimizzare.
Curiosità: Dizzy divenne una delle mascotte europee più popolari degli anni 80, capace di rivaleggiare con le icone giapponesi sui microcomputer.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="de">
<text>Dizzy landet in einem schnellen Labyrinthspiel, in dem er Früchte sammeln und seine gefangenen Freunde befreien muss. Auf dem ZX Spectrum setzt Kwik Snax auf gut lesbare Bildschirme, flinke Bewegungen und Arcade-Rätsellogik nahe an Fast Food, mit Gegnern zum Ausweichen und Wegen zum Optimieren.
Interessante Tatsache: Dizzy wurde zu einer der beliebtesten europäischen Maskottchenfiguren der 80er und konnte auf Mikrocomputern mit japanischen Ikonen konkurrieren.</text>
</text>

<text name="figurine_desc" extra="true" lang="pt">
<text>Dizzy entra num jogo de labirinto rápido em que deve recolher frutas e libertar os amigos capturados. No ZX Spectrum, Kwik Snax aposta em ecrãs legíveis, movimentos rápidos e uma lógica de puzzle arcade próxima de Fast Food, com inimigos a evitar e rotas a otimizar.
Curiosidade: Dizzy tornou-se uma das mascotes europeias mais populares dos anos 80, capaz de competir com ícones japoneses nos microcomputadores.</text>
</text>
</view>
</theme>
